[[{"No": 1, "Stem": "In western countries most people ____ at the age of 65.", "Opt_1": "implement", "Opt_2": "stress", "Opt_3": "halt", "Opt_4": "retire", "Answer": "retire", "Opt_1_def": "to start or put into practice (something that has been planned)", "Opt_2_def": "to emphasize; to say what is important", "Opt_3_def": "to stop", "Opt_4_def": "to stop working"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "China won't take strong action ____ Iran's nuclear program because China just made a deal to buy lots of Iranian oil.", "Opt_1": "against", "Opt_2": "beneath", "Opt_3": "despite", "Opt_4": "worth", "Answer": "against", "Opt_1_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_2_def": "below", "Opt_3_def": "although", "Opt_4_def": "useful; having a point or purpose"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The next ____ will help you learn the difference between the present simple and present continuous tenses.", "Opt_1": "exercise", "Opt_2": "challenge", "Opt_3": "lecture", "Opt_4": "crisis", "Answer": "exercise", "Opt_1_def": "a piece of work, activity", "Opt_2_def": "difficult situation; problem", "Opt_3_def": "a talk on a particular subject; talk criticizing unacceptable behaviour", "Opt_4_def": "very dangerous situation, catastrophe"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The school received an ____ email with complaints against one of the teachers.", "Opt_1": "typical", "Opt_2": "superior", "Opt_3": "overall", "Opt_4": "anonymous", "Answer": "anonymous", "Opt_1_def": "usual", "Opt_2_def": "better", "Opt_3_def": "general", "Opt_4_def": "having no name or known author"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Students who take the class are expected to choose a contemporary problem they would like to address and ____ with each other in researching it.", "Opt_1": "damage", "Opt_2": "collaborate", "Opt_3": "belong", "Opt_4": "highlight", "Answer": "collaborate", "Opt_1_def": "to spoil or break", "Opt_2_def": "to work together", "Opt_3_def": "to be part of something or owned by someone", "Opt_4_def": "to show (the important features of something)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "This is the first step to permanently limiting enrollment growth, something that seemed only a ____ possibility earlier this year.", "Opt_1": "faint", "Opt_2": "remote", "Opt_3": "fortunate", "Opt_4": "positive", "Answer": "remote", "Opt_1_def": "not strong", "Opt_2_def": "far, distant, small", "Opt_3_def": "lucky", "Opt_4_def": "good; optimistic"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "She lied to the ____ and cheated in her test, but because of her family situation, it was decided to allow her to stay.", "Opt_1": "principal", "Opt_2": "tough", "Opt_3": "similar", "Opt_4": "subsequent", "Answer": "principal", "Opt_1_def": "most important", "Opt_2_def": "difficult, strong", "Opt_3_def": "like, almost the same as", "Opt_4_def": "next, following"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "You can lessen your ____ of getting a cold in the winter if you avoid others who already have one!", "Opt_1": "import", "Opt_2": "analyze", "Opt_3": "risk", "Opt_4": "entitle", "Answer": "risk", "Opt_1_def": "to bring in (to a country)", "Opt_2_def": "to look at something in detail in order to understand it", "Opt_3_def": "to act in a way that might lead to danger or failure", "Opt_4_def": "to give the right to do something"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Nugent claimed that how technology is organized is generally not a ____ decision but rather one based on individuals and history.", "Opt_1": "initial", "Opt_2": "mobile", "Opt_3": "rational", "Opt_4": "exact", "Answer": "rational", "Opt_1_def": "starting, first", "Opt_2_def": "moving; able to move", "Opt_3_def": "base on reason, not on emotion or instinct", "Opt_4_def": "precise, opposite of approximate"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "In an era of privatisation and market rule we are facing the fact that ____ments will have to ____ a bit more.", "Opt_1": "subsidize", "Opt_2": "violate", "Opt_3": "broadcast", "Opt_4": "govern", "Answer": "govern", "Opt_1_def": "to support financially", "Opt_2_def": "to spoil or break", "Opt_3_def": "to tell or transmit (often by means of a television programme)", "Opt_4_def": "to control or influence"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "In this article I will discuss the possible use of ____ speech recognition (ASR) for training students to improve their accents in a foreign language.", "Opt_1": "urban", "Opt_2": "credible", "Opt_3": "legitimate", "Opt_4": "automatic", "Answer": "automatic", "Opt_1_def": "of the town or city", "Opt_2_def": "believable", "Opt_3_def": "correct; allowed", "Opt_4_def": "happening by itself; happening naturally or usually"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "If you ____ the data further, you will see that there are many observations that are larger than 600.", "Opt_1": "gather", "Opt_2": "justify", "Opt_3": "inspect", "Opt_4": "comply", "Answer": "inspect", "Opt_1_def": "to bring or get together", "Opt_2_def": "to give a reason for doing something", "Opt_3_def": "to look at carefully", "Opt_4_def": "to do what someone asks or orders"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "A classic ____ of learning vocabulary is to write words and their translations in a small notebook.", "Opt_1": "method", "Opt_2": "level", "Opt_3": "insight", "Opt_4": "state", "Answer": "method", "Opt_1_def": "a way of doing something", "Opt_2_def": "standard; layer; amount", "Opt_3_def": "understanding (often of a complex problem)", "Opt_4_def": "condition, situation"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Patience was not ____ in him, but he developed it under misfortune and opposition.", "Opt_1": "obvious", "Opt_2": "accurate", "Opt_3": "pure", "Opt_4": "inherent", "Answer": "inherent", "Opt_1_def": "clear, evident", "Opt_2_def": "exact, containing no mistakes", "Opt_3_def": "complete, 100%", "Opt_4_def": "part of; a fundamental characteristic of"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The result of such abuse was increased poverty in Russia and lost ____ in the fairness of governmental institutions.", "Opt_1": "implication", "Opt_2": "belief", "Opt_3": "schedule", "Opt_4": "license", "Answer": "belief", "Opt_1_def": "result or consequence", "Opt_2_def": "what you think; what you believe in", "Opt_3_def": "timetable", "Opt_4_def": "permission to do something (often an official document)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The bulk of the ____ districts, particularly in the Northern states, were totally averse to this development.", "Opt_1": "similar", "Opt_2": "intrinsic", "Opt_3": "urban", "Opt_4": "capable", "Answer": "urban", "Opt_1_def": "like, almost the same as", "Opt_2_def": "belonging to; inherent in", "Opt_3_def": "of the town or city", "Opt_4_def": "able"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "He was a soldier, and doubtless felt that it was not his ____ to volunteer advice to the political department.", "Opt_1": "province", "Opt_2": "credit", "Opt_3": "entity", "Opt_4": "passage", "Answer": "province", "Opt_1_def": "area (of interest)", "Opt_2_def": "gained on completing a course of study; praise", "Opt_3_def": "thing; body; organization", "Opt_4_def": "a piece of written or spoken text"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Without a filter on perceptual input, our brains would have the impossible ____ of sifting through an overload of information to separate important from unimportant information.", "Opt_1": "forecast", "Opt_2": "sum", "Opt_3": "task", "Opt_4": "ability", "Answer": "task", "Opt_1_def": "prediction", "Opt_2_def": "an amount of money, total", "Opt_3_def": "job", "Opt_4_def": "ableness to do something; a skill for doing something well"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "I'm trying to ____ a machine that will do my homework for me. - Good luck!", "Opt_1": "invent", "Opt_2": "cease", "Opt_3": "realize", "Opt_4": "defend", "Answer": "invent", "Opt_1_def": "to create (often a new object)", "Opt_2_def": "to stop", "Opt_3_def": "to come to know or understand", "Opt_4_def": "to give reasons for"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The company director decided to ____ his son as the new head of marketing.", "Opt_1": "adopt", "Opt_2": "distort", "Opt_3": "reward", "Opt_4": "install", "Answer": "install", "Opt_1_def": "to take in; to start", "Opt_2_def": "to change or affect something (negatively)", "Opt_3_def": "to give something (e.g. a prize) for good work or behaviour", "Opt_4_def": "to put in (often a machine or new system)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Many people look back on their years at university as the happiest ____ in their lives.", "Opt_1": "episode", "Opt_2": "topic", "Opt_3": "victory", "Opt_4": "revenue", "Answer": "episode", "Opt_1_def": "period of time", "Opt_2_def": "area of interest or discussion", "Opt_3_def": "win", "Opt_4_def": "money, income"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Over the course of her journey in the program she has come a great distance from her primary focus as an ____ for FEMA.", "Opt_1": "agent", "Opt_2": "objective", "Opt_3": "method", "Opt_4": "passage", "Answer": "agent", "Opt_1_def": "a person who is paid to do a job for someone", "Opt_2_def": "aim or goal", "Opt_3_def": "a way of doing something", "Opt_4_def": "a piece of written or spoken text"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The internet allows people to ____ whatever they want without needing to go to the shops.", "Opt_1": "procure", "Opt_2": "employ", "Opt_3": "override", "Opt_4": "claim", "Answer": "procure", "Opt_1_def": "to get or obtain", "Opt_2_def": "to give a job to someone; to use", "Opt_3_def": "to take precedence over; to disregard", "Opt_4_def": "to state to be true"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The manager used the ____ of the opening of the new factory block to make a speech about future developments.", "Opt_1": "goal", "Opt_2": "agent", "Opt_3": "occasion", "Opt_4": "extract", "Answer": "occasion", "Opt_1_def": "aim or intention", "Opt_2_def": "a person who is paid to do a job for someone", "Opt_3_def": "time (opportunity)", "Opt_4_def": "to remove; to take out and use"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The goal of this unit is to teach students how a seemingly unimportant ____ can have a significant effect on their lives.", "Opt_1": "opinion", "Opt_2": "component", "Opt_3": "event", "Opt_4": "statement", "Answer": "event", "Opt_1_def": "view; what you think about someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "part of; an element of", "Opt_3_def": "a happening", "Opt_4_def": "a spoken sentence or sentences (sometimes prepared in advance)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The optical characteristics of the new hardware will have a profound ____ on high-speed networking across the globe.", "Opt_1": "procedure", "Opt_2": "fault", "Opt_3": "revenue", "Opt_4": "implication", "Answer": "implication", "Opt_1_def": "the way to do something", "Opt_2_def": "responsibility for a mistake or other problem", "Opt_3_def": "money, income", "Opt_4_def": "result or consequence"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Due to her student teaching commitments Murray was unable to ____ this year's event.", "Opt_1": "insist", "Opt_2": "reflect", "Opt_3": "exchange", "Opt_4": "organize", "Answer": "organize", "Opt_1_def": "to demand; to make a strong claim", "Opt_2_def": "to think or consider", "Opt_3_def": "to give or change one thing and get a different thing", "Opt_4_def": "to put into (its proper) place"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Fully 10 percent of the U.S. population has some form of learning disability; the true ____ may in fact be higher.", "Opt_1": "error", "Opt_2": "fee", "Opt_3": "figure", "Opt_4": "objection", "Answer": "figure", "Opt_1_def": "a mistake", "Opt_2_def": "money for a service (e.g. a baking service)", "Opt_3_def": "number", "Opt_4_def": "a statement of disagreement or disapproval"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "But his son, who had hoped to ____ the throne of Armenia, could not conceal his discontent.", "Opt_1": "occupy", "Opt_2": "achieve", "Opt_3": "shrink", "Opt_4": "decline", "Answer": "occupy", "Opt_1_def": "to up space or time", "Opt_2_def": "to gain or get something (often academic success)", "Opt_3_def": "to get smaller", "Opt_4_def": "to go down or get worse"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Many people buy ____ vitamin pills because they do not believe that they get enough vitamins from their regular food.", "Opt_1": "vast", "Opt_2": "basic", "Opt_3": "genuine", "Opt_4": "supplementary", "Answer": "supplementary", "Opt_1_def": "very large", "Opt_2_def": "first or easy", "Opt_3_def": "real and authentic", "Opt_4_def": "extra; additional"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "A common cause of ____ between the teacher and a student is when the student comes late to class for no good reason.", "Opt_1": "operation", "Opt_2": "stereotype", "Opt_3": "role", "Opt_4": "dispute", "Answer": "dispute", "Opt_1_def": "procedure; happening; process", "Opt_2_def": "a fixed idea about someone or something (often that is only partly true)", "Opt_3_def": "job or function", "Opt_4_def": "argument; conflict"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Since we can't observe it directly, we need to ____ it from the things we can observe.", "Opt_1": "impress", "Opt_2": "infer", "Opt_3": "broadcast", "Opt_4": "select", "Answer": "infer", "Opt_1_def": "to create a favourable reaction", "Opt_2_def": "to come to a conclusion about something", "Opt_3_def": "to tell or transmit (often by means of a television programme)", "Opt_4_def": "to choose"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The ____ minister has decided to cancel the planned visit to Batavia in view of the outbreak of war in the country.", "Opt_1": "severe", "Opt_2": "satisfactory", "Opt_3": "drastic", "Opt_4": "prime", "Answer": "prime", "Opt_1_def": "serious, harsh", "Opt_2_def": "enough;OK", "Opt_3_def": "severe; great", "Opt_4_def": "most important"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "He rightly concludes that the end of the Cold War failed to ____ significant changes in the Horn of Africa or to improve the mutual security of states.", "Opt_1": "tolerate", "Opt_2": "induce", "Opt_3": "train", "Opt_4": "protect", "Answer": "induce", "Opt_1_def": "to allow to happen; to bear", "Opt_2_def": "to make happen; to force", "Opt_3_def": "to teach someone how to do a job", "Opt_4_def": "to keep something out of danger"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The government neither intends to ____ on the event nor even to admit that it actually happened.", "Opt_1": "choice", "Opt_2": "motive", "Opt_3": "comment", "Opt_4": "justice", "Answer": "comment", "Opt_1_def": "decision, selection", "Opt_2_def": "reason", "Opt_3_def": "a short written or spoken statement or opinion", "Opt_4_def": "fairness in law"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "On-line learning applications will continue to ____ as educational institutions and. business corporations seek new ways to expand their services.", "Opt_1": "harm", "Opt_2": "multiply", "Opt_3": "proceed", "Opt_4": "attain", "Answer": "multiply", "Opt_1_def": "to damage or injure", "Opt_2_def": "to increase greatly", "Opt_3_def": "to go forward (and do ..)", "Opt_4_def": "to get, achieve"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Being under the ____ of illegal drugs or alcohol on the job may pose serious risks.", "Opt_1": "proportion", "Opt_2": "relationship", "Opt_3": "gain", "Opt_4": "influence", "Answer": "influence", "Opt_1_def": "amount; number; percentage", "Opt_2_def": "the way to things are connected", "Opt_3_def": "to get; to increase in ..", "Opt_4_def": "effect"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "I do not ____ about your right to an opinion, but I do ____ about your inability to see the truth when it is explained to you.", "Opt_1": "protest", "Opt_2": "enhance", "Opt_3": "reveal", "Opt_4": "strive", "Answer": "protest", "Opt_1_def": "to express anger or unhappiness about something", "Opt_2_def": "to make something better", "Opt_3_def": "to show or uncover", "Opt_4_def": "to work or try hard"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "What is the ____ between continental and oceanic volcanic eruptions?", "Opt_1": "comparison", "Opt_2": "prestige", "Opt_3": "occasion", "Opt_4": "phenomenon", "Answer": "comparison", "Opt_1_def": "a statement of how two things are similar or different", "Opt_2_def": "fame and respect", "Opt_3_def": "time (opportunity)", "Opt_4_def": "a happening (often unusual or unexpected)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "There is a widespread ____ that scaling up HIV voluntary counseling and testing (VCT) programs in Africa will have large prevention benefits.", "Opt_1": "anomaly", "Opt_2": "belief", "Opt_3": "debt", "Opt_4": "attribute", "Answer": "belief", "Opt_1_def": "an unexpected happening or piece of data", "Opt_2_def": "what you think; what you believe in", "Opt_3_def": "something owed to another person (often money)", "Opt_4_def": "characteristic; property"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "If you work hard all lesson, I will ____ you by letting you go to lunch five minutes early.", "Opt_1": "request", "Opt_2": "recur", "Opt_3": "reward", "Opt_4": "exhaust", "Answer": "reward", "Opt_1_def": "to ask politely", "Opt_2_def": "to happen again", "Opt_3_def": "to give something (e.g. a prize) for good work or behaviour", "Opt_4_def": "to use up"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "He is the inevitable ____ for the leading role in the play. He's by far the best actor in the school.", "Opt_1": "incident", "Opt_2": "prejudice", "Opt_3": "choice", "Opt_4": "task", "Answer": "choice", "Opt_1_def": "happening; event", "Opt_2_def": "bias, discrimination, beliefs or feelings influenced by one's own background", "Opt_3_def": "decision, selection", "Opt_4_def": "job"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Because of ____ protest, the government had to go back on its decision to put up the tax on petrol.", "Opt_1": "domestic", "Opt_2": "instant", "Opt_3": "massive", "Opt_4": "passive", "Answer": "massive", "Opt_1_def": "home", "Opt_2_def": "immediate", "Opt_3_def": "very large", "Opt_4_def": "not active; unresponsive"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The cost of gas (petrol) will continue to ____ as the price of oil goes up or down.", "Opt_1": "train", "Opt_2": "donate", "Opt_3": "ruin", "Opt_4": "fluctuate", "Answer": "fluctuate", "Opt_1_def": "to teach someone how to do a job", "Opt_2_def": "to give (usually money)", "Opt_3_def": "to spoil or damage", "Opt_4_def": "to vary; to rise and fall"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Many countries have a minimum wage - this is the smallest amount of money that people may ____ for a full-time job.", "Opt_1": "facilitate", "Opt_2": "attain", "Opt_3": "earn", "Opt_4": "recur", "Answer": "earn", "Opt_1_def": "to make something easier", "Opt_2_def": "to get, achieve", "Opt_3_def": "to get money or another reward (usually by working for it)", "Opt_4_def": "to happen again"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "With his difficult family ____ it is not really surprising that he's having trouble in school.", "Opt_1": "procedure", "Opt_2": "circumstances", "Opt_3": "reply", "Opt_4": "legislation", "Answer": "circumstances", "Opt_1_def": "the way to do something", "Opt_2_def": "situation", "Opt_3_def": "an answer", "Opt_4_def": "governmental rule; law"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "It is difficult to ____ the importance of the internet.", "Opt_1": "migrate", "Opt_2": "facilitate", "Opt_3": "exaggerate", "Opt_4": "inhibit", "Answer": "exaggerate", "Opt_1_def": "to go to another place", "Opt_2_def": "to make something easier", "Opt_3_def": "to \"overstate\" the truth; to say something is bigger or better than it really is", "Opt_4_def": "to prevent or stop"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The problems of drug-taking at the school ____ to get out of control.", "Opt_1": "enlarge", "Opt_2": "deviate", "Opt_3": "lessen", "Opt_4": "threaten", "Answer": "threaten", "Opt_1_def": "to make larger", "Opt_2_def": "to be different", "Opt_3_def": "to reduce", "Opt_4_def": "to warn or show signs of danger"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The ____ aim of teaching should be to teach the students how to teach themselves.", "Opt_1": "main", "Opt_2": "exact", "Opt_3": "deliberate", "Opt_4": "thorough", "Answer": "main", "Opt_1_def": "most important", "Opt_2_def": "precise, opposite of approximate", "Opt_3_def": "intentional, not by accident", "Opt_4_def": "complete and careful"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Below are some suggestions for achieving a ____ between your work and personal life.", "Opt_1": "propensity", "Opt_2": "balance", "Opt_3": "stereotype", "Opt_4": "province", "Answer": "balance", "Opt_1_def": "tendency; desire", "Opt_2_def": "equalness", "Opt_3_def": "a fixed idea about someone or something (often that is only partly true)", "Opt_4_def": "area (of interest)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The company directors invited the workers' union to ____ in a meeting to discuss the new factory.", "Opt_1": "presume", "Opt_2": "govern", "Opt_3": "justify", "Opt_4": "participate", "Answer": "participate", "Opt_1_def": "to believe, assume", "Opt_2_def": "to control or influence", "Opt_3_def": "to give a reason for doing something", "Opt_4_def": "to take part"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The library is going to extend the space it has made ____ for computers and video screens.", "Opt_1": "abstract", "Opt_2": "proper", "Opt_3": "loose", "Opt_4": "available", "Answer": "available", "Opt_1_def": "not specific or concrete", "Opt_2_def": "correct, appropriate", "Opt_3_def": "not firm or finished", "Opt_4_def": "can be had (bought or obtained)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "My father has a workshop in the garage so I have a lot of ____ knowledge.", "Opt_1": "technical", "Opt_2": "considerable", "Opt_3": "prompt", "Opt_4": "logical", "Answer": "technical", "Opt_1_def": "to do with machines or the way things work", "Opt_2_def": "very big; very much", "Opt_3_def": "quick; on or before time", "Opt_4_def": "making sense"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "What steps do I take to draw a random sample of a target audience in my county to do a needs assessment or ____ baseline data?", "Opt_1": "reserve", "Opt_2": "suppose", "Opt_3": "gather", "Opt_4": "exert", "Answer": "gather", "Opt_1_def": "to keep", "Opt_2_def": "to think, imagine", "Opt_3_def": "to bring or get together", "Opt_4_def": "to use"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The ocean floor is the last great ____ waiting to be exploited for its oil and other minerals.", "Opt_1": "asset", "Opt_2": "sphere", "Opt_3": "constraint", "Opt_4": "resource", "Answer": "resource", "Opt_1_def": "advantage", "Opt_2_def": "area of interest", "Opt_3_def": "to hold back; to prevent", "Opt_4_def": "a source of information or material"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Therefore, if a farm has efficiency problems, simply expanding the ____ may just magnify the problems.", "Opt_1": "operation", "Opt_2": "property", "Opt_3": "interpretation", "Opt_4": "attribute", "Answer": "operation", "Opt_1_def": "procedure; happening; process", "Opt_2_def": "the things that belong to someone, especially their home", "Opt_3_def": "explanation; assessment", "Opt_4_def": "characteristic; property"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "On the whole the great bulk of Canadian immigration of the past ____ has been drawn from the English-speaking countries.", "Opt_1": "incident", "Opt_2": "surface", "Opt_3": "generation", "Opt_4": "obligation", "Answer": "generation", "Opt_1_def": "happening; event", "Opt_2_def": "the outside layer of an object", "Opt_3_def": "group of people all born around the same time", "Opt_4_def": "a requirement to do something"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "On December 4, 1955, the ____ decision was made to boycott the bus system until they were treated with courtesy and black drivers could be hired.", "Opt_1": "frequent", "Opt_2": "anonymous", "Opt_3": "inherent", "Opt_4": "common", "Answer": "anonymous", "Opt_1_def": "often", "Opt_2_def": "having no name or known author", "Opt_3_def": "part of; a fundamental characteristic of", "Opt_4_def": "often seen or happening"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "What would you ____ the patient so that the injury not recur?", "Opt_1": "advise", "Opt_2": "avoid", "Opt_3": "assert", "Opt_4": "dictate", "Answer": "advise", "Opt_1_def": "to say what someone should do; to give advice", "Opt_2_def": "to not do something or go somewhere", "Opt_3_def": "to claim, to say strongly", "Opt_4_def": "to tell someone what to do"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "If you want to have a more interesting style of presentation, ____ the speed and tone of your voice.", "Opt_1": "circumstances", "Opt_2": "field", "Opt_3": "vary", "Opt_4": "phrase", "Answer": "vary", "Opt_1_def": "situation", "Opt_2_def": "area of interest or study", "Opt_3_def": "to change or be different", "Opt_4_def": "one achieves best success through constantly applied pressure."}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "While we must ____ all terrorism, and we have many local enemies in various parts of the world.", "Opt_1": "consume", "Opt_2": "contemplate", "Opt_3": "oppose", "Opt_4": "declare", "Answer": "oppose", "Opt_1_def": "to use, or use up", "Opt_2_def": "to think about; to consider", "Opt_3_def": "to be against or fight against something", "Opt_4_def": "to state"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "If you ____ your calculator like that, you'll break it.", "Opt_1": "consent", "Opt_2": "abuse", "Opt_3": "encourage", "Opt_4": "conserve", "Answer": "abuse", "Opt_1_def": "to agree", "Opt_2_def": "to treat someone or something badly", "Opt_3_def": "to move someone to do something by positive talk; support or help", "Opt_4_def": "to preserve; to not use"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The paper was unable to attract ____ support and ceased publication after a few months.", "Opt_1": "crucial", "Opt_2": "political", "Opt_3": "confident", "Opt_4": "sufficient", "Answer": "sufficient", "Opt_1_def": "extremely important", "Opt_2_def": "to do government and politics", "Opt_3_def": "sure that something will happen", "Opt_4_def": "enough"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Costrell also found it disturbing that the administration failed to exert its ____ to ensure that the funds were appropriately spent.", "Opt_1": "impulse", "Opt_2": "exercise", "Opt_3": "responsibility", "Opt_4": "principle", "Answer": "responsibility", "Opt_1_def": "reason or motivation to do something", "Opt_2_def": "a piece of work, activity", "Opt_3_def": "job, duty to do something", "Opt_4_def": "rule"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "You have had ____ chances to improve your behaviour. Now it's too late.", "Opt_1": "compulsory", "Opt_2": "competent", "Opt_3": "abundant", "Opt_4": "reliable", "Answer": "abundant", "Opt_1_def": "required, must be done", "Opt_2_def": "good at something (often a job)", "Opt_3_def": "existing in large quantities", "Opt_4_def": "can be trusted, does not let you down \r\n"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Can we ____ the scientists and experts to make the right decisions to protect the environment?", "Opt_1": "trust", "Opt_2": "acquire", "Opt_3": "preserve", "Opt_4": "devote", "Answer": "trust", "Opt_1_def": "to believe that someone or something will be or work as promised", "Opt_2_def": "to get or obtain", "Opt_3_def": "forward,\" said Michele Gougeon.", "Opt_4_def": "to give (time) to"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "If you fail the last test, this will seriously affect your ____ grade for the year.", "Opt_1": "frequent", "Opt_2": "distinct", "Opt_3": "reasonable", "Opt_4": "overall", "Answer": "overall", "Opt_1_def": "often", "Opt_2_def": "clear and strong", "Opt_3_def": "acceptable, quite good", "Opt_4_def": "general"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "You can buy each ____ on the school supplies list from the bookstore.", "Opt_1": "individual", "Opt_2": "equipment", "Opt_3": "authority", "Opt_4": "item", "Answer": "item", "Opt_1_def": "one person", "Opt_2_def": "the things you need (to do a job or play sport, etc.)", "Opt_3_def": "control (right to control)", "Opt_4_def": "thing, element"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The U.S. firms selling steel in India must compete against the firms from not ____ India but Europe, Japan, Korea and China as well.", "Opt_1": "merely", "Opt_2": "thereby", "Opt_3": "barely", "Opt_4": "conversely", "Answer": "merely", "Opt_1_def": "only, just, simply", "Opt_2_def": "by doing this", "Opt_3_def": "not very much; hardly", "Opt_4_def": "opposite to what was just said; on the other hand"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The Coroner who made the investigation, was unable to ____ whether it was suicide or accidental death.", "Opt_1": "determine", "Opt_2": "deserve", "Opt_3": "deduce", "Opt_4": "generate", "Answer": "determine", "Opt_1_def": "to find out; to establish or identify; state", "Opt_2_def": "to have the right to something", "Opt_3_def": "to come to a conclusion about someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "to make or produce"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The government reduced its grant to the Arts Council after it was ____ that much of the money had been wasted.", "Opt_1": "precede", "Opt_2": "promote", "Opt_3": "acknowledge", "Opt_4": "found", "Answer": "found", "Opt_1_def": "to go or be before someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "to encourage; to raise to a higher position in a job", "Opt_3_def": "to agree with; admit to; give credit to", "Opt_4_def": "to begin (often an organization)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Everyone has the right to a ____ of living adequate for the health and well-being of himself and of his family, including food, clothing, and shelter.", "Opt_1": "layer", "Opt_2": "standard", "Opt_3": "battle", "Opt_4": "schedule", "Answer": "standard", "Opt_1_def": "level", "Opt_2_def": "quality", "Opt_3_def": "fight, part of a war", "Opt_4_def": "timetable"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "It is hardly a surprise that national governments have failed to solve global problems, since they have also failed to solve their own ____ problems.", "Opt_1": "several", "Opt_2": "domestic", "Opt_3": "ancient", "Opt_4": "liable", "Answer": "domestic", "Opt_1_def": "many (about 6 or seven)", "Opt_2_def": "home", "Opt_3_def": "very old", "Opt_4_def": "likely to happen; at risk of happening"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "She always goes ____ what is expected of her. No wonder she gets such good grades.", "Opt_1": "beneath", "Opt_2": "due", "Opt_3": "beyond", "Opt_4": "prior", "Answer": "beyond", "Opt_1_def": "below", "Opt_2_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_3_def": "further than: past", "Opt_4_def": "before"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The service ____ of the UK economy is much more successful than the manufacturing ____.", "Opt_1": "battle", "Opt_2": "instinct", "Opt_3": "sector", "Opt_4": "individual", "Answer": "sector", "Opt_1_def": "fight, part of a war", "Opt_2_def": "natural feeling or reaction", "Opt_3_def": "part; area", "Opt_4_def": "one person"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The former is preferable for a field of inquiry that is still in its infancy, whereas the latter is ____ for fields that have a developed theory.", "Opt_1": "vague", "Opt_2": "ordinary", "Opt_3": "suitable", "Opt_4": "latter", "Answer": "suitable", "Opt_1_def": "not clear or strong", "Opt_2_def": "usual, typical, every day", "Opt_3_def": "good for a particular job or purpose", "Opt_4_def": "the second of two things mentioned"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Archaeologists found some Roman coins ____ the town wall.", "Opt_1": "against", "Opt_2": "due", "Opt_3": "except", "Opt_4": "beneath", "Answer": "beneath", "Opt_1_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_2_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_3_def": "but (not)", "Opt_4_def": "below"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "It's not ____ asking him. He doesn't know enough about computers.", "Opt_1": "against", "Opt_2": "prior", "Opt_3": "worth", "Opt_4": "beneath", "Answer": "worth", "Opt_1_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_2_def": "before", "Opt_3_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_4_def": "below"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Students engaging in scheduled curricular work have ____ over other students.", "Opt_1": "priority", "Opt_2": "passage", "Opt_3": "progress", "Opt_4": "topic", "Answer": "priority", "Opt_1_def": "first and most important task", "Opt_2_def": "a piece of written or spoken text", "Opt_3_def": "improvement or development", "Opt_4_def": "area of interest or discussion"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Over 100 students marched to the Hoover Institution to ____ a possible U.S. war in Iraq.", "Opt_1": "protest", "Opt_2": "extend", "Opt_3": "overcome", "Opt_4": "complicate", "Answer": "protest", "Opt_1_def": "to express anger or unhappiness about something", "Opt_2_def": "to make longer in time or space", "Opt_3_def": "to conquer, defeat", "Opt_4_def": "to make things more complex or difficult"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Please ____ your books and check each other's writing.", "Opt_1": "explain", "Opt_2": "abandon", "Opt_3": "exchange", "Opt_4": "explore", "Answer": "exchange", "Opt_1_def": "to give the reason for something or say how to do something", "Opt_2_def": "to leave or give up", "Opt_3_def": "to give or change one thing and get a different thing", "Opt_4_def": "to look into a place or thing (in order to learn more about it)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Insurance salesmen often ____ profits that they know are very unlikely.", "Opt_1": "add", "Opt_2": "examine", "Opt_3": "require", "Opt_4": "assert", "Answer": "assert", "Opt_1_def": "to include; to give or say extra", "Opt_2_def": "to look at carefully", "Opt_3_def": "to need", "Opt_4_def": "to claim, to say strongly"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The main ____ of the proposed research is to investigate the influence of West African languages.", "Opt_1": "objective", "Opt_2": "symptom", "Opt_3": "exponent", "Opt_4": "region", "Answer": "objective", "Opt_1_def": "aim or goal", "Opt_2_def": "sign (often of a disease or other problem)", "Opt_3_def": "someone who holds and states an opinion", "Opt_4_def": "part of a place"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "This week's anniversary of the US-led war against Iraq is an appropriate ____ to ask: Are Americans safer than we were a year ago?", "Opt_1": "justice", "Opt_2": "scope", "Opt_3": "situation", "Opt_4": "occasion", "Answer": "occasion", "Opt_1_def": "fairness in law", "Opt_2_def": "extent, range", "Opt_3_def": "circumstances", "Opt_4_def": "time (opportunity)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "During this period she developed her ideas on art, her main one being that the best art did not ____ on reality but evoked the state of the soul.", "Opt_1": "base", "Opt_2": "annotate", "Opt_3": "survive", "Opt_4": "focus", "Answer": "focus", "Opt_1_def": "to use as a way of doing or deciding something", "Opt_2_def": "to make notes on a piece of writing", "Opt_3_def": "to not die", "Opt_4_def": "to direct attention (on an issue)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Recent government IT initiatives ____ narrowly on a specific technical problem, like enabling mobile data communication or Web-based transactions.", "Opt_1": "focus", "Opt_2": "assist", "Opt_3": "frustrate", "Opt_4": "abandon", "Answer": "focus", "Opt_1_def": "to direct attention (on an issue)", "Opt_2_def": "to help", "Opt_3_def": "to stop or prevent", "Opt_4_def": "to leave or give up"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Some students see no ____ for learning German - especially if they know they will only be in the country for a short time.", "Opt_1": "motive", "Opt_2": "intention", "Opt_3": "account", "Opt_4": "struggle", "Answer": "motive", "Opt_1_def": "reason", "Opt_2_def": "plan, aim", "Opt_3_def": "a written or spoken report of a happening", "Opt_4_def": "a fight, a difficult situation to be overcome"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Many parents ____ their children to the bedroom when they behave badly.", "Opt_1": "formulate", "Opt_2": "resist", "Opt_3": "confine", "Opt_4": "displace", "Answer": "confine", "Opt_1_def": "to express", "Opt_2_def": "to fight against", "Opt_3_def": "to limit", "Opt_4_def": "to push out or take the place of something or someone"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "It is very satisfying as a teacher to see the ____ in the ability of your students.", "Opt_1": "district", "Opt_2": "growth", "Opt_3": "debate", "Opt_4": "counsel", "Answer": "growth", "Opt_1_def": "region of a city", "Opt_2_def": "development, increase", "Opt_3_def": "formal discussion", "Opt_4_def": "advice; advisor"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The book focuses on the key role the family plays as teenagers navigate the difficult ____ from childhood to adulthood.", "Opt_1": "exercise", "Opt_2": "interval", "Opt_3": "transition", "Opt_4": "priority", "Answer": "transition", "Opt_1_def": "a piece of work, activity", "Opt_2_def": "a period of time", "Opt_3_def": "a move from one (place, time, etc.) to another", "Opt_4_def": "first and most important task"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "This document will ____ some of the problems that could exist because the computer is unable to install updates for Windows Vista.", "Opt_1": "emphasize", "Opt_2": "arrange", "Opt_3": "refute", "Opt_4": "explain", "Answer": "explain", "Opt_1_def": "to stress, to say something strongly", "Opt_2_def": "to plan to happen; to group together", "Opt_3_def": "to prove to be untrue; to deny", "Opt_4_def": "to give the reason for something or say how to do something"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Most students agree that teachers need ____ them on how much they have learned.", "Opt_1": "suggest", "Opt_2": "assess", "Opt_3": "succeed", "Opt_4": "reform", "Answer": "assess", "Opt_1_def": "to say an idea; to recommend", "Opt_2_def": "to judge or test", "Opt_3_def": "to do well", "Opt_4_def": "to change and improve"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "It is not clear to me how you can simultaneously make cannabis ____ and expect the consumption of it to go down.", "Opt_1": "verbal", "Opt_2": "minor", "Opt_3": "legal", "Opt_4": "mental", "Answer": "legal", "Opt_1_def": "to do with words and language (especially the spoken language)", "Opt_2_def": "small, not important", "Opt_3_def": "acceptable in law (to do with the law)", "Opt_4_def": "of the brain or mind"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The department may ____ students of superior promise but deficient preparation, provided that such students correct their deficiencies.", "Opt_1": "halt", "Opt_2": "assume", "Opt_3": "admit", "Opt_4": "inform", "Answer": "admit", "Opt_1_def": "to stop", "Opt_2_def": "to believe to be true; to presume or predict", "Opt_3_def": "to allow to enter", "Opt_4_def": "to say, give information"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Your first piece of writing was very good, but the ____ ones have been of much lower quality.", "Opt_1": "instant", "Opt_2": "numerous", "Opt_3": "subsequent", "Opt_4": "mental", "Answer": "subsequent", "Opt_1_def": "immediate", "Opt_2_def": "very many", "Opt_3_def": "next, following", "Opt_4_def": "of the brain or mind"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The school plans to ____ the sports field so that games can be played after dark.", "Opt_1": "exist", "Opt_2": "illuminate", "Opt_3": "drain", "Opt_4": "cooperate", "Answer": "illuminate", "Opt_1_def": "to be alive, to be in the world", "Opt_2_def": "to show clearly; to light up", "Opt_3_def": "to take away; to get rid of", "Opt_4_def": "to work (well) with another person"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Many prisons cannot comply with this law ____ to lack of space and inadequate facilities.", "Opt_1": "except", "Opt_2": "beneath", "Opt_3": "due", "Opt_4": "prior", "Answer": "due", "Opt_1_def": "but (not)", "Opt_2_def": "below", "Opt_3_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_4_def": "before"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "In this section of the course, we ____ less familiar territory, namely the equations of relativistic acceleration.", "Opt_1": "base", "Opt_2": "assist", "Opt_3": "cover", "Opt_4": "expand", "Answer": "cover", "Opt_1_def": "to use as a way of doing or deciding something", "Opt_2_def": "to help", "Opt_3_def": "to do; to complete", "Opt_4_def": "to get bigger; to move into new areas"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Many people oppose the ban on smoking in public places, but the ____ are in favour of it.", "Opt_1": "majority", "Opt_2": "sample", "Opt_3": "precaution", "Opt_4": "extract", "Answer": "majority", "Opt_1_def": "more than 50%", "Opt_2_def": "example; a smaller number of a larger collection", "Opt_3_def": "something done to avoid danger, harm or problems", "Opt_4_def": "to remove; to take out and use"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "This is the completely rational response of a country that has no hope of defeating the United States in battle but ____ wants to insure that it isn't attacked.", "Opt_1": "simply", "Opt_2": "roughly", "Opt_3": "thus", "Opt_4": "nevertheless", "Answer": "nevertheless", "Opt_1_def": "completely; just; only", "Opt_2_def": "about, approximately", "Opt_3_def": "so", "Opt_4_def": "however (although / despite that)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The future energy system will need to eliminate the unacceptable risk that the ____ system places on the environment.", "Opt_1": "publish", "Opt_2": "cooperate", "Opt_3": "present", "Opt_4": "magnify", "Answer": "present", "Opt_1_def": "to make available in paper or online form", "Opt_2_def": "to work (well) with another person", "Opt_3_def": "to give or show; to make a presentation", "Opt_4_def": "to make or show larger"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Lack of sufficient ____ often prohibits sound management activities that are necessary to the company's long-term health and stability.", "Opt_1": "layer", "Opt_2": "command", "Opt_3": "revenue", "Opt_4": "element", "Answer": "revenue", "Opt_1_def": "level", "Opt_2_def": "control", "Opt_3_def": "money, income", "Opt_4_def": "aspect, part"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "There is evidence that increases in short sale transactions ____ stock price declines.", "Opt_1": "precede", "Opt_2": "publish", "Opt_3": "depend", "Opt_4": "purchase", "Answer": "precede", "Opt_1_def": "to go or be before someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "to make available in paper or online form", "Opt_3_def": "be influenced (by)", "Opt_4_def": "to buy"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The government can advise people to save money for old age, but it cannot ____ them to do it.", "Opt_1": "reserve", "Opt_2": "spread", "Opt_3": "force", "Opt_4": "behave", "Answer": "force", "Opt_1_def": "to keep", "Opt_2_def": "to move (over a wider area)", "Opt_3_def": "to make happen or to make someone do something", "Opt_4_def": "to act or do things in a certain way"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Stated simply, this ____ means that averaged over large enough distances, one part of the Universe looks approximately like any other part.", "Opt_1": "account", "Opt_2": "limit", "Opt_3": "principle", "Opt_4": "consequence", "Answer": "principle", "Opt_1_def": "a written or spoken report of a happening", "Opt_2_def": "extent, boundary", "Opt_3_def": "rule", "Opt_4_def": "result"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "We got some very ____ results in our science experiment. I think the thermometer was not working correctly.", "Opt_1": "abnormal", "Opt_2": "flexible", "Opt_3": "contemporary", "Opt_4": "widespread", "Answer": "abnormal", "Opt_1_def": "not normal, unusual", "Opt_2_def": "can be changed or bent", "Opt_3_def": "of this time, happening now", "Opt_4_def": "common"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The requirements threaten to decrease family and individual student control over the ____ process.", "Opt_1": "ability", "Opt_2": "transition", "Opt_3": "benefit", "Opt_4": "fault", "Answer": "transition", "Opt_1_def": "ableness to do something; a skill for doing something well", "Opt_2_def": "a move from one (place, time, etc.) to another", "Opt_3_def": "advantage", "Opt_4_def": "responsibility for a mistake or other problem"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Her ____ was that the Korean people believe that the U.S. policy is to have a divided Korea and that the U.S. is the reason the two countries are not united.", "Opt_1": "trait", "Opt_2": "account", "Opt_3": "power", "Opt_4": "perspective", "Answer": "perspective", "Opt_1_def": "characteristic; aspect", "Opt_2_def": "a written or spoken report of a happening", "Opt_3_def": "the right or authority to do something", "Opt_4_def": "view; opinion; way of thinking"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "You will receive a lengthy, very ____ email, which in short, states that your unsubscribe request did not succeed.", "Opt_1": "practical", "Opt_2": "perpetual", "Opt_3": "technical", "Opt_4": "obsolete", "Answer": "technical", "Opt_1_def": "useful; possible", "Opt_2_def": "continuing for ever; never disappearing", "Opt_3_def": "to do with machines or the way things work", "Opt_4_def": "not used or needed any more; out of date"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "In most countries of the world ____ is compulsory for all children.", "Opt_1": "period", "Opt_2": "summary", "Opt_3": "education", "Opt_4": "legislation", "Answer": "education", "Opt_1_def": "a length of time (e.g. a lesson)", "Opt_2_def": "a short account of the most important details", "Opt_3_def": "schooling", "Opt_4_def": "governmental rule; law"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The government has done a deal with the nurses union in order to ____ strikes in hospitals.", "Opt_1": "dictate", "Opt_2": "appear", "Opt_3": "cooperate", "Opt_4": "avoid", "Answer": "avoid", "Opt_1_def": "to tell someone what to do", "Opt_2_def": "to come, be seen", "Opt_3_def": "to work (well) with another person", "Opt_4_def": "to not do something or go somewhere"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "In this problem you have to ____ that x=7.", "Opt_1": "trigger", "Opt_2": "prove", "Opt_3": "communicate", "Opt_4": "consume", "Answer": "prove", "Opt_1_def": "to (cause to) start", "Opt_2_def": "to show to be true", "Opt_3_def": "to convey information", "Opt_4_def": "to use, or use up"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Many people ____ before eating raw fish for the first time. They are not sure what it will taste like.", "Opt_1": "hesitate", "Opt_2": "attend", "Opt_3": "express", "Opt_4": "allege", "Answer": "hesitate", "Opt_1_def": "to pause before saying or doing something", "Opt_2_def": "to go to, to be present at", "Opt_3_def": "to say or mean", "Opt_4_def": "to claim or state"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The priests of this ____ did not give their answers by inspiration, but occupied themselves chiefly with the interpretation of dreams", "Opt_1": "item", "Opt_2": "institution", "Opt_3": "distance", "Opt_4": "bias", "Answer": "institution", "Opt_1_def": "thing, element", "Opt_2_def": "a large organization; an important system or custom", "Opt_3_def": "how far it is from one place to another", "Opt_4_def": "favouring one more than another, prejudice"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "For republicans since Cicero there can be no liberty without law, and no valid law or ____ system when liberty is disregarded.", "Opt_1": "legal", "Opt_2": "appropriate", "Opt_3": "main", "Opt_4": "permanent", "Answer": "legal", "Opt_1_def": "acceptable in law (to do with the law)", "Opt_2_def": "right (for the occasion; suitable", "Opt_3_def": "most important", "Opt_4_def": "lasting for ever or for a very long time"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The company yesterday said it made a ____ of \ufffd\ufffd217.46 million for the six months to June.", "Opt_1": "procedure", "Opt_2": "opportunity", "Opt_3": "effect", "Opt_4": "profit", "Answer": "profit", "Opt_1_def": "the way to do something", "Opt_2_def": "chance", "Opt_3_def": "result", "Opt_4_def": "money gained"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Selecting the panelists is no easy task, and is subject to ____ lobbying.", "Opt_1": "intense", "Opt_2": "imaginary", "Opt_3": "instant", "Opt_4": "consistent", "Answer": "intense", "Opt_1_def": "strong, extreme", "Opt_2_def": "not real; from the imagination", "Opt_3_def": "immediate", "Opt_4_def": "regular or predictable; remaining the same"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Princeton University computer scientist Edward Felton has decided not to publish a paper on how his research team broke the ____ of copyright protection.", "Opt_1": "target", "Opt_2": "code", "Opt_3": "hypothesis", "Opt_4": "means", "Answer": "code", "Opt_1_def": "aim, goal", "Opt_2_def": "a set of rules", "Opt_3_def": "idea or prediction", "Opt_4_def": "way"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "We will ____ growth and development in our district communities by serving as a key educational resource.", "Opt_1": "explain", "Opt_2": "reduce", "Opt_3": "drain", "Opt_4": "facilitate", "Answer": "facilitate", "Opt_1_def": "to give the reason for something or say how to do something", "Opt_2_def": "to make smaller or shorter", "Opt_3_def": "to take away; to get rid of", "Opt_4_def": "to make something easier"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Rexhepi said the incident damaged the ____ for the upcoming talks on practical matters between Kosovar and Serbian officials.", "Opt_1": "extent", "Opt_2": "scope", "Opt_3": "atmosphere", "Opt_4": "field", "Answer": "atmosphere", "Opt_1_def": "size, amount", "Opt_2_def": "extent, range", "Opt_3_def": "mood among people or groups", "Opt_4_def": "area of interest or study"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Stubbornness is a trait that is sometimes ____ and sometimes negative.", "Opt_1": "familiar", "Opt_2": "likely", "Opt_3": "positive", "Opt_4": "explicit", "Answer": "positive", "Opt_1_def": "known; well-known", "Opt_2_def": "probable", "Opt_3_def": "good; optimistic", "Opt_4_def": "clearly and openly expressed"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Many Western businesses are finding it difficult to ____ with Asian companies which pay their workers far less money.", "Opt_1": "compete", "Opt_2": "organize", "Opt_3": "assure", "Opt_4": "overlap", "Answer": "compete", "Opt_1_def": "to try and win against someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "to put into (its proper) place", "Opt_3_def": "to make sure; to say that something will certainly happen", "Opt_4_def": "to have in common; to cover part of"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The government hopes that its proposals will ____ a reduction in teenage pregnancy.", "Opt_1": "deliver", "Opt_2": "trigger", "Opt_3": "repeat", "Opt_4": "increase", "Answer": "trigger", "Opt_1_def": "to provide (often by bringing to people)", "Opt_2_def": "to (cause to) start", "Opt_3_def": "to do or say again", "Opt_4_def": "to get bigger"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "China did not multiply nuclear weapons. Having produced ____ hundred warheads, China stopped building up its military potential.", "Opt_1": "urgent", "Opt_2": "several", "Opt_3": "confident", "Opt_4": "rapid", "Answer": "several", "Opt_1_def": "very important, must be done immediately", "Opt_2_def": "many (about 6 or seven)", "Opt_3_def": "sure that something will happen", "Opt_4_def": "quick"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Edwards ruled on the evidence presented and said Gary Edwards was not ____ to play.", "Opt_1": "apparent", "Opt_2": "urgent", "Opt_3": "positive", "Opt_4": "eligible", "Answer": "eligible", "Opt_1_def": "clear; obvious", "Opt_2_def": "very important, must be done immediately", "Opt_3_def": "good; optimistic", "Opt_4_def": "being entitled or qualified to do something"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Many people like to change the ____ on their computer desktop.", "Opt_1": "sum", "Opt_2": "display", "Opt_3": "comment", "Opt_4": "substitute", "Answer": "display", "Opt_1_def": "an amount of money, total", "Opt_2_def": "a show, demonstration, illustration", "Opt_3_def": "a short written or spoken statement or opinion", "Opt_4_def": "a thing or person to take the place of another"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "It is not in employers' interest to get rid of cheap illegal immigrants - only to ____ them of any rights.", "Opt_1": "contradict", "Opt_2": "deprive", "Opt_3": "facilitate", "Opt_4": "recur", "Answer": "deprive", "Opt_1_def": "to say or show that what someone has said is wrong", "Opt_2_def": "to take away (the opportunity)", "Opt_3_def": "to make something easier", "Opt_4_def": "to happen again"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The government has passed laws to give equal rights to minority groups, but it can do nothing to ____ the prejudice that exists inside some people's heads.", "Opt_1": "offend", "Opt_2": "remove", "Opt_3": "continue", "Opt_4": "disperse", "Answer": "remove", "Opt_1_def": "to go against; to upset", "Opt_2_def": "to take away", "Opt_3_def": "to carry on, not stop", "Opt_4_def": "to spread out; to move apart"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "In my ____ the government's argument for banning smoking is very weak. Surely they don't expect people to agree!", "Opt_1": "bulk", "Opt_2": "opinion", "Opt_3": "atmosphere", "Opt_4": "committee", "Answer": "opinion", "Opt_1_def": "majority; largest part", "Opt_2_def": "view; what you think about someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "mood among people or groups", "Opt_4_def": "a group of people meeting to discuss an issue"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Access to the data network is both an essential tool for university life and work, and a ____ privilege.", "Opt_1": "intense", "Opt_2": "outstanding", "Opt_3": "abstract", "Opt_4": "valuable", "Answer": "valuable", "Opt_1_def": "strong, extreme", "Opt_2_def": "excellent", "Opt_3_def": "not specific or concrete", "Opt_4_def": "worth a lot of money; important"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "This article will only introduce the issues rather than ____ a detailed analysis with proofs.", "Opt_1": "convert", "Opt_2": "yield", "Opt_3": "present", "Opt_4": "confirm", "Answer": "present", "Opt_1_def": "to change from one thing to another", "Opt_2_def": "to produce", "Opt_3_def": "to give or show; to make a presentation", "Opt_4_def": "to agree that something is correct"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Not all members of the Bush Administration have been telling the entire ____ about their dealing with Iraq.", "Opt_1": "truth", "Opt_2": "deed", "Opt_3": "boundary", "Opt_4": "privilege", "Answer": "truth", "Opt_1_def": "actual reason or fact", "Opt_2_def": "an action", "Opt_3_def": "limit, extent", "Opt_4_def": "a right (to do something)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "As life spans increase, the fraction of life spent in retirement will ____ unless we delay our exit from paid work.", "Opt_1": "substitute", "Opt_2": "fund", "Opt_3": "rise", "Opt_4": "phrase", "Answer": "rise", "Opt_1_def": "a thing or person to take the place of another", "Opt_2_def": "money collected for a particular purpose", "Opt_3_def": "to go up", "Opt_4_def": "one achieves best success through constantly applied pressure."}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Colorado State University scientists have found a way to ____ improve the quality of laser light at extremely short wavelengths.", "Opt_1": "dramatically", "Opt_2": "accordingly", "Opt_3": "rather", "Opt_4": "overly", "Answer": "dramatically", "Opt_1_def": "very strongly, significantly", "Opt_2_def": "appropriate to; in compliance with", "Opt_3_def": "instead", "Opt_4_def": "too"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Due to her student teaching commitments Murray was unable to ____ this year's event.", "Opt_1": "induce", "Opt_2": "conform", "Opt_3": "reserve", "Opt_4": "organize", "Answer": "organize", "Opt_1_def": "to make happen; to force", "Opt_2_def": "to do what is required", "Opt_3_def": "to keep", "Opt_4_def": "to put into (its proper) place"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Stubbornness is a ____ that is sometimes positive and sometimes negative.", "Opt_1": "point", "Opt_2": "period", "Opt_3": "fragment", "Opt_4": "trait", "Answer": "trait", "Opt_1_def": "purpose; reason; value", "Opt_2_def": "a length of time (e.g. a lesson)", "Opt_3_def": "part of something", "Opt_4_def": "characteristic; aspect"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Bradley Hall provides backyard access to the lakeshore path, and tennis courts are ____ to the building for your recreational enjoyment.", "Opt_1": "adjacent", "Opt_2": "discrete", "Opt_3": "aware", "Opt_4": "military", "Answer": "adjacent", "Opt_1_def": "next to", "Opt_2_def": "separate", "Opt_3_def": "knowing", "Opt_4_def": "to do with army"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The objective is to find the right ____ of materials that will result in the creation of clear electrical signals.", "Opt_1": "order", "Opt_2": "mixture", "Opt_3": "assent", "Opt_4": "industry", "Answer": "mixture", "Opt_1_def": "sequence, place", "Opt_2_def": "combination", "Opt_3_def": "agreement", "Opt_4_def": "area of business ( often manufacturing )"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "One factor was political: because we had decided to ____ the project at first to the six northernmost counties in our region.", "Opt_1": "refuse", "Opt_2": "distribute", "Opt_3": "train", "Opt_4": "confine", "Answer": "confine", "Opt_1_def": "to not do something that someone wants you to do", "Opt_2_def": "to give out", "Opt_3_def": "to teach someone how to do a job", "Opt_4_def": "to limit"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The equator is an ____ line that divides the earth into a northern and southern hemisphere.", "Opt_1": "subjective", "Opt_2": "major", "Opt_3": "imaginary", "Opt_4": "appropriate", "Answer": "imaginary", "Opt_1_def": "based on personal opinion or feeling", "Opt_2_def": "important, large", "Opt_3_def": "not real; from the imagination", "Opt_4_def": "right (for the occasion; suitable"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "After an initial ____ of introduction and practice, the German course begins with Chapter 1 in the text Deutsch: Na klar!", "Opt_1": "period", "Opt_2": "procedure", "Opt_3": "precaution", "Opt_4": "symbol", "Answer": "period", "Opt_1_def": "a length of time (e.g. a lesson)", "Opt_2_def": "the way to do something", "Opt_3_def": "something done to avoid danger, harm or problems", "Opt_4_def": "a picture; the representation of an idea"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "I need to speak to John's parents ____ his constant absence.", "Opt_1": "beneath", "Opt_2": "regarding", "Opt_3": "due", "Opt_4": "against", "Answer": "regarding", "Opt_1_def": "below", "Opt_2_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_3_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_4_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Compliment employees in public but always ____ them in private; this shows your respect for them and avoids embarrassment.", "Opt_1": "gather", "Opt_2": "explore", "Opt_3": "criticize", "Opt_4": "dispose", "Answer": "criticize", "Opt_1_def": "to bring or get together", "Opt_2_def": "to look into a place or thing (in order to learn more about it)", "Opt_3_def": "to express disapproval; to say what you don't like or think is good about something or someone", "Opt_4_def": "to get rid of"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Students are responsible for gathering all ____ necessary to support an appeal.", "Opt_1": "prejudice", "Opt_2": "fund", "Opt_3": "profit", "Opt_4": "materials", "Answer": "materials", "Opt_1_def": "bias, discrimination, beliefs or feelings influenced by one's own background", "Opt_2_def": "money collected for a particular purpose", "Opt_3_def": "money gained", "Opt_4_def": "the things you need to do something"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "We have not yet been able to find out the ____ reason why he attacked the teacher.", "Opt_1": "exact", "Opt_2": "valid", "Opt_3": "random", "Opt_4": "explicit", "Answer": "exact", "Opt_1_def": "precise, opposite of approximate", "Opt_2_def": "correct", "Opt_3_def": "by chance; without any sequence", "Opt_4_def": "clearly and openly expressed"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "If the funding is from personal or family funds, you will need to obtain a ____ bank statement showing that you have enough funds to cover expenses.", "Opt_1": "accurate", "Opt_2": "perpetual", "Opt_3": "available", "Opt_4": "current", "Answer": "current", "Opt_1_def": "exact, containing no mistakes", "Opt_2_def": "continuing for ever; never disappearing", "Opt_3_def": "can be had (bought or obtained)", "Opt_4_def": "happening now"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Students post messages and ____ ideas through the bulletin board.", "Opt_1": "remove", "Opt_2": "review", "Opt_3": "exchange", "Opt_4": "exhaust", "Answer": "exchange", "Opt_1_def": "to take away", "Opt_2_def": "to check over (and make changes)", "Opt_3_def": "to give or change one thing and get a different thing", "Opt_4_def": "to use up"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The company does a minor amount of business in the USA; the majority of its ____ is in Europe.", "Opt_1": "attend", "Opt_2": "extend", "Opt_3": "trade", "Opt_4": "refute", "Answer": "trade", "Opt_1_def": "to go to, to be present at", "Opt_2_def": "to make longer in time or space", "Opt_3_def": "to exchange products or services", "Opt_4_def": "to prove to be untrue; to deny"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The school is located in the wooded ____ to the north west of Frankfurt.", "Opt_1": "fund", "Opt_2": "region", "Opt_3": "experience", "Opt_4": "agent", "Answer": "region", "Opt_1_def": "money collected for a particular purpose", "Opt_2_def": "part of a place", "Opt_3_def": "knowledge and skills gained over a long period of time", "Opt_4_def": "a person who is paid to do a job for someone"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The essential ____ for successful teaching is the ability to interest the students.", "Opt_1": "criterion", "Opt_2": "manner", "Opt_3": "legislation", "Opt_4": "scheme", "Answer": "criterion", "Opt_1_def": "a way to judge the value or importance of something", "Opt_2_def": "way of doing something", "Opt_3_def": "governmental rule; law", "Opt_4_def": "plan. idea, project"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Trying to water-ski for the first time is difficult but if you keep practising, you will ____ learn how to do it.", "Opt_1": "predominantly", "Opt_2": "rather", "Opt_3": "eventually", "Opt_4": "fairly", "Answer": "eventually", "Opt_1_def": "mostly", "Opt_2_def": "instead", "Opt_3_def": "in the end", "Opt_4_def": "quite, somewhat"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The findings directly ____ the assertion that some verbal areas of the brain are larger in women than in men.", "Opt_1": "predict", "Opt_2": "fulfill", "Opt_3": "contradict", "Opt_4": "replace", "Answer": "contradict", "Opt_1_def": "to say what will happen in the future", "Opt_2_def": "to do; to carry out (completely)", "Opt_3_def": "to say or show that what someone has said is wrong", "Opt_4_def": "to put in or take the place of .."}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The school found it impossible to ____ its promise to reduce tuition fees.", "Opt_1": "undertake", "Opt_2": "exert", "Opt_3": "fulfill", "Opt_4": "share", "Answer": "fulfill", "Opt_1_def": "to (plan to) do", "Opt_2_def": "to use", "Opt_3_def": "to do; to carry out (completely)", "Opt_4_def": "to exchange; to give"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "You have one last opportunity to show that you can work hard and ____ properly. If you don't take it, you will be asked to leave the school.", "Opt_1": "predict", "Opt_2": "develop", "Opt_3": "attach", "Opt_4": "behave", "Answer": "behave", "Opt_1_def": "to say what will happen in the future", "Opt_2_def": "to grow or improve", "Opt_3_def": "to put together with", "Opt_4_def": "to act or do things in a certain way"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "People with another genetic variant, glycine (Gly-389), had no ____ to the drug compared to the placebo.", "Opt_1": "purpose", "Opt_2": "response", "Opt_3": "hierarchy", "Opt_4": "counsel", "Answer": "response", "Opt_1_def": "reason, goal", "Opt_2_def": "answer or reply; reaction", "Opt_3_def": "organizational structure (e.g. showing who works for whom)", "Opt_4_def": "advice; advisor"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The journey to peace and prosperity in the ____ can only commence when the civic authority is brought back in.", "Opt_1": "fee", "Opt_2": "guide", "Opt_3": "region", "Opt_4": "revenue", "Answer": "region", "Opt_1_def": "money for a service (e.g. a baking service)", "Opt_2_def": "someone or something that helps people (to understand or find their way)", "Opt_3_def": "part of a place", "Opt_4_def": "money, income"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Unlike normal children she cannot ____ its ordinary meaning to the word \"blue\", so she cannot fully understand basic sentences.", "Opt_1": "risk", "Opt_2": "attach", "Opt_3": "connect", "Opt_4": "encounter", "Answer": "attach", "Opt_1_def": "to act in a way that might lead to danger or failure", "Opt_2_def": "to put together with", "Opt_3_def": "to bring or put together", "Opt_4_def": "to meet or experience"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "In my opinion the government should ____ more to prevent young people drinking and driving.", "Opt_1": "manipulate", "Opt_2": "earn", "Opt_3": "protest", "Opt_4": "undertake", "Answer": "undertake", "Opt_1_def": "to (use and) change", "Opt_2_def": "to get money or another reward (usually by working for it)", "Opt_3_def": "to express anger or unhappiness about something", "Opt_4_def": "to (plan to) do"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Discussion and analysis in this area has covered a number of ____ issues, including the effect of shifting trade patterns on employment levels.", "Opt_1": "ultimate", "Opt_2": "discrete", "Opt_3": "brief", "Opt_4": "uniform", "Answer": "discrete", "Opt_1_def": "final or most important", "Opt_2_def": "separate", "Opt_3_def": "short", "Opt_4_def": "having the same qualities"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "An employee is entitled to no ____ for the first seven calendar days of disability unless the disability continues for more than 21 days.", "Opt_1": "ability", "Opt_2": "aid", "Opt_3": "compensation", "Opt_4": "extract", "Answer": "compensation", "Opt_1_def": "ableness to do something; a skill for doing something well", "Opt_2_def": "help (often financial help)", "Opt_3_def": "money (or some other reward) given to someone who has suffered a loss or injustice", "Opt_4_def": "to remove; to take out and use"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Click here to review the rules of comma usage when you ____ two independent clauses.", "Opt_1": "prefer", "Opt_2": "allocate", "Opt_3": "combine", "Opt_4": "contact", "Answer": "combine", "Opt_1_def": "to like better", "Opt_2_def": "to give to (to promise to give)", "Opt_3_def": "to put or go together", "Opt_4_def": "to get in touch (e.g. by phone or email)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "This has been the province of scientists and engineers for many years and has only recently been considered a hot research ____ with real business potential.", "Opt_1": "operation", "Opt_2": "field", "Opt_3": "technique", "Opt_4": "topic", "Answer": "topic", "Opt_1_def": "procedure; happening; process", "Opt_2_def": "area of interest or study", "Opt_3_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_4_def": "area of interest or discussion"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Burning of coal is a ____ way to obtain energy, but it creates a serious amount of pollution.", "Opt_1": "efficient", "Opt_2": "urban", "Opt_3": "essential", "Opt_4": "convenient", "Answer": "convenient", "Opt_1_def": "working quickly and easily", "Opt_2_def": "of the town or city", "Opt_3_def": "very important", "Opt_4_def": "easy, not causing problems"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Antigone makes it clear that she is willing to meet her untimely death to ____ justice.", "Opt_1": "relationship", "Opt_2": "behalf", "Opt_3": "perspective", "Opt_4": "gain", "Answer": "gain", "Opt_1_def": "the way to things are connected", "Opt_2_def": "as a representative of; for the benefit of", "Opt_3_def": "view; opinion; way of thinking", "Opt_4_def": "to get; to increase in .."}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "For republicans since Cicero there can be no liberty without law, and no valid law or ____ system when liberty is disregarded.", "Opt_1": "utter", "Opt_2": "moderate", "Opt_3": "legal", "Opt_4": "reasonable", "Answer": "legal", "Opt_1_def": "complete, total", "Opt_2_def": "not very much; not very strong; not extreme", "Opt_3_def": "acceptable in law (to do with the law)", "Opt_4_def": "acceptable, quite good"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "She accepted the arduous task of vice president, according to the papers, saying that she could not ____ the will of the people.", "Opt_1": "postpone", "Opt_2": "indicate", "Opt_3": "frustrate", "Opt_4": "constitute", "Answer": "frustrate", "Opt_1_def": "to put back in time", "Opt_2_def": "to show or convey", "Opt_3_def": "to stop or prevent", "Opt_4_def": "to be; to make up"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The government has decided to block financial ____ to the African country until the civil war is over.", "Opt_1": "comment", "Opt_2": "task", "Opt_3": "truth", "Opt_4": "aid", "Answer": "aid", "Opt_1_def": "a short written or spoken statement or opinion", "Opt_2_def": "job", "Opt_3_def": "actual reason or fact", "Opt_4_def": "help (often financial help)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "I didn't have my identity card with me so I was not allowed ____ to the building.", "Opt_1": "property", "Opt_2": "access", "Opt_3": "support", "Opt_4": "doubt", "Answer": "access", "Opt_1_def": "the things that belong to someone, especially their home", "Opt_2_def": "the right to enter or use", "Opt_3_def": "help", "Opt_4_def": "a feeling of uncertainty (whether something is true)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "If you are eligible for Financial Aid in excess of your tuition and fees then you do not ____ Ivy Tech Community College money.", "Opt_1": "recur", "Opt_2": "entitle", "Opt_3": "force", "Opt_4": "owe", "Answer": "owe", "Opt_1_def": "to happen again", "Opt_2_def": "to give the right to do something", "Opt_3_def": "to make happen or to make someone do something", "Opt_4_def": "to be in someone's debt (especially money)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Telephone and telegraph ____ from the Greek words meaning far speak and far write.", "Opt_1": "derive", "Opt_2": "found", "Opt_3": "imply", "Opt_4": "accept", "Answer": "derive", "Opt_1_def": "to come from or get from", "Opt_2_def": "to begin (often an organization)", "Opt_3_def": "to mean; to give to understand", "Opt_4_def": "to agree (to have)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Metals ____ when heated.", "Opt_1": "expand", "Opt_2": "mention", "Opt_3": "afford", "Opt_4": "consult", "Answer": "expand", "Opt_1_def": "to get bigger; to move into new areas", "Opt_2_def": "to say; state", "Opt_3_def": "to be able to pay for something", "Opt_4_def": "to get the advice of someone ( often an expert)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The school can recommend that parents communicate by email, but they cannot ____ on it.", "Opt_1": "obey", "Opt_2": "insist", "Opt_3": "exaggerate", "Opt_4": "produce", "Answer": "insist", "Opt_1_def": "to do as commanded or expected", "Opt_2_def": "to demand; to make a strong claim", "Opt_3_def": "to \"overstate\" the truth; to say something is bigger or better than it really is", "Opt_4_def": "to make or create"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Mobile phones have made it ____ to contact someone anytime and anywhere.", "Opt_1": "feasible", "Opt_2": "concise", "Opt_3": "genuine", "Opt_4": "arbitrary", "Answer": "feasible", "Opt_1_def": "possible", "Opt_2_def": "short, not detailed", "Opt_3_def": "real and authentic", "Opt_4_def": "not planned or thought-out; not considering the wishes of others"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The school have employed some guards to make the campus more ____ against unannounced visitors.", "Opt_1": "broad", "Opt_2": "secure", "Opt_3": "perpetual", "Opt_4": "compulsory", "Answer": "secure", "Opt_1_def": "wide, extensive", "Opt_2_def": "safe", "Opt_3_def": "continuing for ever; never disappearing", "Opt_4_def": "required, must be done"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The explanation for this ____ decision lies in the immediate circumstances surrounding the creation of the United Nations.", "Opt_1": "political", "Opt_2": "elementary", "Opt_3": "stable", "Opt_4": "extraordinary", "Answer": "extraordinary", "Opt_1_def": "to do government and politics", "Opt_2_def": "easy", "Opt_3_def": "not changing; not easy to change", "Opt_4_def": "very unusual"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Your good grades in the report ____ my expectations. Well done!", "Opt_1": "exceed", "Opt_2": "broadcast", "Opt_3": "solve", "Opt_4": "share", "Answer": "exceed", "Opt_1_def": "to be more than or better than", "Opt_2_def": "to tell or transmit (often by means of a television programme)", "Opt_3_def": "to find an answer", "Opt_4_def": "to exchange; to give"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "It is unclear whether this facility will be able to ____ complete missiles or only some major component.", "Opt_1": "receive", "Opt_2": "manufacture", "Opt_3": "suppress", "Opt_4": "expose", "Answer": "manufacture", "Opt_1_def": "to get", "Opt_2_def": "to produce (with machines)", "Opt_3_def": "to hold back; to not allow to happen", "Opt_4_def": "to uncover, reveal"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "So, what's the point of all this hindsight and what do we stand to ____ from it?", "Opt_1": "layer", "Opt_2": "gain", "Opt_3": "doubt", "Opt_4": "pressure", "Answer": "gain", "Opt_1_def": "level", "Opt_2_def": "to get; to increase in ..", "Opt_3_def": "a feeling of uncertainty (whether something is true)", "Opt_4_def": "force; influence; stress"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Describe the study in detail sufficient to convince the reviewer that the problem is ____ investigation.", "Opt_1": "instead", "Opt_2": "beyond", "Opt_3": "among", "Opt_4": "worth", "Answer": "worth", "Opt_1_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_2_def": "further than: past", "Opt_3_def": "in, between", "Opt_4_def": "useful; having a point or purpose"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The revolutionary ____ must come from those basic human needs that are failed by capitalism.", "Opt_1": "society", "Opt_2": "distance", "Opt_3": "plenty", "Opt_4": "impulse", "Answer": "impulse", "Opt_1_def": "a group of people; the entire group of people living in a country", "Opt_2_def": "how far it is from one place to another", "Opt_3_def": "many, lots of", "Opt_4_def": "reason or motivation to do something"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "It is a fact that ____ drivers have fewer accidents than reckless ones.", "Opt_1": "harsh", "Opt_2": "deficient", "Opt_3": "constant", "Opt_4": "cautious", "Answer": "cautious", "Opt_1_def": "hard, unfair", "Opt_2_def": "poor, lacking in quantity or quality", "Opt_3_def": "not changing; long-lasting", "Opt_4_def": "careful"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "I don't really like science but my parents decided to ____ me to take biology and chemistry in grade 10.", "Opt_1": "adapt", "Opt_2": "compel", "Opt_3": "dismiss", "Opt_4": "verify", "Answer": "compel", "Opt_1_def": "to change (often in response to a changed situation)", "Opt_2_def": "to force or make happen", "Opt_3_def": "to reject, to treat as unimportant", "Opt_4_def": "to prove or claim the truth"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The UK Highway ____ is the book of road rules that must be learned by new drivers.", "Opt_1": "code", "Opt_2": "item", "Opt_3": "majority", "Opt_4": "research", "Answer": "code", "Opt_1_def": "a set of rules", "Opt_2_def": "thing, element", "Opt_3_def": "more than 50%", "Opt_4_def": "study; the finding of information"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The failures of the national soccer and tennis teams ____ all that is wrong with British sport.", "Opt_1": "correlate", "Opt_2": "multiply", "Opt_3": "recognize", "Opt_4": "embody", "Answer": "embody", "Opt_1_def": "to have a close connection", "Opt_2_def": "to increase greatly", "Opt_3_def": "to know or understand (who someone is or what something is)", "Opt_4_def": "to be a good example of .."}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The government hopes that its new tax law will result ____ in a reduction in teenage pregnancy.", "Opt_1": "indirectly", "Opt_2": "indeed", "Opt_3": "occasionally", "Opt_4": "roughly", "Answer": "indirectly", "Opt_1_def": "in a indirect way; not straight or immediate", "Opt_2_def": "used in confirmation or emphasis; really", "Opt_3_def": "sometimes", "Opt_4_def": "about, approximately"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "This is yet another ____ example of the positive partnership between TMH and the FSU College of Medicine.", "Opt_1": "outstanding", "Opt_2": "liable", "Opt_3": "former", "Opt_4": "trivial", "Answer": "outstanding", "Opt_1_def": "excellent", "Opt_2_def": "likely to happen; at risk of happening", "Opt_3_def": "previous, the one before, the first of two", "Opt_4_def": "not important"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Plants that possess ____ traits or characteristics not common to the entire species are referred to as biotypes.", "Opt_1": "certain", "Opt_2": "actual", "Opt_3": "smooth", "Opt_4": "reliable", "Answer": "certain", "Opt_1_def": "sure", "Opt_2_def": "real", "Opt_3_def": "easy, unproblematic", "Opt_4_def": "can be trusted, does not let you down \r\n"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "You will not have to seek permission to ____ if the purpose of your work falls under one of the following criteria.", "Opt_1": "conduct", "Opt_2": "publish", "Opt_3": "comprise", "Opt_4": "collapse", "Answer": "publish", "Opt_1_def": "to do or perform; to behave", "Opt_2_def": "to make available in paper or online form", "Opt_3_def": "to be made up of; to include", "Opt_4_def": "to fall down completely and heavily; to fail"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Do we have an ____ to help the poor?", "Opt_1": "treatment", "Opt_2": "reluctance", "Opt_3": "obligation", "Opt_4": "deal", "Answer": "obligation", "Opt_1_def": "way of handing a person, situation or problem (often of illness)", "Opt_2_def": "unwillingness; hesitation", "Opt_3_def": "a requirement to do something", "Opt_4_def": "agreement"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The new teacher has been away quite often this year. I ____ that she will not be given a permanent job at the school.", "Opt_1": "transmit", "Opt_2": "diminish", "Opt_3": "speculate", "Opt_4": "subsidize", "Answer": "speculate", "Opt_1_def": "to send or convey", "Opt_2_def": "to get smaller or less important", "Opt_3_def": "to think and talk about (often future events)", "Opt_4_def": "to support financially"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The ____ goal of teaching is to teach students how to teach themselves.", "Opt_1": "homogeneous", "Opt_2": "visual", "Opt_3": "aware", "Opt_4": "ultimate", "Answer": "ultimate", "Opt_1_def": "having the same qualities or characteristics", "Opt_2_def": "to do with sight and seeing", "Opt_3_def": "knowing", "Opt_4_def": "final or most important"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "These two-word verbs ____ one other problem, besides not appearing as separate entries in the dictionary.", "Opt_1": "complicate", "Opt_2": "present", "Opt_3": "disrupt", "Opt_4": "interact", "Answer": "present", "Opt_1_def": "to make things more complex or difficult", "Opt_2_def": "to give or show; to make a presentation", "Opt_3_def": "to interrupt an event; to damage", "Opt_4_def": "to react, to affect and be affected"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Even more extraordinary, every child ____ one was more than willing to state his or her name to the stranger.", "Opt_1": "among", "Opt_2": "prior", "Opt_3": "besides", "Opt_4": "except", "Answer": "except", "Opt_1_def": "in, between", "Opt_2_def": "before", "Opt_3_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_4_def": "but (not)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The company directors made a ____ attempt to save the business by dismissing half the workforce.", "Opt_1": "drastic", "Opt_2": "supplementary", "Opt_3": "abundant", "Opt_4": "scarce", "Answer": "drastic", "Opt_1_def": "severe; great", "Opt_2_def": "extra; additional", "Opt_3_def": "existing in large quantities", "Opt_4_def": "rare, not abundant"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "What do western Louisville and the Appalachian region have in common ____ being two of the poorest areas in Kentucky?", "Opt_1": "prior", "Opt_2": "despite", "Opt_3": "worth", "Opt_4": "besides", "Answer": "besides", "Opt_1_def": "before", "Opt_2_def": "although", "Opt_3_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_4_def": "in addition to; as well as"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "This unnecessary legislation would adversely impact the existing review system that ensures the high ____ of scientific research in the United States.", "Opt_1": "volume", "Opt_2": "belief", "Opt_3": "expert", "Opt_4": "quality", "Answer": "quality", "Opt_1_def": "amount", "Opt_2_def": "what you think; what you believe in", "Opt_3_def": "someone with great knowledge in a particular field", "Opt_4_def": "worth or value"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "We got some very ____ results in our science experiment. I think the thermometer was not working correctly.", "Opt_1": "former", "Opt_2": "abnormal", "Opt_3": "overall", "Opt_4": "deficient", "Answer": "abnormal", "Opt_1_def": "previous, the one before, the first of two", "Opt_2_def": "not normal, unusual", "Opt_3_def": "general", "Opt_4_def": "poor, lacking in quantity or quality"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "This is a very trivial example for demonstration purposes. However, the effect is ____ for more complex cases.", "Opt_1": "probable", "Opt_2": "subsequent", "Opt_3": "similar", "Opt_4": "ultimate", "Answer": "similar", "Opt_1_def": "it is not probable that any thing better will be discovered than what was known to our fathers.", "Opt_2_def": "next, following", "Opt_3_def": "like, almost the same as", "Opt_4_def": "final or most important"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The school's decision to raise the tuition fees will have a serious ____ on the number of students who plan to attend.", "Opt_1": "innovation", "Opt_2": "revenue", "Opt_3": "theory", "Opt_4": "implication", "Answer": "implication", "Opt_1_def": "new object or idea", "Opt_2_def": "money, income", "Opt_3_def": "idea or hypothesis", "Opt_4_def": "result or consequence"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It is interesting to think about how teaching will ____ under the influence of digital technologies.", "Opt_1": "contradict", "Opt_2": "evolve", "Opt_3": "entitle", "Opt_4": "convert", "Answer": "evolve", "Opt_1_def": "to say or show that what someone has said is wrong", "Opt_2_def": "to develop (into something better)", "Opt_3_def": "to give the right to do something", "Opt_4_def": "to change from one thing to another"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "She would have a better chance of academic success if she didn't ____ in so many activities outside of school.", "Opt_1": "exist", "Opt_2": "overlap", "Opt_3": "engage", "Opt_4": "disturb", "Answer": "engage", "Opt_1_def": "to be alive, to be in the world", "Opt_2_def": "to have in common; to cover part of", "Opt_3_def": "to participate in; to focus attention on", "Opt_4_def": "to interrupt, stop from working"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Insurance salesmen often ____ profits that they know are very unlikely.", "Opt_1": "notice", "Opt_2": "obey", "Opt_3": "prosper", "Opt_4": "assert", "Answer": "assert", "Opt_1_def": "to see or realize", "Opt_2_def": "to do as commanded or expected", "Opt_3_def": "to do well; to become rich", "Opt_4_def": "to claim, to say strongly"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Students are strongly recommended to seek assistance from the Student Rights Officer at their campus should they decide to appeal ____ exclusion.", "Opt_1": "except", "Opt_2": "prior", "Opt_3": "regarding", "Opt_4": "against", "Answer": "against", "Opt_1_def": "but (not)", "Opt_2_def": "before", "Opt_3_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_4_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The most powerful typhoon in over a ____ should break south of Shanghai early on Wednesday.", "Opt_1": "decade", "Opt_2": "hypothesis", "Opt_3": "counsel", "Opt_4": "topic", "Answer": "decade", "Opt_1_def": "a period of ten years", "Opt_2_def": "idea or prediction", "Opt_3_def": "advice; advisor", "Opt_4_def": "area of interest or discussion"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The main ____ of teaching should be to teach the students how to teach themselves.", "Opt_1": "precaution", "Opt_2": "aim", "Opt_3": "fragment", "Opt_4": "region", "Answer": "aim", "Opt_1_def": "something done to avoid danger, harm or problems", "Opt_2_def": "goal or intention", "Opt_3_def": "part of something", "Opt_4_def": "part of a place"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The test will ____ all of the topics that we have covered this trimester.", "Opt_1": "permit", "Opt_2": "unite", "Opt_3": "contain", "Opt_4": "overcome", "Answer": "contain", "Opt_1_def": "to allow", "Opt_2_def": "to bring or get together", "Opt_3_def": "to have in it; to hold inside", "Opt_4_def": "to conquer, defeat"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "There is a ____ belief among the public that the government lied about the reason for going to war.", "Opt_1": "complete", "Opt_2": "concise", "Opt_3": "major", "Opt_4": "widespread", "Answer": "widespread", "Opt_1_def": "full or finished", "Opt_2_def": "short, not detailed", "Opt_3_def": "important, large", "Opt_4_def": "common"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The need for regulation is quite ____ today but was not apparent before the early years of the 20th century.", "Opt_1": "massive", "Opt_2": "practical", "Opt_3": "evident", "Opt_4": "regular", "Answer": "evident", "Opt_1_def": "very large", "Opt_2_def": "useful; possible", "Opt_3_def": "clear", "Opt_4_def": "predictable, following a pattern; normal"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "It is not pleasant to contemplate the results of a German ____ in World War II.", "Opt_1": "distance", "Opt_2": "career", "Opt_3": "experience", "Opt_4": "victory", "Answer": "victory", "Opt_1_def": "how far it is from one place to another", "Opt_2_def": "a long-term job", "Opt_3_def": "knowledge and skills gained over a long period of time", "Opt_4_def": "win"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "If we ____ just a little more, we will see that random is hardly the right adjective.", "Opt_1": "reflect", "Opt_2": "forego", "Opt_3": "investigate", "Opt_4": "separate", "Answer": "reflect", "Opt_1_def": "to think or consider", "Opt_2_def": "to do without; to give up", "Opt_3_def": "to find out what has happened or why something has happened", "Opt_4_def": "to pull or put apart"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "If we are to contemplate actions designed to ____ the pattern of current difficulties in Viet Nam we ought to lay the groundwork.", "Opt_1": "migrate", "Opt_2": "reverse", "Opt_3": "eliminate", "Opt_4": "master", "Answer": "reverse", "Opt_1_def": "to go to another place", "Opt_2_def": "to turn back or go back", "Opt_3_def": "to dispose of", "Opt_4_def": "to (gain) control"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The system uses a ____ inference engine that does not require users to explicitly provide information about the start or ending points of their journeys.", "Opt_1": "novel", "Opt_2": "actual", "Opt_3": "global", "Opt_4": "slight", "Answer": "novel", "Opt_1_def": "new", "Opt_2_def": "real", "Opt_3_def": "world", "Opt_4_def": "small"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Hacking's book suffers from a serious defect, ____ he does not understand the nature of hypnosis.", "Opt_1": "recently", "Opt_2": "indirectly", "Opt_3": "simply", "Opt_4": "namely", "Answer": "namely", "Opt_1_def": "in the near past", "Opt_2_def": "in a indirect way; not straight or immediate", "Opt_3_def": "completely; just; only", "Opt_4_def": "specifically, that is to say ( .. used to list or explain)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "If you ____ a book from Amazon, you usually receive it within a few days.", "Opt_1": "order", "Opt_2": "forecast", "Opt_3": "conflict", "Opt_4": "field", "Answer": "order", "Opt_1_def": "sequence, place", "Opt_2_def": "prediction", "Opt_3_def": "problem, struggle or battle", "Opt_4_def": "area of interest or study"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Most western countries want to ____ with China. It's the largest market in the world and its developing fast.", "Opt_1": "transfer", "Opt_2": "master", "Opt_3": "adjust", "Opt_4": "trade", "Answer": "trade", "Opt_1_def": "to move to a different place or job", "Opt_2_def": "to (gain) control", "Opt_3_def": "to change (often in order to make something work properly)", "Opt_4_def": "to exchange products or services"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Frankfurt International School has attracted many more German students recently. My ____ is that parents are not happy with the education their children are getting in German public schools.", "Opt_1": "hypothesis", "Opt_2": "hierarchy", "Opt_3": "privilege", "Opt_4": "background", "Answer": "hypothesis", "Opt_1_def": "idea or prediction", "Opt_2_def": "organizational structure (e.g. showing who works for whom)", "Opt_3_def": "a right (to do something)", "Opt_4_def": "family experiences; circumstances"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Many new astronomy learners, students and adults alike, are unfamiliar with the universe ____ the solar system.", "Opt_1": "worth", "Opt_2": "besides", "Opt_3": "prior", "Opt_4": "beyond", "Answer": "beyond", "Opt_1_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_3_def": "before", "Opt_4_def": "further than: past"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The need for regulation is quite evident today but was not ____ before the early years of the 20th century.", "Opt_1": "apparent", "Opt_2": "major", "Opt_3": "principal", "Opt_4": "fortunate", "Answer": "apparent", "Opt_1_def": "clear; obvious", "Opt_2_def": "important, large", "Opt_3_def": "most important", "Opt_4_def": "lucky"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Although Katrina affected the material environment of Louisiana, it did not ____ the great spirit of the people here.", "Opt_1": "train", "Opt_2": "retreat", "Opt_3": "diminish", "Opt_4": "confine", "Answer": "diminish", "Opt_1_def": "to teach someone how to do a job", "Opt_2_def": "to go back", "Opt_3_def": "to get smaller or less important", "Opt_4_def": "to limit"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "This finding may explain why increasing numbers of people in the United States ____ the natural ability to regulate food intake and body weight.", "Opt_1": "pressure", "Opt_2": "aspect", "Opt_3": "priority", "Opt_4": "lack", "Answer": "lack", "Opt_1_def": "force; influence; stress", "Opt_2_def": "environment that lifts people up,\" says Jain.", "Opt_3_def": "first and most important task", "Opt_4_def": "absence of a thing"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Aschoff's trip failed because he was unable to ____ his concept against the competitive approach favored by German and Russian scientists.", "Opt_1": "trigger", "Opt_2": "trust", "Opt_3": "diverge", "Opt_4": "defend", "Answer": "defend", "Opt_1_def": "to (cause to) start", "Opt_2_def": "to believe that someone or something will be or work as promised", "Opt_3_def": "to move apart; to be different from", "Opt_4_def": "to give reasons for"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Before having a major surgical ____ patients must always consent.", "Opt_1": "procedure", "Opt_2": "source", "Opt_3": "factor", "Opt_4": "advantage", "Answer": "procedure", "Opt_1_def": "the way to do something", "Opt_2_def": "where something begins, where you can find something", "Opt_3_def": "an aspect to be considered", "Opt_4_def": "benefit"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "There is no trace of sentimentality in Weil's ____ of the beauty and order of the world.", "Opt_1": "speed", "Opt_2": "remedy", "Opt_3": "notion", "Opt_4": "comment", "Answer": "notion", "Opt_1_def": "how quickly something moves or changes", "Opt_2_def": "cure (often for an illness)", "Opt_3_def": "idea; concept", "Opt_4_def": "a short written or spoken statement or opinion"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Many people used to believe that if cancer did not ____ within five years, a person was safe.", "Opt_1": "apply", "Opt_2": "require", "Opt_3": "recur", "Opt_4": "measure", "Answer": "recur", "Opt_1_def": "to be relevant (to)", "Opt_2_def": "to need", "Opt_3_def": "to happen again", "Opt_4_def": "to find out how much there is of something"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "It is still ____ of a risk to purchase things on the internet.", "Opt_1": "greatly", "Opt_2": "hardly", "Opt_3": "somewhat", "Opt_4": "gradually", "Answer": "somewhat", "Opt_1_def": "very much", "Opt_2_def": "not very much", "Opt_3_def": "quite, rather", "Opt_4_def": "slowly; steadily"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Asia is our closest region and essentially I feel that we need more understanding and ____ culturally to make sense of where we all are'.", "Opt_1": "exchange", "Opt_2": "generate", "Opt_3": "measure", "Opt_4": "attach", "Answer": "exchange", "Opt_1_def": "to give or change one thing and get a different thing", "Opt_2_def": "to make or produce", "Opt_3_def": "to find out how much there is of something", "Opt_4_def": "to put together with"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Due to the recent increase in student numbers, the school can now ____ to build a new science laboratory.", "Opt_1": "afford", "Opt_2": "engage", "Opt_3": "connect", "Opt_4": "reward", "Answer": "afford", "Opt_1_def": "to be able to pay for something", "Opt_2_def": "to participate in; to focus attention on", "Opt_3_def": "to bring or put together", "Opt_4_def": "to give something (e.g. a prize) for good work or behaviour"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The company has the ____ to dismiss employees without giving a reason during the first 6 months of their employment.", "Opt_1": "administration", "Opt_2": "liberty", "Opt_3": "credit", "Opt_4": "career", "Answer": "liberty", "Opt_1_def": "the people responsible for running an organization such as the government or a school", "Opt_2_def": "freedom", "Opt_3_def": "gained on completing a course of study; praise", "Opt_4_def": "a long-term job"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "They are never forgotten, those brief moments of splendid ____ sandwiched between so many slices of rancid defeat.", "Opt_1": "victory", "Opt_2": "expert", "Opt_3": "crisis", "Opt_4": "penalty", "Answer": "victory", "Opt_1_def": "win", "Opt_2_def": "someone with great knowledge in a particular field", "Opt_3_def": "very dangerous situation, catastrophe", "Opt_4_def": "negative consequence; punishment"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "We must hope that her heavy involvement in the school's sporting programme will not be to the ____ of her studies.", "Opt_1": "detriment", "Opt_2": "battle", "Opt_3": "forecast", "Opt_4": "society", "Answer": "detriment", "Opt_1_def": "disadvantage", "Opt_2_def": "fight, part of a war", "Opt_3_def": "prediction", "Opt_4_def": "a group of people; the entire group of people living in a country"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Before this century there was little ____ between them; indeed, they did not think of themselves as two distinct kinds of people.", "Opt_1": "response", "Opt_2": "conflict", "Opt_3": "institution", "Opt_4": "outline", "Answer": "conflict", "Opt_1_def": "answer or reply; reaction", "Opt_2_def": "problem, struggle or battle", "Opt_3_def": "a large organization; an important system or custom", "Opt_4_def": "plan or summary"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Oil is becoming more and more scarce. It is ____ that we find new ways of powering cars and industry.", "Opt_1": "vital", "Opt_2": "local", "Opt_3": "formal", "Opt_4": "abnormal", "Answer": "vital", "Opt_1_def": "very important", "Opt_2_def": "in the area where you live or work", "Opt_3_def": "serious, not relaxed or everyday", "Opt_4_def": "not normal, unusual"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "You will ____ recurrent patterns of international political conflict, identify underlying issues, and suggest alternative resolutions.", "Opt_1": "react", "Opt_2": "prepare", "Opt_3": "analyze", "Opt_4": "enable", "Answer": "analyze", "Opt_1_def": "to respond", "Opt_2_def": "to get something ready (or to get ready for something)", "Opt_3_def": "to look at something in detail in order to understand it", "Opt_4_def": "to make something or someone able to do something"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Traditional social skills strategies (such as board games about friendships and appropriate classroom behavior) tend to be too ____ for many children.", "Opt_1": "ordinary", "Opt_2": "identical", "Opt_3": "principal", "Opt_4": "subtle", "Answer": "subtle", "Opt_1_def": "usual, typical, every day", "Opt_2_def": "exactly the same", "Opt_3_def": "most important", "Opt_4_def": "not clear or strong"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "This interesting ____ offers the student of neuroscience access to an immense amount of information on the discipline.", "Opt_1": "site", "Opt_2": "responsibility", "Opt_3": "attribute", "Opt_4": "source", "Answer": "site", "Opt_1_def": "place", "Opt_2_def": "job, duty to do something", "Opt_3_def": "characteristic; property", "Opt_4_def": "where something begins, where you can find something"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "For the purposes of this study, then, increasing the testing strength did not ____ more accurate results.", "Opt_1": "yield", "Opt_2": "dedicate", "Opt_3": "construct", "Opt_4": "infer", "Answer": "yield", "Opt_1_def": "to produce", "Opt_2_def": "to devote (time and attention)", "Opt_3_def": "to make", "Opt_4_def": "to come to a conclusion about something"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Of the questions asked in this ____ of the survey, having an explicit privacy policy is one of the highest percentage of responses.", "Opt_1": "supply", "Opt_2": "section", "Opt_3": "feature", "Opt_4": "diagram", "Answer": "section", "Opt_1_def": "provision, store", "Opt_2_def": "part", "Opt_3_def": "part, aspect", "Opt_4_def": "a type of picture or chart"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The supply of blue agave (agave azul) cactus in Mexico has gone from one extreme to another during the past ____ years.", "Opt_1": "several", "Opt_2": "typical", "Opt_3": "constant", "Opt_4": "inevitable", "Answer": "several", "Opt_1_def": "many (about 6 or seven)", "Opt_2_def": "usual", "Opt_3_def": "not changing; long-lasting", "Opt_4_def": "cannot be changed or avoided; obvious"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "It is a ____ at the school for teachers to share a cake or cookies with their colleagues when it is their birthday.", "Opt_1": "quantity", "Opt_2": "tradition", "Opt_3": "debt", "Opt_4": "bias", "Answer": "tradition", "Opt_1_def": "amount", "Opt_2_def": "a usual, old-time way of doing things", "Opt_3_def": "something owed to another person (often money)", "Opt_4_def": "favouring one more than another, prejudice"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "This is NOT a reliable ____ and you should simply ignore it.", "Opt_1": "substitute", "Opt_2": "attack", "Opt_3": "statistic", "Opt_4": "result", "Answer": "statistic", "Opt_1_def": "a thing or person to take the place of another", "Opt_2_def": "to criticize; to attempt to harm or damage", "Opt_3_def": "mathematical number", "Opt_4_def": "outcome, effect"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "A snowstorm failed to ____ soccer practice on the Inlet early last week.", "Opt_1": "interrupt", "Opt_2": "block", "Opt_3": "embody", "Opt_4": "afford", "Answer": "interrupt", "Opt_1_def": "to stop something from happening", "Opt_2_def": "to not allow; to stop or prevent", "Opt_3_def": "to be a good example of ..", "Opt_4_def": "to be able to pay for something"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The school needs to ____ new students otherwise one or two teachers will have to lose their jobs.", "Opt_1": "enumerate", "Opt_2": "procure", "Opt_3": "train", "Opt_4": "attract", "Answer": "attract", "Opt_1_def": "to list", "Opt_2_def": "to get or obtain", "Opt_3_def": "to teach someone how to do a job", "Opt_4_def": "to be interesting; to cause to like"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The government failed to recognize the ____ of the public's unhappiness with the new law.", "Opt_1": "debate", "Opt_2": "trait", "Opt_3": "dimension", "Opt_4": "decision", "Answer": "dimension", "Opt_1_def": "formal discussion", "Opt_2_def": "characteristic; aspect", "Opt_3_def": "importance; amount", "Opt_4_def": "intention to do something, choice"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "If you do not have a particular title in mind, but wish to suggest that the library ____ more material on a specific subject, please enter your name.", "Opt_1": "purchase", "Opt_2": "notice", "Opt_3": "confine", "Opt_4": "magnify", "Answer": "purchase", "Opt_1_def": "to buy", "Opt_2_def": "to see or realize", "Opt_3_def": "to limit", "Opt_4_def": "to make or show larger"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Give me a ____ explanation of how the accident happened.", "Opt_1": "brief", "Opt_2": "strict", "Opt_3": "vast", "Opt_4": "complete", "Answer": "brief", "Opt_1_def": "short", "Opt_2_def": "hard, not changeable", "Opt_3_def": "very large", "Opt_4_def": "full or finished"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "There is no magic ____ for getting better in English, but lots of reading is an easy and enjoyable way to improve.", "Opt_1": "balance", "Opt_2": "formula", "Opt_3": "instruction", "Opt_4": "transition", "Answer": "formula", "Opt_1_def": "equalness", "Opt_2_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_3_def": "advice or teaching how to do something; an order to do something", "Opt_4_def": "a move from one (place, time, etc.) to another"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "If you do not ____ the rules of the classroom, you will be sent to the headmaster.", "Opt_1": "obey", "Opt_2": "appear", "Opt_3": "broadcast", "Opt_4": "conform", "Answer": "obey", "Opt_1_def": "to do as commanded or expected", "Opt_2_def": "to come, be seen", "Opt_3_def": "to tell or transmit (often by means of a television programme)", "Opt_4_def": "to do what is required"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "This international ____ course has been especially created for international students in their final stage of studies in Law.", "Opt_1": "margin", "Opt_2": "constraint", "Opt_3": "degree", "Opt_4": "background", "Answer": "degree", "Opt_1_def": "amount; distance", "Opt_2_def": "to hold back; to prevent", "Opt_3_def": "amount", "Opt_4_def": "family experiences; circumstances"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The war in Iraq serves to ____ the government's unwillingness to listen to the wishes of the majority of its people.", "Opt_1": "lessen", "Opt_2": "survive", "Opt_3": "modify", "Opt_4": "illustrate", "Answer": "illustrate", "Opt_1_def": "to reduce", "Opt_2_def": "to not die", "Opt_3_def": "to change", "Opt_4_def": "to show; to make clear"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Our chief problem is how to ____ the governors that we are right.", "Opt_1": "promote", "Opt_2": "distort", "Opt_3": "comprise", "Opt_4": "convince", "Answer": "convince", "Opt_1_def": "to encourage; to raise to a higher position in a job", "Opt_2_def": "to change or affect something (negatively)", "Opt_3_def": "to be made up of; to include", "Opt_4_def": "to (try and) get someone to believe something"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "This line on the playground is the ____ to where you are allowed to go as a grade 7 student.", "Opt_1": "source", "Opt_2": "limit", "Opt_3": "community", "Opt_4": "mechanism", "Answer": "limit", "Opt_1_def": "where something begins, where you can find something", "Opt_2_def": "extent, boundary", "Opt_3_def": "a group of people", "Opt_4_def": "procedure, process"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "There are a few meetings next week but the ____ conference doesn't start until on Monday 23.", "Opt_1": "effective", "Opt_2": "actual", "Opt_3": "logical", "Opt_4": "scarce", "Answer": "actual", "Opt_1_def": "good, working well", "Opt_2_def": "real", "Opt_3_def": "making sense", "Opt_4_def": "rare, not abundant"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Students who are awarded an International Student Scholarship must fulfill the following requirements each semester in order to ____ receiving this award.", "Opt_1": "consist", "Opt_2": "purchase", "Opt_3": "continue", "Opt_4": "establish", "Answer": "continue", "Opt_1_def": "to have in it; to have as part of it", "Opt_2_def": "to buy", "Opt_3_def": "to carry on, not stop", "Opt_4_def": "to begin or set up"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "He has a ____ chance of getting in to Oxford University if he gets top scores in all his exams.", "Opt_1": "independent", "Opt_2": "explicit", "Opt_3": "slight", "Opt_4": "deliberate", "Answer": "slight", "Opt_1_def": "free; not needing anyone or anything else", "Opt_2_def": "clearly and openly expressed", "Opt_3_def": "small", "Opt_4_def": "intentional, not by accident"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The strategy failed to persuade workers themselves to consider ____ service as anything other than a temporary transition.", "Opt_1": "domestic", "Opt_2": "appropriate", "Opt_3": "flexible", "Opt_4": "utter", "Answer": "domestic", "Opt_1_def": "home", "Opt_2_def": "right (for the occasion; suitable", "Opt_3_def": "can be changed or bent", "Opt_4_def": "complete, total"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Some students find it difficult to ____ to a new school in a new country.", "Opt_1": "appoint", "Opt_2": "threaten", "Opt_3": "adapt", "Opt_4": "reward", "Answer": "adapt", "Opt_1_def": "to give a job to someone", "Opt_2_def": "to warn or show signs of danger", "Opt_3_def": "to change (often in response to a changed situation)", "Opt_4_def": "to give something (e.g. a prize) for good work or behaviour"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "They ____ decided for various reasons that his age was not a drawback, that perhaps (at that time and for that position) it was an advantage.", "Opt_1": "recently", "Opt_2": "virtually", "Opt_3": "seldom", "Opt_4": "simply", "Answer": "simply", "Opt_1_def": "in the near past", "Opt_2_def": "almost", "Opt_3_def": "rare", "Opt_4_def": "completely; just; only"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The conclusion did not distort the truth of the ____ even though the student distorted some of the data that he collected.", "Opt_1": "manner", "Opt_2": "mixture", "Opt_3": "instruction", "Opt_4": "situation", "Answer": "situation", "Opt_1_def": "way of doing something", "Opt_2_def": "combination", "Opt_3_def": "advice or teaching how to do something; an order to do something", "Opt_4_def": "circumstances"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Please write a brief ____ of the causes of the first world war. Write no more than 300 words.", "Opt_1": "ratio", "Opt_2": "term", "Opt_3": "resident", "Opt_4": "summary", "Answer": "summary", "Opt_1_def": "mathematical relationship between two amount", "Opt_2_def": "a word or expression", "Opt_3_def": "a person who lives in a place", "Opt_4_def": "a short account of the most important details"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "There is land ____ the ice in Antarctica, but water ____ it at the North Pole.", "Opt_1": "beyond", "Opt_2": "beneath", "Opt_3": "worth", "Opt_4": "besides", "Answer": "beneath", "Opt_1_def": "further than: past", "Opt_2_def": "below", "Opt_3_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_4_def": "in addition to; as well as"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "While I don't present this as absolutely the ____ method that everyone should use, it is important that a standardized technique be adopted.", "Opt_1": "common", "Opt_2": "minor", "Opt_3": "ultimate", "Opt_4": "equivalent", "Answer": "ultimate", "Opt_1_def": "often seen or happening", "Opt_2_def": "small, not important", "Opt_3_def": "final or most important", "Opt_4_def": "equal to; the same as"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Use this form when you need to ____ accidentally deleted files from the network.", "Opt_1": "restore", "Opt_2": "suspect", "Opt_3": "rotate", "Opt_4": "stipulate", "Answer": "restore", "Opt_1_def": "to put back, create again", "Opt_2_def": "to believe", "Opt_3_def": "to turn or move (around)", "Opt_4_def": "to require"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The management wanted to dismiss the incompetent employee but could find no-one better to ____ him.", "Opt_1": "approve", "Opt_2": "replace", "Opt_3": "donate", "Opt_4": "fail", "Answer": "replace", "Opt_1_def": "to agree to", "Opt_2_def": "to put in or take the place of ..", "Opt_3_def": "to give (usually money)", "Opt_4_def": "to not do something, or not work as expected; to do badly"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The twins ____ most of the weekend to their fishing hobby.", "Opt_1": "devote", "Opt_2": "claim", "Opt_3": "increase", "Opt_4": "react", "Answer": "devote", "Opt_1_def": "to give (time) to", "Opt_2_def": "to state to be true", "Opt_3_def": "to get bigger", "Opt_4_def": "to respond"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "There's no ____ to make an effort if the teacher never gives you back your work.", "Opt_1": "prejudice", "Opt_2": "loss", "Opt_3": "incentive", "Opt_4": "version", "Answer": "incentive", "Opt_1_def": "bias, discrimination, beliefs or feelings influenced by one's own background", "Opt_2_def": "removal or reduction", "Opt_3_def": "reason to do something", "Opt_4_def": "form"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Vegetable crops are the most important ____ group for small farms in southern states and their importance is expected to increase.", "Opt_1": "aid", "Opt_2": "equipment", "Opt_3": "commodity", "Opt_4": "liberty", "Answer": "commodity", "Opt_1_def": "help (often financial help)", "Opt_2_def": "the things you need (to do a job or play sport, etc.)", "Opt_3_def": "a product; something you can buy", "Opt_4_def": "freedom"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "In an ____ group, each person can exert sufficient influence on the decisions of the group to prevent the group from setting unattainable goals.", "Opt_1": "urban", "Opt_2": "effective", "Opt_3": "various", "Opt_4": "brief", "Answer": "effective", "Opt_1_def": "of the town or city", "Opt_2_def": "good, working well", "Opt_3_def": "several, of different kinds", "Opt_4_def": "short"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "It was not a ____ that anybody in the world would consider wise.", "Opt_1": "deed", "Opt_2": "objection", "Opt_3": "effort", "Opt_4": "career", "Answer": "deed", "Opt_1_def": "an action", "Opt_2_def": "a statement of disagreement or disapproval", "Opt_3_def": "hard work; attempt", "Opt_4_def": "a long-term job"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The new technique could lead to ____ use of solar power.", "Opt_1": "inherent", "Opt_2": "essential", "Opt_3": "widespread", "Opt_4": "ambiguous", "Answer": "widespread", "Opt_1_def": "part of; a fundamental characteristic of", "Opt_2_def": "very important", "Opt_3_def": "common", "Opt_4_def": "not clear; open to more than one interpretation"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "You should not ____ that the test questions this semester will be on the same topics.", "Opt_1": "harm", "Opt_2": "magnify", "Opt_3": "assume", "Opt_4": "promote", "Answer": "assume", "Opt_1_def": "to damage or injure", "Opt_2_def": "to make or show larger", "Opt_3_def": "to believe to be true; to presume or predict", "Opt_4_def": "to encourage; to raise to a higher position in a job"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The ____ of available parking spaces is a significant detriment to faculty and students.", "Opt_1": "lack", "Opt_2": "comment", "Opt_3": "demand", "Opt_4": "forecast", "Answer": "lack", "Opt_1_def": "absence of a thing", "Opt_2_def": "a short written or spoken statement or opinion", "Opt_3_def": "a need or desire for", "Opt_4_def": "prediction"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "In Ancient Rome not every ____ had equal rights.", "Opt_1": "citizen", "Opt_2": "occasion", "Opt_3": "process", "Opt_4": "hypothesis", "Answer": "citizen", "Opt_1_def": "person (member of a country)", "Opt_2_def": "time (opportunity)", "Opt_3_def": "a series of steps", "Opt_4_def": "idea or prediction"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Throughout the day, with a brief interval for lunch, he stared at the history project which was ____ the next morning.", "Opt_1": "despite", "Opt_2": "against", "Opt_3": "regarding", "Opt_4": "due", "Answer": "due", "Opt_1_def": "although", "Opt_2_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_3_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_4_def": "as a result of, because of"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The bulk of the urban districts, particularly in the Northern states, were totally ____ to this development.", "Opt_1": "discrete", "Opt_2": "spare", "Opt_3": "averse", "Opt_4": "verbal", "Answer": "averse", "Opt_1_def": "separate", "Opt_2_def": "not needed", "Opt_3_def": "against", "Opt_4_def": "to do with words and language (especially the spoken language)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The World Bank said China has the capacity to ____ the impact of the recent international financial market fluctuations.", "Opt_1": "strive", "Opt_2": "force", "Opt_3": "affect", "Opt_4": "absorb", "Answer": "absorb", "Opt_1_def": "to work or try hard", "Opt_2_def": "to make happen or to make someone do something", "Opt_3_def": "to have an influence on", "Opt_4_def": "to take in; to take up"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Her consistent efforts throughout the school year are ____ to yield excellent results in her final examinations.", "Opt_1": "political", "Opt_2": "current", "Opt_3": "formal", "Opt_4": "certain", "Answer": "certain", "Opt_1_def": "to do government and politics", "Opt_2_def": "happening now", "Opt_3_def": "serious, not relaxed or everyday", "Opt_4_def": "sure"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The machine did not work properly because the person installing it did not ____ the instructions.", "Opt_1": "enable", "Opt_2": "observe", "Opt_3": "obey", "Opt_4": "engage", "Answer": "obey", "Opt_1_def": "to make something or someone able to do something", "Opt_2_def": "to watch carefully", "Opt_3_def": "to do as commanded or expected", "Opt_4_def": "to participate in; to focus attention on"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Doctors can give no ____ explanation for the fact that so many people smoke even though they know how dangerous it is.", "Opt_1": "suitable", "Opt_2": "discrete", "Opt_3": "logical", "Opt_4": "confident", "Answer": "logical", "Opt_1_def": "good for a particular job or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "separate", "Opt_3_def": "making sense", "Opt_4_def": "sure that something will happen"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Be sure to ____ and disinfect feeding equipment and other objects that may have come in contact with the sick animals.", "Opt_1": "conceal", "Opt_2": "isolate", "Opt_3": "threaten", "Opt_4": "detect", "Answer": "isolate", "Opt_1_def": "to hide", "Opt_2_def": "to separate something or someone from others", "Opt_3_def": "to warn or show signs of danger", "Opt_4_def": "to see, find or notice"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It is easy to ____ the government for its failures, but no-one has come up with any better ideas.", "Opt_1": "blame", "Opt_2": "generate", "Opt_3": "criticize", "Opt_4": "review", "Answer": "criticize", "Opt_1_def": "to accuse", "Opt_2_def": "to make or produce", "Opt_3_def": "to express disapproval; to say what you don't like or think is good about something or someone", "Opt_4_def": "to check over (and make changes)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "It seems that the mind cannot extract the ____ information from what is supplied to it.", "Opt_1": "overall", "Opt_2": "necessary", "Opt_3": "broad", "Opt_4": "exact", "Answer": "necessary", "Opt_1_def": "general", "Opt_2_def": "needed; very important", "Opt_3_def": "wide, extensive", "Opt_4_def": "precise, opposite of approximate"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "These findings suggest that something in the brain's pain-processing and pain-killing systems may ____ by race and ethnicity.", "Opt_1": "transition", "Opt_2": "vary", "Opt_3": "grant", "Opt_4": "layer", "Answer": "vary", "Opt_1_def": "a move from one (place, time, etc.) to another", "Opt_2_def": "to change or be different", "Opt_3_def": "a sum of money given to a person or organization", "Opt_4_def": "level"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Survey show that women in American don't ____ their most serious health risk.", "Opt_1": "sustain", "Opt_2": "compete", "Opt_3": "recognize", "Opt_4": "consult", "Answer": "recognize", "Opt_1_def": "to keep going; to maintain", "Opt_2_def": "to try and win against someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "to know or understand (who someone is or what something is)", "Opt_4_def": "to get the advice of someone ( often an expert)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "No program has developed an approach that is ____ successful in working with the types of problems that we try to solve.", "Opt_1": "universally", "Opt_2": "extremely", "Opt_3": "roughly", "Opt_4": "definitely", "Answer": "universally", "Opt_1_def": "all over the world; by everyone", "Opt_2_def": "very", "Opt_3_def": "about, approximately", "Opt_4_def": "certainly; without doubt"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Many new astronomy learners, students and adults alike, are unfamiliar with the universe ____ the solar system.", "Opt_1": "beyond", "Opt_2": "except", "Opt_3": "besides", "Opt_4": "beneath", "Answer": "beyond", "Opt_1_def": "further than: past", "Opt_2_def": "but (not)", "Opt_3_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_4_def": "below"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "In about 5 billion years, the sun will ____ its fuel supply, and will puff up into a bloated star called a red giant.", "Opt_1": "spread", "Opt_2": "exhaust", "Opt_3": "expand", "Opt_4": "allocate", "Answer": "exhaust", "Opt_1_def": "to move (over a wider area)", "Opt_2_def": "to use up", "Opt_3_def": "to get bigger; to move into new areas", "Opt_4_def": "to give to (to promise to give)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "An employee or University student who wishes the matter to receive a ____ investigation and review should contact the EEO Officer.", "Opt_1": "principal", "Opt_2": "imaginary", "Opt_3": "credible", "Opt_4": "formal", "Answer": "formal", "Opt_1_def": "most important", "Opt_2_def": "not real; from the imagination", "Opt_3_def": "believable", "Opt_4_def": "serious, not relaxed or everyday"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The company does a minor ____ of business in the USA; the majority of its trade is in Europe.", "Opt_1": "affair", "Opt_2": "amount", "Opt_3": "route", "Opt_4": "institution", "Answer": "amount", "Opt_1_def": "an event or series of events", "Opt_2_def": "how much there is of something", "Opt_3_def": "the way to get to a place or a thing", "Opt_4_def": "a large organization; an important system or custom"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The school is planning to bring in an external tax ____ to analyze its finance methods.", "Opt_1": "territory", "Opt_2": "revolution", "Opt_3": "phase", "Opt_4": "expert", "Answer": "expert", "Opt_1_def": "land; area (of interest)", "Opt_2_def": "a time of great change", "Opt_3_def": "a (short) period of time; stage", "Opt_4_def": "someone with great knowledge in a particular field"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It is often ____ to revise a mathematical model several times in the course of an urban operations research study.", "Opt_1": "subjective", "Opt_2": "wise", "Opt_3": "necessary", "Opt_4": "original", "Answer": "necessary", "Opt_1_def": "based on personal opinion or feeling", "Opt_2_def": "intelligent; sensible", "Opt_3_def": "needed; very important", "Opt_4_def": "the first of its kind"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Attendance will not constitute a specific percentage of your final grade, but if you miss more than two classes you will ____ fail this course.", "Opt_1": "accordingly", "Opt_2": "definitely", "Opt_3": "nevertheless", "Opt_4": "greatly", "Answer": "definitely", "Opt_1_def": "appropriate to; in compliance with", "Opt_2_def": "certainly; without doubt", "Opt_3_def": "however (although / despite that)", "Opt_4_def": "very much"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "NOAA is supporting the Coast Guard in the ____ to an oil spill in the Calcasieu Ship Channel.", "Opt_1": "passage", "Opt_2": "insight", "Opt_3": "response", "Opt_4": "legislation", "Answer": "response", "Opt_1_def": "a piece of written or spoken text", "Opt_2_def": "understanding (often of a complex problem)", "Opt_3_def": "answer or reply; reaction", "Opt_4_def": "governmental rule; law"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "I went on a long ____ last year. First I travelled to Japan, then I flew to Brazil. After that I sailed to California before coming home.", "Opt_1": "instance", "Opt_2": "ability", "Opt_3": "journey", "Opt_4": "topic", "Answer": "journey", "Opt_1_def": "example", "Opt_2_def": "ableness to do something; a skill for doing something well", "Opt_3_def": "a long trip to a different place", "Opt_4_def": "area of interest or discussion"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Students who seriously ____ network security or otherwise misuse the computing facilities will have their accounts terminated.", "Opt_1": "prevail", "Opt_2": "disrupt", "Opt_3": "expand", "Opt_4": "violate", "Answer": "violate", "Opt_1_def": "to succeed; to overcome", "Opt_2_def": "to interrupt an event; to damage", "Opt_3_def": "to get bigger; to move into new areas", "Opt_4_def": "to spoil or break"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "They still ____ copying the work from the internet, but I ran a Google search and found it immediately.", "Opt_1": "explore", "Opt_2": "deny", "Opt_3": "avoid", "Opt_4": "behave", "Answer": "deny", "Opt_1_def": "to look into a place or thing (in order to learn more about it)", "Opt_2_def": "to refuse ( responsibility for doing or saying something); to say that something is not correct", "Opt_3_def": "to not do something or go somewhere", "Opt_4_def": "to act or do things in a certain way"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Game reasoning is simply moral reasoning that occurs in the context of competitive sports, and ____ elsewhere as well.", "Opt_1": "thereby", "Opt_2": "eventually", "Opt_3": "seldom", "Opt_4": "perhaps", "Answer": "perhaps", "Opt_1_def": "by doing this", "Opt_2_def": "in the end", "Opt_3_def": "rare", "Opt_4_def": "maybe, possibly"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Some people have claimed that the ____ reason for the invasion of Iraq was to gain control of the oil fields.", "Opt_1": "poor", "Opt_2": "passive", "Opt_3": "sole", "Opt_4": "domestic", "Answer": "sole", "Opt_1_def": "bad, unsatisfactory", "Opt_2_def": "not active; unresponsive", "Opt_3_def": "only", "Opt_4_def": "home"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The Commission was unable to estimate the cost of complying with new requirements ____ data recording.", "Opt_1": "despite", "Opt_2": "regarding", "Opt_3": "beneath", "Opt_4": "except", "Answer": "regarding", "Opt_1_def": "although", "Opt_2_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_3_def": "below", "Opt_4_def": "but (not)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Desdemona is ____ for much of the play and when she dies at the end, she takes the blame for her death.", "Opt_1": "deliberate", "Opt_2": "ideal", "Opt_3": "unique", "Opt_4": "passive", "Answer": "passive", "Opt_1_def": "intentional, not by accident", "Opt_2_def": "best, optimal", "Opt_3_def": "single, unusual, one of a kind", "Opt_4_def": "not active; unresponsive"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "ESL students ____ better in classrooms where the teacher is aware of their special needs.", "Opt_1": "decrease", "Opt_2": "consist", "Opt_3": "fare", "Opt_4": "generate", "Answer": "fare", "Opt_1_def": "to get smaller, to go down", "Opt_2_def": "to have in it; to have as part of it", "Opt_3_def": "to do or succeed", "Opt_4_def": "to make or produce"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Good teaching is a ____ of fairness, firmness and friendliness.", "Opt_1": "balance", "Opt_2": "ratio", "Opt_3": "research", "Opt_4": "amount", "Answer": "balance", "Opt_1_def": "equalness", "Opt_2_def": "mathematical relationship between two amount", "Opt_3_def": "study; the finding of information", "Opt_4_def": "how much there is of something"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Plagiarism is easy to ____ but often hard to define. This is partly because the legal rules differ sharply from the ethical ones.", "Opt_1": "condemn", "Opt_2": "appeal", "Opt_3": "detect", "Opt_4": "address", "Answer": "condemn", "Opt_1_def": "to express strong disapproval", "Opt_2_def": "to complain against an official judgment; to make a strong request", "Opt_3_def": "to see, find or notice", "Opt_4_def": "to give attention to (an issue)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The Morningside Heights ____ in New York is a prime example of what Jacobs feels should not be done for city rebuilding.", "Opt_1": "sum", "Opt_2": "area", "Opt_3": "region", "Opt_4": "skill", "Answer": "area", "Opt_1_def": "an amount of money, total", "Opt_2_def": "field, sphere", "Opt_3_def": "part of a place", "Opt_4_def": "ability (e.g. in sport or music)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Doctors can give no ____ explanation for the fact that so many people smoke even though they know how dangerous it is.", "Opt_1": "minor", "Opt_2": "rigid", "Opt_3": "independent", "Opt_4": "logical", "Answer": "logical", "Opt_1_def": "small, not important", "Opt_2_def": "strict, unbending", "Opt_3_def": "free; not needing anyone or anything else", "Opt_4_def": "making sense"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "This is the single most important deed a district ____ can perform in the administration of his duties.", "Opt_1": "explain", "Opt_2": "withdraw", "Opt_3": "judge", "Opt_4": "view", "Answer": "judge", "Opt_1_def": "to give the reason for something or say how to do something", "Opt_2_def": "to go back or take away", "Opt_3_def": "to give an opinion about someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "to have an opinion"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The Education Department's increased demand for paperwork will ____ the patience and good will of teachers.", "Opt_1": "strain", "Opt_2": "approve", "Opt_3": "allege", "Opt_4": "belong", "Answer": "strain", "Opt_1_def": "to put under stress or make difficult", "Opt_2_def": "to agree to", "Opt_3_def": "to claim or state", "Opt_4_def": "to be part of something or owned by someone"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "In the heat of election campaigning, it is in no-one's interest to impose an ____ crisis upon the economy.", "Opt_1": "artificial", "Opt_2": "deficient", "Opt_3": "feasible", "Opt_4": "passive", "Answer": "artificial", "Opt_1_def": "not real or natural", "Opt_2_def": "poor, lacking in quantity or quality", "Opt_3_def": "possible", "Opt_4_def": "not active; unresponsive"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The police did not have the necessary ____ to cut the man free from the crashed car.", "Opt_1": "mechanism", "Opt_2": "equipment", "Opt_3": "contrast", "Opt_4": "doubt", "Answer": "equipment", "Opt_1_def": "procedure, process", "Opt_2_def": "the things you need (to do a job or play sport, etc.)", "Opt_3_def": "difference", "Opt_4_def": "a feeling of uncertainty (whether something is true)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "There is a ____ belief among the public that the government lied about the reason for going to war.", "Opt_1": "principal", "Opt_2": "suitable", "Opt_3": "widespread", "Opt_4": "available", "Answer": "widespread", "Opt_1_def": "most important", "Opt_2_def": "good for a particular job or purpose", "Opt_3_def": "common", "Opt_4_def": "can be had (bought or obtained)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "DeRosa's success is a ____ example of how the right environment and excellent faculty really can cause a scholarly transformation.", "Opt_1": "identical", "Opt_2": "genuine", "Opt_3": "basic", "Opt_4": "former", "Answer": "genuine", "Opt_1_def": "exactly the same", "Opt_2_def": "real and authentic", "Opt_3_def": "first or easy", "Opt_4_def": "previous, the one before, the first of two"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The teacher's threat to give the student a detention had an ____ impact on his behaviour.", "Opt_1": "sole", "Opt_2": "discrete", "Opt_3": "immediate", "Opt_4": "subsequent", "Answer": "immediate", "Opt_1_def": "only", "Opt_2_def": "separate", "Opt_3_def": "first (without delay)", "Opt_4_def": "next, following"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Why have these countries failed to develop ____ receiving billions of dollars in assistance?", "Opt_1": "prior", "Opt_2": "except", "Opt_3": "despite", "Opt_4": "instead", "Answer": "despite", "Opt_1_def": "before", "Opt_2_def": "but (not)", "Opt_3_def": "although", "Opt_4_def": "in place of; rather than"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The boss decided not to ____ her employee's request to leave work early.", "Opt_1": "accelerate", "Opt_2": "approve", "Opt_3": "defend", "Opt_4": "exclude", "Answer": "approve", "Opt_1_def": "to get or make faster", "Opt_2_def": "to agree to", "Opt_3_def": "to give reasons for", "Opt_4_def": "to leave out; opposite of include"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Most historians agree that Kievan Russia was not a ____ political, cultural, or ethnic entity.", "Opt_1": "discrete", "Opt_2": "physical", "Opt_3": "homogeneous", "Opt_4": "average", "Answer": "homogeneous", "Opt_1_def": "separate", "Opt_2_def": "of the body", "Opt_3_def": "having the same qualities or characteristics", "Opt_4_def": "ordinary, typical"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Among male baboons, dominance ____ is independent of maternal ____, and changes markedly with age; males reach their highest ____ between 8 and 10 years of age.", "Opt_1": "scheme", "Opt_2": "rank", "Opt_3": "incident", "Opt_4": "distance", "Answer": "rank", "Opt_1_def": "plan. idea, project", "Opt_2_def": "position (in a list or hierarchy)", "Opt_3_def": "happening; event", "Opt_4_def": "how far it is from one place to another"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The government has come under pressure to ____ the tax on petrol because of the high cost of oil.", "Opt_1": "interfere", "Opt_2": "postpone", "Opt_3": "donate", "Opt_4": "reduce", "Answer": "reduce", "Opt_1_def": "to prevent; to harm", "Opt_2_def": "to put back in time", "Opt_3_def": "to give (usually money)", "Opt_4_def": "to make smaller or shorter"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "While I am not in favor of teaching creationism in public schools, I am also not ____ to having it presented and examined.", "Opt_1": "rare", "Opt_2": "crucial", "Opt_3": "averse", "Opt_4": "rational", "Answer": "averse", "Opt_1_def": "unusual", "Opt_2_def": "extremely important", "Opt_3_def": "against", "Opt_4_def": "base on reason, not on emotion or instinct"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Visit our web page Phases of the Moon for a more detailed explanation and a clear ____ that shows the phases of our moon.", "Opt_1": "rise", "Opt_2": "pattern", "Opt_3": "diagram", "Opt_4": "objection", "Answer": "diagram", "Opt_1_def": "to go up", "Opt_2_def": "clear and consistent behaviour", "Opt_3_def": "a type of picture or chart", "Opt_4_def": "a statement of disagreement or disapproval"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "We must hope that her heavy involvement in the school's sporting programme will not be to the ____ of her studies.", "Opt_1": "tradition", "Opt_2": "advantage", "Opt_3": "opportunity", "Opt_4": "detriment", "Answer": "detriment", "Opt_1_def": "a usual, old-time way of doing things", "Opt_2_def": "benefit", "Opt_3_def": "chance", "Opt_4_def": "disadvantage"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "She was raised by a family that did not ____ the significance of racial differences and the importance of developing a positive racial identity.", "Opt_1": "appreciate", "Opt_2": "assimilate", "Opt_3": "advocate", "Opt_4": "notice", "Answer": "appreciate", "Opt_1_def": "to understand (the value of someone or something)", "Opt_2_def": "to take in", "Opt_3_def": "to speak or write on behalf of someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "to see or realize"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The government needs to do more to ____ people without jobs to business that are looking for workers.", "Opt_1": "connect", "Opt_2": "suspend", "Opt_3": "anticipate", "Opt_4": "contribute", "Answer": "connect", "Opt_1_def": "to bring or put together", "Opt_2_def": "to stop (often for a short time only)", "Opt_3_def": "to expect", "Opt_4_def": "to give (for example: money, help or ideas); to play a part in"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "As the advisor, you often have other responsibilities that do not always permit giving undivided ____ to the organization.", "Opt_1": "attention", "Opt_2": "staff", "Opt_3": "feature", "Opt_4": "phase", "Answer": "attention", "Opt_1_def": "focus", "Opt_2_def": "people working at a particular place (particularly an office or school)", "Opt_3_def": "part, aspect", "Opt_4_def": "a (short) period of time; stage"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The new law will ____ unmarried mothers.", "Opt_1": "deny", "Opt_2": "persuade", "Opt_3": "undertake", "Opt_4": "exclude", "Answer": "exclude", "Opt_1_def": "to refuse ( responsibility for doing or saying something); to say that something is not correct", "Opt_2_def": "to try and make someone do something or agree to something", "Opt_3_def": "to (plan to) do", "Opt_4_def": "to leave out; opposite of include"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Such activity cannot be considered an ____ substitute for excellence in teaching and research.", "Opt_1": "diverse", "Opt_2": "adequate", "Opt_3": "positive", "Opt_4": "commercial", "Answer": "adequate", "Opt_1_def": "many and different", "Opt_2_def": "good enough; ok", "Opt_3_def": "good; optimistic", "Opt_4_def": "to do with business"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The school needs to ____ the serious problem of bullying among grade 7 students.", "Opt_1": "address", "Opt_2": "convince", "Opt_3": "drain", "Opt_4": "emphasize", "Answer": "address", "Opt_1_def": "to give attention to (an issue)", "Opt_2_def": "to (try and) get someone to believe something", "Opt_3_def": "to take away; to get rid of", "Opt_4_def": "to stress, to say something strongly"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "In addition to paying for the required tuition and fees, you will need to ____ a variety of materials to complete this class.", "Opt_1": "annotate", "Opt_2": "procure", "Opt_3": "suspect", "Opt_4": "suppose", "Answer": "procure", "Opt_1_def": "to make notes on a piece of writing", "Opt_2_def": "to get or obtain", "Opt_3_def": "to believe", "Opt_4_def": "to think, imagine"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "A student seeking a career in this ____ of study will have abundant opportunities to develop personal and professional skills.", "Opt_1": "field", "Opt_2": "phenomenon", "Opt_3": "portion", "Opt_4": "impact", "Answer": "field", "Opt_1_def": "area of interest or study", "Opt_2_def": "a happening (often unusual or unexpected)", "Opt_3_def": "part, amount", "Opt_4_def": "effect"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The school is located in the wooded ____ to the north west of Frankfurt.", "Opt_1": "image", "Opt_2": "region", "Opt_3": "criterion", "Opt_4": "privilege", "Answer": "region", "Opt_1_def": "picture", "Opt_2_def": "part of a place", "Opt_3_def": "a way to judge the value or importance of something", "Opt_4_def": "a right (to do something)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "If we accept your request to amend the information, we will make ____ efforts to inform others, including people you have authorized, of the amendment.", "Opt_1": "capable", "Opt_2": "reasonable", "Opt_3": "actual", "Opt_4": "averse", "Answer": "reasonable", "Opt_1_def": "able", "Opt_2_def": "acceptable, quite good", "Opt_3_def": "real", "Opt_4_def": "against"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Dairy farmers have led the latest in a long series of protests by agricultural associations, ____ the record high prices for farm products.", "Opt_1": "besides", "Opt_2": "beyond", "Opt_3": "despite", "Opt_4": "worth", "Answer": "despite", "Opt_1_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_2_def": "further than: past", "Opt_3_def": "although", "Opt_4_def": "useful; having a point or purpose"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "I ____ to put all of my lecture notes online because I do want students to attend the lectures.", "Opt_1": "attain", "Opt_2": "dismiss", "Opt_3": "hesitate", "Opt_4": "provide", "Answer": "hesitate", "Opt_1_def": "to get, achieve", "Opt_2_def": "to reject, to treat as unimportant", "Opt_3_def": "to pause before saying or doing something", "Opt_4_def": "to give"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "In an article in the March 11, 2004 issue of Nature, the investigators report that female mice ____ the ability to make new egg cells well into adulthood.", "Opt_1": "retain", "Opt_2": "hesitate", "Opt_3": "expand", "Opt_4": "convey", "Answer": "retain", "Opt_1_def": "to keep", "Opt_2_def": "to pause before saying or doing something", "Opt_3_def": "to get bigger; to move into new areas", "Opt_4_def": "to pass on to another person (often by speaking)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Some tests may be very ____ but too costly to run, while others are less costly but not as precise.", "Opt_1": "rational", "Opt_2": "accurate", "Opt_3": "relevant", "Opt_4": "public", "Answer": "accurate", "Opt_1_def": "base on reason, not on emotion or instinct", "Opt_2_def": "exact, containing no mistakes", "Opt_3_def": "connected to the topic of discussion or consideration", "Opt_4_def": "open to all; not private"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "At this stage of our research we were unable to find a means for accessing the ____ decisions made in these cases.", "Opt_1": "actual", "Opt_2": "invisible", "Opt_3": "certain", "Opt_4": "sole", "Answer": "actual", "Opt_1_def": "real", "Opt_2_def": "cannot be seen", "Opt_3_def": "sure", "Opt_4_def": "only"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "It was an ____ conservative institution, and did not enlarge its business to any extent.", "Opt_1": "therefore", "Opt_2": "gradually", "Opt_3": "eventually", "Opt_4": "extremely", "Answer": "extremely", "Opt_1_def": "so, as a result", "Opt_2_def": "slowly; steadily", "Opt_3_def": "in the end", "Opt_4_def": "very"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Doctors often fail in their attempt to ____ patients to stop smoking. The habit is too addictive.", "Opt_1": "permit", "Opt_2": "persuade", "Opt_3": "illuminate", "Opt_4": "view", "Answer": "persuade", "Opt_1_def": "to allow", "Opt_2_def": "to try and make someone do something or agree to something", "Opt_3_def": "to show clearly; to light up", "Opt_4_def": "to have an opinion"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The U.S. firms selling steel in India must ____ against the firms from not merely India but Europe, Japan, Korea and China as well.", "Opt_1": "manage", "Opt_2": "compete", "Opt_3": "strive", "Opt_4": "restore", "Answer": "compete", "Opt_1_def": "to succeed in doing something; to be able to do something", "Opt_2_def": "to try and win against someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "to work or try hard", "Opt_4_def": "to put back, create again"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Beethoven was not an ideal parent and ____ friction developed between the two, contributing to his son's attempted suicide in 1826.", "Opt_1": "convenient", "Opt_2": "enormous", "Opt_3": "genuine", "Opt_4": "fortunate", "Answer": "enormous", "Opt_1_def": "easy, not causing problems", "Opt_2_def": "very big", "Opt_3_def": "real and authentic", "Opt_4_def": "lucky"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Although we have already received a number of excellent proposals for papers, it has been decided to ____ the deadline for submissions.", "Opt_1": "deteriorate", "Opt_2": "strive", "Opt_3": "extend", "Opt_4": "neglect", "Answer": "extend", "Opt_1_def": "to get worse", "Opt_2_def": "to work or try hard", "Opt_3_def": "to make longer in time or space", "Opt_4_def": "to not think about or care for"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "If you are caught drinking and driving, this results in an ____ driving ban of at least 3 months.", "Opt_1": "characteristic", "Opt_2": "novel", "Opt_3": "initial", "Opt_4": "automatic", "Answer": "automatic", "Opt_1_def": "typical", "Opt_2_def": "new", "Opt_3_def": "starting, first", "Opt_4_def": "happening by itself; happening naturally or usually"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The most serious objection raised ____ the survey questions the use of self-report scales to assess prejudice.", "Opt_1": "despite", "Opt_2": "beyond", "Opt_3": "against", "Opt_4": "besides", "Answer": "against", "Opt_1_def": "although", "Opt_2_def": "further than: past", "Opt_3_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_4_def": "in addition to; as well as"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The media and the public should not ____ the music industry for the jobs that parents are not fulfilling.", "Opt_1": "blame", "Opt_2": "undertake", "Opt_3": "accumulate", "Opt_4": "halt", "Answer": "blame", "Opt_1_def": "to accuse", "Opt_2_def": "to (plan to) do", "Opt_3_def": "to grow; to gather together", "Opt_4_def": "to stop"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The single, vital, principle on which the true republic must ____ itself, he insists, is the principle of good-will.", "Opt_1": "ignore", "Opt_2": "found", "Opt_3": "praise", "Opt_4": "accelerate", "Answer": "found", "Opt_1_def": "to take no notice of; to leave out (of consideration)", "Opt_2_def": "to begin (often an organization)", "Opt_3_def": "to express approval about something someone has done", "Opt_4_def": "to get or make faster"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The conclusion did not ____ the truth of the situation even though the student ____ed some of the data that he collected.", "Opt_1": "master", "Opt_2": "compile", "Opt_3": "distort", "Opt_4": "reveal", "Answer": "distort", "Opt_1_def": "to (gain) control", "Opt_2_def": "to put together (often in a list", "Opt_3_def": "to change or affect something (negatively)", "Opt_4_def": "to show or uncover"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The government has decided to ____ it proposals to increase income tax after massive demonstrations on the streets of the capital city.", "Opt_1": "assimilate", "Opt_2": "revise", "Opt_3": "confront", "Opt_4": "inhibit", "Answer": "revise", "Opt_1_def": "to take in", "Opt_2_def": "to change (in order to improve)", "Opt_3_def": "to deal with someone or something (often a problem or unpleasant situation)", "Opt_4_def": "to prevent or stop"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Learning to value and ____ the differences of the people around you is an important part of a liberal arts education.", "Opt_1": "cover", "Opt_2": "respect", "Opt_3": "assume", "Opt_4": "require", "Answer": "respect", "Opt_1_def": "to do; to complete", "Opt_2_def": "to think positively about someone; to tolerate or avoid interfering with something", "Opt_3_def": "to believe to be true; to presume or predict", "Opt_4_def": "to need"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The student council can ____ suggestions, but it has no power to make changes happen.", "Opt_1": "offer", "Opt_2": "emphasize", "Opt_3": "refuse", "Opt_4": "promote", "Answer": "offer", "Opt_1_def": "to ask if someone would like something (e.g. food or help)", "Opt_2_def": "to stress, to say something strongly", "Opt_3_def": "to not do something that someone wants you to do", "Opt_4_def": "to encourage; to raise to a higher position in a job"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "A poorly selected specimen or inaccurate information may result in an erroneous ____ or an inappropriate control recommendation.", "Opt_1": "bulk", "Opt_2": "decade", "Opt_3": "procedure", "Opt_4": "diagnosis", "Answer": "diagnosis", "Opt_1_def": "majority; largest part", "Opt_2_def": "a period of ten years", "Opt_3_def": "the way to do something", "Opt_4_def": "assessment of a situation (particularly of a problem)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Look at the ____ of your book. Did your dog try to eat it?", "Opt_1": "transition", "Opt_2": "innovation", "Opt_3": "sum", "Opt_4": "state", "Answer": "state", "Opt_1_def": "a move from one (place, time, etc.) to another", "Opt_2_def": "new object or idea", "Opt_3_def": "an amount of money, total", "Opt_4_def": "condition, situation"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The patient is making ____ progress after the 5-hour operation.", "Opt_1": "sound", "Opt_2": "logical", "Opt_3": "satisfactory", "Opt_4": "sufficient", "Answer": "satisfactory", "Opt_1_def": "good; strong", "Opt_2_def": "making sense", "Opt_3_def": "enough;OK", "Opt_4_def": "enough"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "You will analyze recurrent patterns of international political conflict, identify underlying issues, and suggest ____ resolutions.", "Opt_1": "substitute", "Opt_2": "assignment", "Opt_3": "alternative", "Opt_4": "agent", "Answer": "alternative", "Opt_1_def": "a thing or person to take the place of another", "Opt_2_def": "a task; the giving of a task", "Opt_3_def": "other possibility", "Opt_4_def": "a person who is paid to do a job for someone"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Illegal drugs are grouped into one or other ____ according to how dangerous they are considered.", "Opt_1": "agent", "Opt_2": "exponent", "Opt_3": "category", "Opt_4": "purpose", "Answer": "category", "Opt_1_def": "a person who is paid to do a job for someone", "Opt_2_def": "someone who holds and states an opinion", "Opt_3_def": "group of similar items", "Opt_4_def": "reason, goal"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Why have these countries failed to ____ despite receiving billions of dollars in assistance?", "Opt_1": "suppose", "Opt_2": "develop", "Opt_3": "succeed", "Opt_4": "conduct", "Answer": "develop", "Opt_1_def": "to think, imagine", "Opt_2_def": "to grow or improve", "Opt_3_def": "to do well", "Opt_4_def": "to do or perform; to behave"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "It offers an ____ solution to a problem based on good audience analysis, and fulfills minor as well as all major purposes.", "Opt_1": "uniform", "Opt_2": "common", "Opt_3": "compatible", "Opt_4": "effective", "Answer": "effective", "Opt_1_def": "having the same qualities", "Opt_2_def": "often seen or happening", "Opt_3_def": "able to work with someone or something else", "Opt_4_def": "good, working well"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Children ____ in classes where their teachers care about each of them as individuals.", "Opt_1": "damage", "Opt_2": "prosper", "Opt_3": "supervise", "Opt_4": "adapt", "Answer": "prosper", "Opt_1_def": "to spoil or break", "Opt_2_def": "to do well; to become rich", "Opt_3_def": "to control; to watch over people doing something", "Opt_4_def": "to change (often in response to a changed situation)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "If these reports are not returned, we will ____ that you have used all available sick leave for that particular reporting period.", "Opt_1": "criticize", "Opt_2": "presume", "Opt_3": "trade", "Opt_4": "explain", "Answer": "presume", "Opt_1_def": "to express disapproval; to say what you don't like or think is good about something or someone", "Opt_2_def": "to believe, assume", "Opt_3_def": "to exchange products or services", "Opt_4_def": "to give the reason for something or say how to do something"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The third stage of the writing process is when you revise your work. This means that you make any necessary changes to its ____ or content.", "Opt_1": "structure", "Opt_2": "experience", "Opt_3": "state", "Opt_4": "level", "Answer": "structure", "Opt_1_def": "the way something is made or organized", "Opt_2_def": "knowledge and skills gained over a long period of time", "Opt_3_def": "condition, situation", "Opt_4_def": "standard; layer; amount"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "It is impossible for the government to ____ the wishes of all its citizens.", "Opt_1": "subsidize", "Opt_2": "fulfill", "Opt_3": "discuss", "Opt_4": "convince", "Answer": "fulfill", "Opt_1_def": "to support financially", "Opt_2_def": "to do; to carry out (completely)", "Opt_3_def": "to talk about", "Opt_4_def": "to (try and) get someone to believe something"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Students are encouraged to discuss topics early on with the instructor, especially in the case of an ____ investigation.", "Opt_1": "intrinsic", "Opt_2": "independent", "Opt_3": "elaborate", "Opt_4": "global", "Answer": "independent", "Opt_1_def": "belonging to; inherent in", "Opt_2_def": "free; not needing anyone or anything else", "Opt_3_def": "detailed; complex", "Opt_4_def": "world"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Food prices are ____ rising again after many months of no change.", "Opt_1": "gradually", "Opt_2": "perhaps", "Opt_3": "barely", "Opt_4": "especially", "Answer": "gradually", "Opt_1_def": "slowly; steadily", "Opt_2_def": "maybe, possibly", "Opt_3_def": "not very much; hardly", "Opt_4_def": "particularly"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Some environmental scientists ____ that the dangers of global warming are even greater than most people suppose.", "Opt_1": "claim", "Opt_2": "prepare", "Opt_3": "shrink", "Opt_4": "impose", "Answer": "claim", "Opt_1_def": "to state to be true", "Opt_2_def": "to get something ready (or to get ready for something)", "Opt_3_def": "to get smaller", "Opt_4_def": "to force; to require to happen"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "How can you tell if the book, article, website, or other resource you located is a valid, ____ source?", "Opt_1": "credible", "Opt_2": "apparent", "Opt_3": "adequate", "Opt_4": "physical", "Answer": "credible", "Opt_1_def": "believable", "Opt_2_def": "clear; obvious", "Opt_3_def": "good enough; ok", "Opt_4_def": "of the body"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The final event of the day was an ____ tour of the Single Sisters House, which is in the process of restoration.", "Opt_1": "mobile", "Opt_2": "practical", "Opt_3": "optional", "Opt_4": "contemporary", "Answer": "optional", "Opt_1_def": "moving; able to move", "Opt_2_def": "useful; possible", "Opt_3_def": "not necessary or compulsory; can do it if you want", "Opt_4_def": "of this time, happening now"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The value of books would certainly degenerate if they could simply be produced and reproduced in cyberspace at an ____ minimal cost.", "Opt_1": "merely", "Opt_2": "absolutely", "Opt_3": "largely", "Opt_4": "extremely", "Answer": "extremely", "Opt_1_def": "only, just, simply", "Opt_2_def": "completely; 100%", "Opt_3_def": "mostly", "Opt_4_def": "very"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The conflict ended with a rebellion ____ the East India Company in 1857, and the firm eventually was nationalized.", "Opt_1": "against", "Opt_2": "beyond", "Opt_3": "except", "Opt_4": "besides", "Answer": "against", "Opt_1_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_2_def": "further than: past", "Opt_3_def": "but (not)", "Opt_4_def": "in addition to; as well as"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "While this was a great idea, the ____ were unclear about the requirements and how it would be graded.", "Opt_1": "opinion", "Opt_2": "figure", "Opt_3": "directions", "Opt_4": "struggle", "Answer": "directions", "Opt_1_def": "view; what you think about someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "number", "Opt_3_def": "instructions", "Opt_4_def": "a fight, a difficult situation to be overcome"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "We should never ____ or blame any person on account of outward actions that are common to all; but only on account of their principles.", "Opt_1": "praise", "Opt_2": "embody", "Opt_3": "join", "Opt_4": "enter", "Answer": "praise", "Opt_1_def": "to express approval about something someone has done", "Opt_2_def": "to be a good example of ..", "Opt_3_def": "to become a member (of an organization; to get together with others", "Opt_4_def": "to go in or put in"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "This survey is being used to gather information about the current level of frustration with computers and the ____ to which users feel rage.", "Opt_1": "gain", "Opt_2": "extent", "Opt_3": "comment", "Opt_4": "expense", "Answer": "extent", "Opt_1_def": "to get; to increase in ..", "Opt_2_def": "size, amount", "Opt_3_def": "a short written or spoken statement or opinion", "Opt_4_def": "cost"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Medical science now uses a computer scanning technique to examine the ____ of the human body.", "Opt_1": "interior", "Opt_2": "description", "Opt_3": "mixture", "Opt_4": "level", "Answer": "interior", "Opt_1_def": "inside", "Opt_2_def": "an account of what something is like or looks like", "Opt_3_def": "combination", "Opt_4_def": "standard; layer; amount"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Most students are ____ about the suggestion to replace the blackboards with whiteboards.", "Opt_1": "former", "Opt_2": "neutral", "Opt_3": "moderate", "Opt_4": "brief", "Answer": "neutral", "Opt_1_def": "previous, the one before, the first of two", "Opt_2_def": "neither for nor against; neither positive nor negative", "Opt_3_def": "not very much; not very strong; not extreme", "Opt_4_def": "short"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Telephone and telegraph ____ from the Greek words meaning far speak and far write.", "Opt_1": "fare", "Opt_2": "subsidize", "Opt_3": "derive", "Opt_4": "expose", "Answer": "derive", "Opt_1_def": "to do or succeed", "Opt_2_def": "to support financially", "Opt_3_def": "to come from or get from", "Opt_4_def": "to uncover, reveal"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "If you submit your application in person, there will be a ____ of up to 48 hours following receipt of your application before you can enroll for classes.", "Opt_1": "location", "Opt_2": "delay", "Opt_3": "evidence", "Opt_4": "objection", "Answer": "delay", "Opt_1_def": "place, where something or someone is", "Opt_2_def": "lateness", "Opt_3_def": "proof, signs", "Opt_4_def": "a statement of disagreement or disapproval"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The manager has decided form a committee to ____ the recent increase in theft from the storeroom.", "Opt_1": "increase", "Opt_2": "investigate", "Opt_3": "share", "Opt_4": "halt", "Answer": "investigate", "Opt_1_def": "to get bigger", "Opt_2_def": "to find out what has happened or why something has happened", "Opt_3_def": "to exchange; to give", "Opt_4_def": "to stop"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Ultimately, this research will ____ the negative health impact of the hurricanes, which in turn will ____ the economic burden on society.", "Opt_1": "lessen", "Opt_2": "commence", "Opt_3": "circulate", "Opt_4": "obtain", "Answer": "lessen", "Opt_1_def": "to reduce", "Opt_2_def": "to start", "Opt_3_def": "to move from one place or person to another (often in a circle)", "Opt_4_def": "to get"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Since we can't observe it directly, we need to ____ it from the things we can observe.", "Opt_1": "rotate", "Opt_2": "investigate", "Opt_3": "communicate", "Opt_4": "infer", "Answer": "infer", "Opt_1_def": "to turn or move (around)", "Opt_2_def": "to find out what has happened or why something has happened", "Opt_3_def": "to convey information", "Opt_4_def": "to come to a conclusion about something"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The government ministers ____ to treat people as children to be protected from all the ills of the world.", "Opt_1": "correspond", "Opt_2": "suppress", "Opt_3": "diverge", "Opt_4": "tend", "Answer": "tend", "Opt_1_def": "to be related to", "Opt_2_def": "to hold back; to not allow to happen", "Opt_3_def": "to move apart; to be different from", "Opt_4_def": "to often behave in a certain way"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Educational websites have the ____ suffix: .edu. For example, the URL of this website is: esl.fis.edu.", "Opt_1": "theory", "Opt_2": "domain", "Opt_3": "assignment", "Opt_4": "quantity", "Answer": "domain", "Opt_1_def": "idea or hypothesis", "Opt_2_def": "area (of interest)", "Opt_3_def": "a task; the giving of a task", "Opt_4_def": "amount"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "There are ____ parts of the planet that have not yet been explored. These are all on the ocean floor.", "Opt_1": "immense", "Opt_2": "numerous", "Opt_3": "massive", "Opt_4": "rational", "Answer": "immense", "Opt_1_def": "very large", "Opt_2_def": "very many", "Opt_3_def": "very large", "Opt_4_def": "base on reason, not on emotion or instinct"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Rumours about teachers ____ quickly through schools.", "Opt_1": "circulate", "Opt_2": "discuss", "Opt_3": "migrate", "Opt_4": "assert", "Answer": "circulate", "Opt_1_def": "to move from one place or person to another (often in a circle)", "Opt_2_def": "to talk about", "Opt_3_def": "to go to another place", "Opt_4_def": "to claim, to say strongly"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The text should contain a concise ____ of the aims and scope of your thesis.", "Opt_1": "process", "Opt_2": "means", "Opt_3": "concept", "Opt_4": "description", "Answer": "description", "Opt_1_def": "a series of steps", "Opt_2_def": "way", "Opt_3_def": "idea; understanding", "Opt_4_def": "an account of what something is like or looks like"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Click here to review the rules of comma usage when you combine two ____ clauses.", "Opt_1": "independent", "Opt_2": "imaginary", "Opt_3": "widespread", "Opt_4": "equivalent", "Answer": "independent", "Opt_1_def": "free; not needing anyone or anything else", "Opt_2_def": "not real; from the imagination", "Opt_3_def": "common", "Opt_4_def": "equal to; the same as"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The teacher gave me a ____ about the need to be in class on time with all my materials.", "Opt_1": "profit", "Opt_2": "objective", "Opt_3": "lecture", "Opt_4": "substitute", "Answer": "lecture", "Opt_1_def": "money gained", "Opt_2_def": "aim or goal", "Opt_3_def": "a talk on a particular subject; talk criticizing unacceptable behaviour", "Opt_4_def": "a thing or person to take the place of another"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "As the advisor, you often have other responsibilities that do not always ____ giving undivided attention to the organization.", "Opt_1": "comply", "Opt_2": "verify", "Opt_3": "dedicate", "Opt_4": "permit", "Answer": "permit", "Opt_1_def": "to do what someone asks or orders", "Opt_2_def": "to prove or claim the truth", "Opt_3_def": "to devote (time and attention)", "Opt_4_def": "to allow"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The school's decision to ____ the tuition fees will have a serious implication on the number of students who plan to attend.", "Opt_1": "employ", "Opt_2": "stimulate", "Opt_3": "raise", "Opt_4": "extend", "Answer": "raise", "Opt_1_def": "to give a job to someone; to use", "Opt_2_def": "to interest, make grow or encourage", "Opt_3_def": "to lift; to make higher", "Opt_4_def": "to make longer in time or space"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Many prisons cannot comply with this law ____ to lack of space and inadequate facilities.", "Opt_1": "instead", "Opt_2": "due", "Opt_3": "against", "Opt_4": "beneath", "Answer": "due", "Opt_1_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_2_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_3_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_4_def": "below"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "When schools are unable to ____ student academic achievement, districts are responsible for helping those schools make the necessary changes.", "Opt_1": "disperse", "Opt_2": "improve", "Opt_3": "appreciate", "Opt_4": "exploit", "Answer": "improve", "Opt_1_def": "to spread out; to move apart", "Opt_2_def": "to get better", "Opt_3_def": "to understand (the value of someone or something)", "Opt_4_def": "to use (sometimes in a negative way)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The government hopes that its new tax law will result ____ in a reduction in teenage pregnancy.", "Opt_1": "accordingly", "Opt_2": "respectively", "Opt_3": "indirectly", "Opt_4": "simultaneously", "Answer": "indirectly", "Opt_1_def": "appropriate to; in compliance with", "Opt_2_def": "an expression used to refer to two things, one after the other", "Opt_3_def": "in a indirect way; not straight or immediate", "Opt_4_def": "at the same time"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "I cannot ____ you to listen, but I will ask you to leave the room if you talk while I do.", "Opt_1": "remain", "Opt_2": "compel", "Opt_3": "sustain", "Opt_4": "protect", "Answer": "compel", "Opt_1_def": "to stay; still exist", "Opt_2_def": "to force or make happen", "Opt_3_def": "to keep going; to maintain", "Opt_4_def": "to keep something out of danger"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "A student who is in ____ to the University at the end of any academic term shall not be permitted to register in the University again.", "Opt_1": "range", "Opt_2": "debt", "Opt_3": "apparatus", "Opt_4": "description", "Answer": "debt", "Opt_1_def": "extent, distance between two points", "Opt_2_def": "something owed to another person (often money)", "Opt_3_def": "equipment; things you need to do a job", "Opt_4_def": "an account of what something is like or looks like"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "At this stage of our research we were unable to find a means for accessing the ____ decisions made in these cases.", "Opt_1": "voluntary", "Opt_2": "consistent", "Opt_3": "actual", "Opt_4": "uniform", "Answer": "actual", "Opt_1_def": "done freely; from personal choice", "Opt_2_def": "regular or predictable; remaining the same", "Opt_3_def": "real", "Opt_4_def": "having the same qualities"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "A typical problem is that many companies will only ____ workers with experience, but how do young people gain that experience if they are not given a job. This is called a \"vicious circle\".", "Opt_1": "encourage", "Opt_2": "discover", "Opt_3": "cease", "Opt_4": "employ", "Answer": "employ", "Opt_1_def": "to move someone to do something by positive talk; support or help", "Opt_2_def": "to find out; to find something for the first time (esp. land or scientific knowledge)", "Opt_3_def": "to stop", "Opt_4_def": "to give a job to someone; to use"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "One of the most important jobs of a parent is to teach the child how to ____ in different situations.", "Opt_1": "behave", "Opt_2": "integrate", "Opt_3": "complicate", "Opt_4": "contribute", "Answer": "behave", "Opt_1_def": "to act or do things in a certain way", "Opt_2_def": "to fit into a new situation", "Opt_3_def": "to make things more complex or difficult", "Opt_4_def": "to give (for example: money, help or ideas); to play a part in"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The work involves some lifting and bending, and ____ requires travel away from the normal duty station.", "Opt_1": "somewhat", "Opt_2": "occasionally", "Opt_3": "eventually", "Opt_4": "thus", "Answer": "occasionally", "Opt_1_def": "quite, rather", "Opt_2_def": "sometimes", "Opt_3_def": "in the end", "Opt_4_def": "so"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "I ____ vocabulary as the single most important aspect of learning English.", "Opt_1": "accompany", "Opt_2": "examine", "Opt_3": "enable", "Opt_4": "regard", "Answer": "regard", "Opt_1_def": "to go with someone or something; to exist together", "Opt_2_def": "to look at carefully", "Opt_3_def": "to make something or someone able to do something", "Opt_4_def": "to think or have an opinion about something or someone"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The public are ____ satisfied with the government's performance.", "Opt_1": "largely", "Opt_2": "moreover", "Opt_3": "naturally", "Opt_4": "seldom", "Answer": "largely", "Opt_1_def": "mostly", "Opt_2_def": "also .., what is more ..", "Opt_3_def": "of course, obviously", "Opt_4_def": "rare"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The idea was to ____ the possibility of a local court or government treating a foreign investor unfairly.", "Opt_1": "retain", "Opt_2": "remove", "Opt_3": "include", "Opt_4": "suppose", "Answer": "remove", "Opt_1_def": "to keep", "Opt_2_def": "to take away", "Opt_3_def": "to put in; to have in", "Opt_4_def": "to think, imagine"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "There is a very clear ____ in the school for expelling students who do not follow the rules.", "Opt_1": "tool", "Opt_2": "mechanism", "Opt_3": "outcome", "Opt_4": "lecture", "Answer": "mechanism", "Opt_1_def": "something used to do a job", "Opt_2_def": "procedure, process", "Opt_3_def": "result", "Opt_4_def": "a talk on a particular subject; talk criticizing unacceptable behaviour"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "While a considerable ____ of agreement was attained, a uniform approach to food policy could not be reached.", "Opt_1": "delay", "Opt_2": "debate", "Opt_3": "degree", "Opt_4": "design", "Answer": "degree", "Opt_1_def": "lateness", "Opt_2_def": "formal discussion", "Opt_3_def": "amount", "Opt_4_def": "planning (drawing)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "If you want to have a more interesting style of presentation, vary the ____ and tone of your voice.", "Opt_1": "speed", "Opt_2": "challenge", "Opt_3": "exhibit", "Opt_4": "interpretation", "Answer": "speed", "Opt_1_def": "how quickly something moves or changes", "Opt_2_def": "difficult situation; problem", "Opt_3_def": "to show", "Opt_4_def": "explanation; assessment"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "As the advisor, you often have other responsibilities that do not always ____ giving undivided attention to the organization.", "Opt_1": "permit", "Opt_2": "embody", "Opt_3": "repeat", "Opt_4": "publish", "Answer": "permit", "Opt_1_def": "to allow", "Opt_2_def": "to be a good example of ..", "Opt_3_def": "to do or say again", "Opt_4_def": "to make available in paper or online form"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "People who ____ from hay fever cannot have real flowers in their house. They have artificial ones instead.", "Opt_1": "focus", "Opt_2": "react", "Opt_3": "suffer", "Opt_4": "declare", "Answer": "suffer", "Opt_1_def": "to direct attention (on an issue)", "Opt_2_def": "to respond", "Opt_3_def": "to experience something bad or painful", "Opt_4_def": "to state"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The ____ will move to a 42-volt electrical system within this decade.", "Opt_1": "treatment", "Opt_2": "generation", "Opt_3": "industry", "Opt_4": "course", "Answer": "industry", "Opt_1_def": "way of handing a person, situation or problem (often of illness)", "Opt_2_def": "group of people all born around the same time", "Opt_3_def": "area of business ( often manufacturing )", "Opt_4_def": "a subject or period of study"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The easiest way to ____ documents in .pdf is by using the Adobe Acrobat software.", "Opt_1": "appreciate", "Opt_2": "clarify", "Opt_3": "produce", "Opt_4": "regulate", "Answer": "produce", "Opt_1_def": "to understand (the value of someone or something)", "Opt_2_def": "to make something clear, explain", "Opt_3_def": "to make or create", "Opt_4_def": "to control"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "I propose that we ____ our own faults before we are too loud about the faults of others.", "Opt_1": "request", "Opt_2": "retreat", "Opt_3": "consider", "Opt_4": "trust", "Answer": "consider", "Opt_1_def": "to ask politely", "Opt_2_def": "to go back", "Opt_3_def": "to think", "Opt_4_def": "to believe that someone or something will be or work as promised"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Army leadership must emphasize the importance of reducing energy ____ to decrease costs.", "Opt_1": "credit", "Opt_2": "facilities", "Opt_3": "rank", "Opt_4": "demand", "Answer": "demand", "Opt_1_def": "gained on completing a course of study; praise", "Opt_2_def": "buildings and other places that can be used by people", "Opt_3_def": "position (in a list or hierarchy)", "Opt_4_def": "a need or desire for"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The good result in the election does not give the government ____ to do whatever it wants.", "Opt_1": "license", "Opt_2": "device", "Opt_3": "rank", "Opt_4": "lack", "Answer": "license", "Opt_1_def": "permission to do something (often an official document)", "Opt_2_def": "object; method", "Opt_3_def": "position (in a list or hierarchy)", "Opt_4_def": "absence of a thing"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "A major ____ in the proposal is that there is not sufficient money to finance it.", "Opt_1": "defect", "Opt_2": "profit", "Opt_3": "deal", "Opt_4": "fault", "Answer": "defect", "Opt_1_def": "problem; mistake", "Opt_2_def": "money gained", "Opt_3_def": "agreement", "Opt_4_def": "responsibility for a mistake or other problem"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "During the period of time that a student is on probation, any further instance of misconduct will ____ the Board seriously to consider requiring the student to withdraw from the College.", "Opt_1": "cause", "Opt_2": "growth", "Opt_3": "experiment", "Opt_4": "operation", "Answer": "cause", "Opt_1_def": "the reason why something happens", "Opt_2_def": "development, increase", "Opt_3_def": "test", "Opt_4_def": "procedure; happening; process"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "There are ____ ways that you can improve your English. Probably the best is to do plenty of reading.", "Opt_1": "verbal", "Opt_2": "original", "Opt_3": "various", "Opt_4": "logical", "Answer": "various", "Opt_1_def": "to do with words and language (especially the spoken language)", "Opt_2_def": "the first of its kind", "Opt_3_def": "several, of different kinds", "Opt_4_def": "making sense"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "This review found that some guidelines and standards for reprocessing rigid laryngoscopes are incomplete, inadequate, and not ____ with one another.", "Opt_1": "remote", "Opt_2": "consistent", "Opt_3": "steady", "Opt_4": "discrete", "Answer": "consistent", "Opt_1_def": "far, distant, small", "Opt_2_def": "regular or predictable; remaining the same", "Opt_3_def": "gradual; without interruptions; firm", "Opt_4_def": "separate"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The referee decided ____ the game because of the predicted thunderstorm.", "Opt_1": "arise", "Opt_2": "postpone", "Opt_3": "fade", "Opt_4": "acquire", "Answer": "postpone", "Opt_1_def": "to happen", "Opt_2_def": "to put back in time", "Opt_3_def": "to disappear slowly", "Opt_4_def": "to get or obtain"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "This document contains a ____ of what scientists think happened at Loihi in the summer of 1996, based upon geological, geophysical, geochemical and biological evidence.", "Opt_1": "function", "Opt_2": "summary", "Opt_3": "implication", "Opt_4": "education", "Answer": "summary", "Opt_1_def": "job or role", "Opt_2_def": "a short account of the most important details", "Opt_3_def": "result or consequence", "Opt_4_def": "schooling"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "She always goes ____ what is expected of her. No wonder she gets such good grades.", "Opt_1": "regarding", "Opt_2": "instead", "Opt_3": "beyond", "Opt_4": "despite", "Answer": "beyond", "Opt_1_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_2_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_3_def": "further than: past", "Opt_4_def": "although"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Compliment employees in public but always ____ them in private; this shows your respect for them and avoids embarrassment.", "Opt_1": "attract", "Opt_2": "recognize", "Opt_3": "criticize", "Opt_4": "succeed", "Answer": "criticize", "Opt_1_def": "to be interesting; to cause to like", "Opt_2_def": "to know or understand (who someone is or what something is)", "Opt_3_def": "to express disapproval; to say what you don't like or think is good about something or someone", "Opt_4_def": "to do well"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Television and the other news media have helped to ____ the person and the institution of the presidency.", "Opt_1": "cooperate", "Opt_2": "strain", "Opt_3": "appoint", "Opt_4": "magnify", "Answer": "magnify", "Opt_1_def": "to work (well) with another person", "Opt_2_def": "to put under stress or make difficult", "Opt_3_def": "to give a job to someone", "Opt_4_def": "to make or show larger"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "I don't think she realises the ____ of the task she has set herself.", "Opt_1": "magnitude", "Opt_2": "operation", "Opt_3": "power", "Opt_4": "instinct", "Answer": "magnitude", "Opt_1_def": "size; amount", "Opt_2_def": "procedure; happening; process", "Opt_3_def": "the right or authority to do something", "Opt_4_def": "natural feeling or reaction"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "She has gained ____ good grades since she has started attending school more regularly.", "Opt_1": "hardly", "Opt_2": "predominantly", "Opt_3": "hence", "Opt_4": "somewhat", "Answer": "predominantly", "Opt_1_def": "not very much", "Opt_2_def": "mostly", "Opt_3_def": "so, therefore", "Opt_4_def": "quite, rather"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "A close study of this volume will ____ any reader.", "Opt_1": "confine", "Opt_2": "diminish", "Opt_3": "consult", "Opt_4": "reward", "Answer": "reward", "Opt_1_def": "to limit", "Opt_2_def": "to get smaller or less important", "Opt_3_def": "to get the advice of someone ( often an expert)", "Opt_4_def": "to give something (e.g. a prize) for good work or behaviour"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Doctors can give no ____ explanation for the fact that so many people smoke even though they know how dangerous it is.", "Opt_1": "averse", "Opt_2": "logical", "Opt_3": "remote", "Opt_4": "anonymous", "Answer": "logical", "Opt_1_def": "against", "Opt_2_def": "making sense", "Opt_3_def": "far, distant, small", "Opt_4_def": "having no name or known author"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The ____ of the aid money that has been allocated to Afghanistan has been wasted.", "Opt_1": "episode", "Opt_2": "opinion", "Opt_3": "controversy", "Opt_4": "bulk", "Answer": "bulk", "Opt_1_def": "period of time", "Opt_2_def": "view; what you think about someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "an issue on which their are strong and conflicting opinions", "Opt_4_def": "majority; largest part"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "An even number multiplied by an odd number will always ____ an even number.", "Opt_1": "fear", "Opt_2": "distort", "Opt_3": "yield", "Opt_4": "add", "Answer": "yield", "Opt_1_def": "to be concerned or frightened about", "Opt_2_def": "to change or affect something (negatively)", "Opt_3_def": "to produce", "Opt_4_def": "to include; to give or say extra"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Her writing was poor in every respect; it was difficult to ____ her biggest problem.", "Opt_1": "disrupt", "Opt_2": "exist", "Opt_3": "fail", "Opt_4": "isolate", "Answer": "isolate", "Opt_1_def": "to interrupt an event; to damage", "Opt_2_def": "to be alive, to be in the world", "Opt_3_def": "to not do something, or not work as expected; to do badly", "Opt_4_def": "to separate something or someone from others"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "We used this information to construct a continuous measure of the ____ of subject-specific coursework to total coursework.", "Opt_1": "ratio", "Opt_2": "profit", "Opt_3": "field", "Opt_4": "task", "Answer": "ratio", "Opt_1_def": "mathematical relationship between two amount", "Opt_2_def": "money gained", "Opt_3_def": "area of interest or study", "Opt_4_def": "job"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "What do western Louisville and the Appalachian region have in common ____ being two of the poorest areas in Kentucky?", "Opt_1": "worth", "Opt_2": "among", "Opt_3": "besides", "Opt_4": "except", "Answer": "besides", "Opt_1_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "in, between", "Opt_3_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_4_def": "but (not)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Because multicultural audiences will ____ become more and more common, you will need to anticipate cultural differences when you analyze your audience.", "Opt_1": "dynamic", "Opt_2": "discrete", "Opt_3": "likely", "Opt_4": "complex", "Answer": "likely", "Opt_1_def": "changing; growing; energetic", "Opt_2_def": "separate", "Opt_3_def": "probable", "Opt_4_def": "difficult, complicated"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "It is a common belief that the universe is infinite. But who knows? Maybe one day we will ____ it has an edge or end.", "Opt_1": "discover", "Opt_2": "enlarge", "Opt_3": "adhere", "Opt_4": "precede", "Answer": "discover", "Opt_1_def": "to find out; to find something for the first time (esp. land or scientific knowledge)", "Opt_2_def": "to make larger", "Opt_3_def": "to keep to; to follow", "Opt_4_def": "to go or be before someone or something"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "A popular type of TV programme shows people who escape the ____ world and pretend to live as farmers did 100 years ago.", "Opt_1": "enormous", "Opt_2": "contemporary", "Opt_3": "arbitrary", "Opt_4": "tough", "Answer": "contemporary", "Opt_1_def": "very big", "Opt_2_def": "of this time, happening now", "Opt_3_def": "not planned or thought-out; not considering the wishes of others", "Opt_4_def": "difficult, strong"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Nevertheless, thirty-three years later, Israel is not ____ to withdraw from the Golan Heights to the 4 June 1967, prewar border.", "Opt_1": "willing", "Opt_2": "inherent", "Opt_3": "trivial", "Opt_4": "satisfactory", "Answer": "willing", "Opt_1_def": "happy or prepared to do something", "Opt_2_def": "part of; a fundamental characteristic of", "Opt_3_def": "not important", "Opt_4_def": "enough;OK"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "It is important to note that the ____ at which refracted light travels is dependent upon the density of the materials it is traveling through.", "Opt_1": "speed", "Opt_2": "dimension", "Opt_3": "duration", "Opt_4": "extract", "Answer": "speed", "Opt_1_def": "how quickly something moves or changes", "Opt_2_def": "importance; amount", "Opt_3_def": "period of time", "Opt_4_def": "to remove; to take out and use"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The school will ____ use of the library for all students unless the student who damaged the photocopier is found.", "Opt_1": "suspend", "Opt_2": "convince", "Opt_3": "abuse", "Opt_4": "manage", "Answer": "suspend", "Opt_1_def": "to stop (often for a short time only)", "Opt_2_def": "to (try and) get someone to believe something", "Opt_3_def": "to treat someone or something badly", "Opt_4_def": "to succeed in doing something; to be able to do something"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "For the purposes of this study, then, increasing the testing strength did not yield more ____ results.", "Opt_1": "reasonable", "Opt_2": "spare", "Opt_3": "crucial", "Opt_4": "accurate", "Answer": "accurate", "Opt_1_def": "acceptable, quite good", "Opt_2_def": "not needed", "Opt_3_def": "extremely important", "Opt_4_def": "exact, containing no mistakes"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "It was a ____ decision, but ultimately I think it was the student life that had the greatest impact on my decision to come to Wheaton.", "Opt_1": "technical", "Opt_2": "minor", "Opt_3": "obvious", "Opt_4": "tough", "Answer": "tough", "Opt_1_def": "to do with machines or the way things work", "Opt_2_def": "small, not important", "Opt_3_def": "clear, evident", "Opt_4_def": "difficult, strong"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "It is important that the government's proposals do not ____ the development of small businesses.", "Opt_1": "yield", "Opt_2": "suppose", "Opt_3": "spread", "Opt_4": "inhibit", "Answer": "inhibit", "Opt_1_def": "to produce", "Opt_2_def": "to think, imagine", "Opt_3_def": "to move (over a wider area)", "Opt_4_def": "to prevent or stop"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Some government decisions are made for ____ reasons and others for economic reasons.", "Opt_1": "permanent", "Opt_2": "actual", "Opt_3": "political", "Opt_4": "familiar", "Answer": "political", "Opt_1_def": "lasting for ever or for a very long time", "Opt_2_def": "real", "Opt_3_def": "to do government and politics", "Opt_4_def": "known; well-known"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Patience was not ____ in him, but he developed it under misfortune and opposition.", "Opt_1": "inherent", "Opt_2": "classic", "Opt_3": "voluntary", "Opt_4": "supplementary", "Answer": "inherent", "Opt_1_def": "part of; a fundamental characteristic of", "Opt_2_def": "very good, the best or most used", "Opt_3_def": "done freely; from personal choice", "Opt_4_def": "extra; additional"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Factory farming is just not ____ with animal welfare.", "Opt_1": "uniform", "Opt_2": "drastic", "Opt_3": "compatible", "Opt_4": "arbitrary", "Answer": "compatible", "Opt_1_def": "having the same qualities", "Opt_2_def": "severe; great", "Opt_3_def": "able to work with someone or something else", "Opt_4_def": "not planned or thought-out; not considering the wishes of others"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The company directors are ____ that business will improve in the new year.", "Opt_1": "inevitable", "Opt_2": "confident", "Opt_3": "prime", "Opt_4": "ideal", "Answer": "confident", "Opt_1_def": "cannot be changed or avoided; obvious", "Opt_2_def": "sure that something will happen", "Opt_3_def": "most important", "Opt_4_def": "best, optimal"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "In fact, most nations do not ____ immigrants for permanent settlement.", "Opt_1": "conduct", "Opt_2": "admit", "Opt_3": "own", "Opt_4": "justify", "Answer": "admit", "Opt_1_def": "to do or perform; to behave", "Opt_2_def": "to allow to enter", "Opt_3_def": "to have or possess", "Opt_4_def": "to give a reason for doing something"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Many people say that he does not ____ the qualities to become president of this country.", "Opt_1": "retire", "Opt_2": "possess", "Opt_3": "forego", "Opt_4": "monitor", "Answer": "possess", "Opt_1_def": "to stop working", "Opt_2_def": "to have or own", "Opt_3_def": "to do without; to give up", "Opt_4_def": "to watch ( someone's or something's behaviour )"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The government generally did not take steps to ____ or punish the most serious cases of abuse.", "Opt_1": "override", "Opt_2": "displace", "Opt_3": "investigate", "Opt_4": "accelerate", "Answer": "investigate", "Opt_1_def": "to take precedence over; to disregard", "Opt_2_def": "to push out or take the place of something or someone", "Opt_3_def": "to find out what has happened or why something has happened", "Opt_4_def": "to get or make faster"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Both Initial and Wokingham now ____ the figure for the cost of food and say it is lower.", "Opt_1": "dispute", "Opt_2": "doubt", "Opt_3": "proportion", "Opt_4": "layer", "Answer": "dispute", "Opt_1_def": "argument; conflict", "Opt_2_def": "a feeling of uncertainty (whether something is true)", "Opt_3_def": "amount; number; percentage", "Opt_4_def": "level"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "A geography graduate produces a piece of geographic research and analyzes, synthesizes, and evaluates the ____ information.", "Opt_1": "relevant", "Opt_2": "suitable", "Opt_3": "passive", "Opt_4": "sound", "Answer": "relevant", "Opt_1_def": "connected to the topic of discussion or consideration", "Opt_2_def": "good for a particular job or purpose", "Opt_3_def": "not active; unresponsive", "Opt_4_def": "good; strong"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "All this progress was a ____ of the advance of technology and also of advances in government and other social organizations in capitalist society.", "Opt_1": "consequence", "Opt_2": "battle", "Opt_3": "struggle", "Opt_4": "outcome", "Answer": "consequence", "Opt_1_def": "result", "Opt_2_def": "fight, part of a war", "Opt_3_def": "a fight, a difficult situation to be overcome", "Opt_4_def": "result"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The many hours of practice that usually underlie exceptional ____ remain out of sight to the casual observer.", "Opt_1": "performance", "Opt_2": "controversy", "Opt_3": "means", "Opt_4": "defect", "Answer": "performance", "Opt_1_def": "action or achievement", "Opt_2_def": "an issue on which their are strong and conflicting opinions", "Opt_3_def": "way", "Opt_4_def": "problem; mistake"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Unfortunately, hunger is no ____ problem in the United States, where the disparity between the affluent and the indigent is considerable.", "Opt_1": "minor", "Opt_2": "rigid", "Opt_3": "essential", "Opt_4": "utter", "Answer": "minor", "Opt_1_def": "small, not important", "Opt_2_def": "strict, unbending", "Opt_3_def": "very important", "Opt_4_def": "complete, total"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "McCready said she could not ____ anything in the New York Daily News story about her.", "Opt_1": "refute", "Opt_2": "recur", "Opt_3": "illustrate", "Opt_4": "present", "Answer": "refute", "Opt_1_def": "to prove to be untrue; to deny", "Opt_2_def": "to happen again", "Opt_3_def": "to show; to make clear", "Opt_4_def": "to give or show; to make a presentation"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "There is more than one successful ____ to teach and learn a foreign language.", "Opt_1": "concern", "Opt_2": "method", "Opt_3": "priority", "Opt_4": "victory", "Answer": "method", "Opt_1_def": "worry, fear", "Opt_2_def": "a way of doing something", "Opt_3_def": "first and most important task", "Opt_4_def": "win"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The government has invested little money in the health system. The quality of hospital care is sure to ____ more and more.", "Opt_1": "deteriorate", "Opt_2": "owe", "Opt_3": "form", "Opt_4": "assemble", "Answer": "deteriorate", "Opt_1_def": "to get worse", "Opt_2_def": "to be in someone's debt (especially money)", "Opt_3_def": "to make (into a shape)", "Opt_4_def": "to get, put or bring together"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "As a child, he began to stutter severely and, despite the best efforts of his teachers and parents, he was unable to ____ it.", "Opt_1": "approve", "Opt_2": "prosper", "Opt_3": "multiply", "Opt_4": "overcome", "Answer": "overcome", "Opt_1_def": "to agree to", "Opt_2_def": "to do well; to become rich", "Opt_3_def": "to increase greatly", "Opt_4_def": "to conquer, defeat"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "President Tom Gerety announced today that he will ____ on June 30, 2003, after nine years as the head of the college.", "Opt_1": "confront", "Opt_2": "fare", "Opt_3": "resign", "Opt_4": "encourage", "Answer": "resign", "Opt_1_def": "to deal with someone or something (often a problem or unpleasant situation)", "Opt_2_def": "to do or succeed", "Opt_3_def": "to give up (one's job)", "Opt_4_def": "to move someone to do something by positive talk; support or help"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "This could substantially change the nature of the Internet we have come to know, to the ____ of both the consumers and the providers of information.", "Opt_1": "detriment", "Opt_2": "goal", "Opt_3": "resident", "Opt_4": "counsel", "Answer": "detriment", "Opt_1_def": "disadvantage", "Opt_2_def": "aim or intention", "Opt_3_def": "a person who lives in a place", "Opt_4_def": "advice; advisor"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Although there are a number of credible strategies for trying to retain employees, money appears to be the most powerful retention tool with ____ to top performers.", "Opt_1": "clarify", "Opt_2": "regard", "Opt_3": "justify", "Opt_4": "reduce", "Answer": "regard", "Opt_1_def": "to make something clear, explain", "Opt_2_def": "to think or have an opinion about something or someone", "Opt_3_def": "to give a reason for doing something", "Opt_4_def": "to make smaller or shorter"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Digital Libraries constitute a relatively young scientific field, whose life spans ____ the last fifteen years.", "Opt_1": "thereby", "Opt_2": "dramatically", "Opt_3": "roughly", "Opt_4": "absolutely", "Answer": "roughly", "Opt_1_def": "by doing this", "Opt_2_def": "very strongly, significantly", "Opt_3_def": "about, approximately", "Opt_4_def": "completely; 100%"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "It operated below 60%, was generally poorly designed and ____ not worth considering.", "Opt_1": "therefore", "Opt_2": "roughly", "Opt_3": "rather", "Opt_4": "accordingly", "Answer": "therefore", "Opt_1_def": "so, as a result", "Opt_2_def": "about, approximately", "Opt_3_def": "instead", "Opt_4_def": "appropriate to; in compliance with"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The government refused to ____ from its plan to ban smoking in public places.", "Opt_1": "offer", "Opt_2": "diverge", "Opt_3": "yield", "Opt_4": "refuse", "Answer": "diverge", "Opt_1_def": "to ask if someone would like something (e.g. food or help)", "Opt_2_def": "to move apart; to be different from", "Opt_3_def": "to produce", "Opt_4_def": "to not do something that someone wants you to do"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Hopkins argues that the ____ court committed three discrete errors in determining his sentence.", "Opt_1": "district", "Opt_2": "guarantee", "Opt_3": "tool", "Opt_4": "desire", "Answer": "district", "Opt_1_def": "region of a city", "Opt_2_def": "to promise or assure that something will or will not happen", "Opt_3_def": "something used to do a job", "Opt_4_def": "a want or wish for something"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Example: She doesn't have a very good ____ with her parents.", "Opt_1": "instinct", "Opt_2": "purpose", "Opt_3": "rate", "Opt_4": "relationship", "Answer": "relationship", "Opt_1_def": "natural feeling or reaction", "Opt_2_def": "reason, goal", "Opt_3_def": "quantity; proportion; speed", "Opt_4_def": "the way to things are connected"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "TOEFL is not the most ____ part of the application, but it is an unavoidable part, which sometimes can be quite painful and time- consuming.", "Opt_1": "extraordinary", "Opt_2": "commercial", "Opt_3": "automatic", "Opt_4": "crucial", "Answer": "crucial", "Opt_1_def": "very unusual", "Opt_2_def": "to do with business", "Opt_3_def": "happening by itself; happening naturally or usually", "Opt_4_def": "extremely important"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Some students claim that they can ____ watch TV and do their homework.", "Opt_1": "simultaneously", "Opt_2": "definitely", "Opt_3": "simply", "Opt_4": "conversely", "Answer": "simultaneously", "Opt_1_def": "at the same time", "Opt_2_def": "certainly; without doubt", "Opt_3_def": "completely; just; only", "Opt_4_def": "opposite to what was just said; on the other hand"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The different religious groups ____ came to realize that none of them could hope to prevail over all the others.", "Opt_1": "gradually", "Opt_2": "simultaneously", "Opt_3": "definitely", "Opt_4": "naturally", "Answer": "gradually", "Opt_1_def": "slowly; steadily", "Opt_2_def": "at the same time", "Opt_3_def": "certainly; without doubt", "Opt_4_def": "of course, obviously"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Our chief problem is how to ____ the governors that we are right.", "Opt_1": "overlap", "Opt_2": "adopt", "Opt_3": "convince", "Opt_4": "compile", "Answer": "convince", "Opt_1_def": "to have in common; to cover part of", "Opt_2_def": "to take in; to start", "Opt_3_def": "to (try and) get someone to believe something", "Opt_4_def": "to put together (often in a list"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The unemployment figures ____ that the recent changes in tax have been successful.", "Opt_1": "introduce", "Opt_2": "indicate", "Opt_3": "infer", "Opt_4": "maintain", "Answer": "indicate", "Opt_1_def": "to talk about or bring in for the first time", "Opt_2_def": "to show or convey", "Opt_3_def": "to come to a conclusion about something", "Opt_4_def": "to claim or state"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "A small proportion of the government were ____ the Prime Minister's plan, but they were outvoted.", "Opt_1": "regarding", "Opt_2": "against", "Opt_3": "worth", "Opt_4": "prior", "Answer": "against", "Opt_1_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_2_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_3_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_4_def": "before"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "These budgets must be very carefully designed as it is extremely difficult, if not impossible, to ____ the amount of the award once it has been granted.", "Opt_1": "alter", "Opt_2": "cease", "Opt_3": "speculate", "Opt_4": "accuse", "Answer": "alter", "Opt_1_def": "to change", "Opt_2_def": "to stop", "Opt_3_def": "to think and talk about (often future events)", "Opt_4_def": "to blame"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "To ____ the highest positions in American politics it is necessary to come from a rich family.", "Opt_1": "attain", "Opt_2": "stress", "Opt_3": "focus", "Opt_4": "reward", "Answer": "attain", "Opt_1_def": "to get, achieve", "Opt_2_def": "to emphasize; to say what is important", "Opt_3_def": "to direct attention (on an issue)", "Opt_4_def": "to give something (e.g. a prize) for good work or behaviour"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "It is often necessary to revise a mathematical model ____ times in the course of an urban operations research study.", "Opt_1": "ideal", "Opt_2": "neutral", "Opt_3": "reliable", "Opt_4": "several", "Answer": "several", "Opt_1_def": "best, optimal", "Opt_2_def": "neither for nor against; neither positive nor negative", "Opt_3_def": "can be trusted, does not let you down \r\n", "Opt_4_def": "many (about 6 or seven)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The most serious ____ to implementing the Convention in Venezuela was clearly the poverty facing a large proportion of the population.", "Opt_1": "exercise", "Opt_2": "course", "Opt_3": "impact", "Opt_4": "obstacle", "Answer": "obstacle", "Opt_1_def": "a piece of work, activity", "Opt_2_def": "a subject or period of study", "Opt_3_def": "effect", "Opt_4_def": "barrier; problem"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Working with the Teacher Assistant is not ____ but recommended.", "Opt_1": "diverse", "Opt_2": "compulsory", "Opt_3": "elementary", "Opt_4": "legitimate", "Answer": "compulsory", "Opt_1_def": "many and different", "Opt_2_def": "required, must be done", "Opt_3_def": "easy", "Opt_4_def": "correct; allowed"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "You know that ____ of a law will not prevent you from being arrested for breaking it.", "Opt_1": "situation", "Opt_2": "scale", "Opt_3": "trend", "Opt_4": "ignorance", "Answer": "ignorance", "Opt_1_def": "circumstances", "Opt_2_def": "extent", "Opt_3_def": "pattern of continuing behaviour", "Opt_4_def": "lack of knowledge"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Her family were persecuted by the Nazis, so it's no surprise that she shows bias ____ the Germans.", "Opt_1": "among", "Opt_2": "worth", "Opt_3": "due", "Opt_4": "against", "Answer": "against", "Opt_1_def": "in, between", "Opt_2_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_3_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_4_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "This also helps you determine which variables it is essential to control to avoid an ____ answer.", "Opt_1": "formal", "Opt_2": "valid", "Opt_3": "ambiguous", "Opt_4": "flexible", "Answer": "ambiguous", "Opt_1_def": "serious, not relaxed or everyday", "Opt_2_def": "correct", "Opt_3_def": "not clear; open to more than one interpretation", "Opt_4_def": "can be changed or bent"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The information that you ____ in today's lesson will enable you to complete your project on nuclear energy.", "Opt_1": "overcome", "Opt_2": "receive", "Opt_3": "prosper", "Opt_4": "focus", "Answer": "receive", "Opt_1_def": "to conquer, defeat", "Opt_2_def": "to get", "Opt_3_def": "to do well; to become rich", "Opt_4_def": "to direct attention (on an issue)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "As a simple soldier he gained much ____ by conducting a retreat after all the superior officers had been killed or wounded.", "Opt_1": "credit", "Opt_2": "crisis", "Opt_3": "exponent", "Opt_4": "level", "Answer": "credit", "Opt_1_def": "gained on completing a course of study; praise", "Opt_2_def": "very dangerous situation, catastrophe", "Opt_3_def": "someone who holds and states an opinion", "Opt_4_def": "standard; layer; amount"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "I regard vocabulary as the single most important ____ of learning English.", "Opt_1": "notion", "Opt_2": "contrary", "Opt_3": "defect", "Opt_4": "aspect", "Answer": "aspect", "Opt_1_def": "idea; concept", "Opt_2_def": "opposite", "Opt_3_def": "problem; mistake", "Opt_4_def": "environment that lifts people up,\" says Jain."}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Stephen Krashen, a distinguished scholar and leading ____ in the field of language acquisition, held an open forum to present his findings on five topics.", "Opt_1": "phase", "Opt_2": "revolution", "Opt_3": "expert", "Opt_4": "desire", "Answer": "expert", "Opt_1_def": "a (short) period of time; stage", "Opt_2_def": "a time of great change", "Opt_3_def": "someone with great knowledge in a particular field", "Opt_4_def": "a want or wish for something"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "I cannot ____ you to listen, but I will ask you to leave the room if you talk while I do.", "Opt_1": "convince", "Opt_2": "consult", "Opt_3": "compel", "Opt_4": "magnify", "Answer": "compel", "Opt_1_def": "to (try and) get someone to believe something", "Opt_2_def": "to get the advice of someone ( often an expert)", "Opt_3_def": "to force or make happen", "Opt_4_def": "to make or show larger"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The government does not ____ its citizens an explanation for every decision it makes.", "Opt_1": "employ", "Opt_2": "owe", "Opt_3": "survive", "Opt_4": "label", "Answer": "owe", "Opt_1_def": "to give a job to someone; to use", "Opt_2_def": "to be in someone's debt (especially money)", "Opt_3_def": "to not die", "Opt_4_def": "to give a name to someone or something"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "President Tom Gerety announced today that he will ____ on June 30, 2003, after nine years as the head of the college.", "Opt_1": "embody", "Opt_2": "belong", "Opt_3": "prefer", "Opt_4": "resign", "Answer": "resign", "Opt_1_def": "to be a good example of ..", "Opt_2_def": "to be part of something or owned by someone", "Opt_3_def": "to like better", "Opt_4_def": "to give up (one's job)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Could you please ____ the question. I didn't understand what you said.", "Opt_1": "repeat", "Opt_2": "persuade", "Opt_3": "harm", "Opt_4": "succeed", "Answer": "repeat", "Opt_1_def": "to do or say again", "Opt_2_def": "to try and make someone do something or agree to something", "Opt_3_def": "to damage or injure", "Opt_4_def": "to do well"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Your work has shown a ____ improvement in recent weeks.", "Opt_1": "consistent", "Opt_2": "strict", "Opt_3": "significant", "Opt_4": "harsh", "Answer": "significant", "Opt_1_def": "regular or predictable; remaining the same", "Opt_2_def": "hard, not changeable", "Opt_3_def": "important, large", "Opt_4_def": "hard, unfair"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "As a teacher educator, I believe that new teachers need to reflect on, critically analyze, and ____ their own teaching.", "Opt_1": "compel", "Opt_2": "discuss", "Opt_3": "prohibit", "Opt_4": "evaluate", "Answer": "evaluate", "Opt_1_def": "to force or make happen", "Opt_2_def": "to talk about", "Opt_3_def": "to ban, disallow", "Opt_4_def": "to decide on the value, quality or importance of something"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "During this period she developed her ideas on art, her main one being that the best art did not ____ on reality but evoked the state of the soul.", "Opt_1": "ensure", "Opt_2": "devote", "Opt_3": "threaten", "Opt_4": "focus", "Answer": "focus", "Opt_1_def": "to make sure (of)", "Opt_2_def": "to give (time) to", "Opt_3_def": "to warn or show signs of danger", "Opt_4_def": "to direct attention (on an issue)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "You should ____ your name from the copies of the items you submit.", "Opt_1": "omit", "Opt_2": "generate", "Opt_3": "culminate", "Opt_4": "enhance", "Answer": "omit", "Opt_1_def": "to leave something out or not do something", "Opt_2_def": "to make or produce", "Opt_3_def": "to end", "Opt_4_def": "to make something better"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "This report summarizes our ____ findings.", "Opt_1": "absent", "Opt_2": "initial", "Opt_3": "common", "Opt_4": "widespread", "Answer": "initial", "Opt_1_def": "being not there; missing", "Opt_2_def": "starting, first", "Opt_3_def": "often seen or happening", "Opt_4_def": "common"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The contributors ____ that teaching is a gendered occupation with low status and relatively low pay.", "Opt_1": "restore", "Opt_2": "indicate", "Opt_3": "denote", "Opt_4": "assert", "Answer": "assert", "Opt_1_def": "to put back, create again", "Opt_2_def": "to show or convey", "Opt_3_def": "to mean; to be a sign of", "Opt_4_def": "to claim, to say strongly"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The government is planning to spend a ____ amount of money on new hospitals next year.", "Opt_1": "superior", "Opt_2": "homogeneous", "Opt_3": "legitimate", "Opt_4": "substantial", "Answer": "substantial", "Opt_1_def": "better", "Opt_2_def": "having the same qualities or characteristics", "Opt_3_def": "correct; allowed", "Opt_4_def": "large"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Educational research is a useful tool for both ____ and theoretical problem solving.", "Opt_1": "straightforward", "Opt_2": "practical", "Opt_3": "radical", "Opt_4": "capable", "Answer": "practical", "Opt_1_def": "easy", "Opt_2_def": "useful; possible", "Opt_3_def": "extreme, strong", "Opt_4_def": "able"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Matilda Thurston considered who was the most ____ architect to design a proper campus for 200 students.", "Opt_1": "adequate", "Opt_2": "valid", "Opt_3": "logical", "Opt_4": "final", "Answer": "logical", "Opt_1_def": "good enough; ok", "Opt_2_def": "correct", "Opt_3_def": "making sense", "Opt_4_def": "last"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Not any of these persons shall perform or ____ any practice that may damage the reputation of the university.", "Opt_1": "occupy", "Opt_2": "permit", "Opt_3": "reform", "Opt_4": "add", "Answer": "permit", "Opt_1_def": "to up space or time", "Opt_2_def": "to allow", "Opt_3_def": "to change and improve", "Opt_4_def": "to include; to give or say extra"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The sorting of students into homogeneous ____ and achievement groups is nearly as old as universal compulsory education in the United States.", "Opt_1": "goal", "Opt_2": "quality", "Opt_3": "ability", "Opt_4": "formula", "Answer": "ability", "Opt_1_def": "aim or intention", "Opt_2_def": "worth or value", "Opt_3_def": "ableness to do something; a skill for doing something well", "Opt_4_def": "a method of doing something"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The University may ____ the Contract at any time by giving thirty (30) days written notice to the Contract.", "Opt_1": "accelerate", "Opt_2": "fail", "Opt_3": "inspect", "Opt_4": "terminate", "Answer": "terminate", "Opt_1_def": "to get or make faster", "Opt_2_def": "to not do something, or not work as expected; to do badly", "Opt_3_def": "to look at carefully", "Opt_4_def": "to finish or stop"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Some assignments will be graded; others will ____ receive a check-mark.", "Opt_1": "merely", "Opt_2": "somewhat", "Opt_3": "hardly", "Opt_4": "dramatically", "Answer": "merely", "Opt_1_def": "only, just, simply", "Opt_2_def": "quite, rather", "Opt_3_def": "not very much", "Opt_4_def": "very strongly, significantly"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "What would you ____ to do today? Write a dictation or watch a video?", "Opt_1": "prefer", "Opt_2": "focus", "Opt_3": "appoint", "Opt_4": "clarify", "Answer": "prefer", "Opt_1_def": "to like better", "Opt_2_def": "to direct attention (on an issue)", "Opt_3_def": "to give a job to someone", "Opt_4_def": "to make something clear, explain"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "After about a year his family realized that this was not just a ____ and that he was serious about me and that we really cared about each other.", "Opt_1": "technique", "Opt_2": "advantage", "Opt_3": "phase", "Opt_4": "hypothesis", "Answer": "phase", "Opt_1_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_2_def": "benefit", "Opt_3_def": "a (short) period of time; stage", "Opt_4_def": "idea or prediction"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The workers participated in an ____ to see if they worked harder with music in the background.", "Opt_1": "expert", "Opt_2": "course", "Opt_3": "experiment", "Opt_4": "symbol", "Answer": "experiment", "Opt_1_def": "someone with great knowledge in a particular field", "Opt_2_def": "a subject or period of study", "Opt_3_def": "test", "Opt_4_def": "a picture; the representation of an idea"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Digital Libraries constitute a relatively young scientific field, whose life spans ____ the last fifteen years.", "Opt_1": "predominantly", "Opt_2": "roughly", "Opt_3": "approximately", "Opt_4": "hence", "Answer": "roughly", "Opt_1_def": "mostly", "Opt_2_def": "about, approximately", "Opt_3_def": "about; not exactly", "Opt_4_def": "so, therefore"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Sometimes it is necessary to ____ force in order to achieve peace in a troubled region.", "Opt_1": "contribute", "Opt_2": "decline", "Opt_3": "participate", "Opt_4": "exert", "Answer": "exert", "Opt_1_def": "to give (for example: money, help or ideas); to play a part in", "Opt_2_def": "to go down or get worse", "Opt_3_def": "to take part", "Opt_4_def": "to use"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "He certainly could not ____ the existence of major problems.", "Opt_1": "accelerate", "Opt_2": "deny", "Opt_3": "address", "Opt_4": "prevail", "Answer": "deny", "Opt_1_def": "to get or make faster", "Opt_2_def": "to refuse ( responsibility for doing or saying something); to say that something is not correct", "Opt_3_def": "to give attention to (an issue)", "Opt_4_def": "to succeed; to overcome"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The goal is to produce world-class scholars with capabilities in research, teaching, and service within the ____ area of Information and Decision Sciences.", "Opt_1": "broad", "Opt_2": "visual", "Opt_3": "domestic", "Opt_4": "logical", "Answer": "broad", "Opt_1_def": "wide, extensive", "Opt_2_def": "to do with sight and seeing", "Opt_3_def": "home", "Opt_4_def": "making sense"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The school cafeteria has made the ____ decision not to offer hamburgers, hot dogs and French fries to the younger students .", "Opt_1": "formal", "Opt_2": "sane", "Opt_3": "former", "Opt_4": "probable", "Answer": "sane", "Opt_1_def": "serious, not relaxed or everyday", "Opt_2_def": "reasonable; not mad", "Opt_3_def": "previous, the one before, the first of two", "Opt_4_def": "it is not probable that any thing better will be discovered than what was known to our fathers."}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "We do not ____ a unilateral ban on cosmetic testing on animals, nor do we reject the use of animals in biomedical research.", "Opt_1": "frustrate", "Opt_2": "advocate", "Opt_3": "train", "Opt_4": "threaten", "Answer": "advocate", "Opt_1_def": "to stop or prevent", "Opt_2_def": "to speak or write on behalf of someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "to teach someone how to do a job", "Opt_4_def": "to warn or show signs of danger"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "As a consequence, it often takes many years of regular water quality data collection to statistically ____ a trend.", "Opt_1": "eliminate", "Opt_2": "detect", "Opt_3": "adjust", "Opt_4": "terminate", "Answer": "detect", "Opt_1_def": "to dispose of", "Opt_2_def": "to see, find or notice", "Opt_3_def": "to change (often in order to make something work properly)", "Opt_4_def": "to finish or stop"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The student's answer may not address all parts of the question or may demonstrate an inaccurate or ____ analysis of the passage.", "Opt_1": "latter", "Opt_2": "immediate", "Opt_3": "mobile", "Opt_4": "superficial", "Answer": "superficial", "Opt_1_def": "the second of two things mentioned", "Opt_2_def": "first (without delay)", "Opt_3_def": "moving; able to move", "Opt_4_def": "done quickly and without enough thought; not thorough; trivial"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "One enjoyable way to improve in English is to do ____ of reading.", "Opt_1": "experience", "Opt_2": "record", "Opt_3": "performance", "Opt_4": "plenty", "Answer": "plenty", "Opt_1_def": "knowledge and skills gained over a long period of time", "Opt_2_def": "evidence; documentation", "Opt_3_def": "action or achievement", "Opt_4_def": "many, lots of"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "I'm not sure how to ____ any of these abstract terms, and yet I recognize some of the components of forgiveness.", "Opt_1": "recommend", "Opt_2": "define", "Opt_3": "qualify", "Opt_4": "survive", "Answer": "define", "Opt_1_def": "to suggest something to someone because it is good", "Opt_2_def": "to state what something is or means", "Opt_3_def": "to become eligible", "Opt_4_def": "to not die"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Results will be published in the ____ issue of the Canadian Journal of Fisheries and Aquatic Sciences.", "Opt_1": "forthcoming", "Opt_2": "intense", "Opt_3": "essential", "Opt_4": "physical", "Answer": "forthcoming", "Opt_1_def": "coming soon", "Opt_2_def": "strong, extreme", "Opt_3_def": "very important", "Opt_4_def": "of the body"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Mr. Elliott was at fault for delegating that function to a person who lacked the ____ to perform the job properly.", "Opt_1": "counsel", "Opt_2": "experience", "Opt_3": "decision", "Opt_4": "reply", "Answer": "experience", "Opt_1_def": "advice; advisor", "Opt_2_def": "knowledge and skills gained over a long period of time", "Opt_3_def": "intention to do something, choice", "Opt_4_def": "an answer"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The data is ____ as some analysts measure this figure according to different moments of the year, geographic regions and other variables.", "Opt_1": "ambiguous", "Opt_2": "infinite", "Opt_3": "elementary", "Opt_4": "economic", "Answer": "ambiguous", "Opt_1_def": "not clear; open to more than one interpretation", "Opt_2_def": "without an end", "Opt_3_def": "easy", "Opt_4_def": "financial; to do with money"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Be certain to answer the question in its entirety. Be certain to explain how and why you came to a ____ conclusion.", "Opt_1": "vague", "Opt_2": "unique", "Opt_3": "particular", "Opt_4": "broad", "Answer": "particular", "Opt_1_def": "not clear or strong", "Opt_2_def": "single, unusual, one of a kind", "Opt_3_def": "specific", "Opt_4_def": "wide, extensive"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The principle behind this policy is that the rights of the individuals should be respected; subjects must ____ to participation in research.", "Opt_1": "precede", "Opt_2": "consent", "Opt_3": "suppose", "Opt_4": "contemplate", "Answer": "consent", "Opt_1_def": "to go or be before someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "to agree", "Opt_3_def": "to think, imagine", "Opt_4_def": "to think about; to consider"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The two teams are ____ equal. It's difficult to predict who is going to win.", "Opt_1": "predominantly", "Opt_2": "roughly", "Opt_3": "thereby", "Opt_4": "gradually", "Answer": "roughly", "Opt_1_def": "mostly", "Opt_2_def": "about, approximately", "Opt_3_def": "by doing this", "Opt_4_def": "slowly; steadily"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The Commission was unable to estimate the cost of complying with new requirements ____ data recording.", "Opt_1": "despite", "Opt_2": "worth", "Opt_3": "beneath", "Opt_4": "regarding", "Answer": "regarding", "Opt_1_def": "although", "Opt_2_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_3_def": "below", "Opt_4_def": "about, concerning, with respect to"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The illegal downloading of music via the internet is ____ among young people.", "Opt_1": "widespread", "Opt_2": "tough", "Opt_3": "immediate", "Opt_4": "uniform", "Answer": "widespread", "Opt_1_def": "common", "Opt_2_def": "difficult, strong", "Opt_3_def": "first (without delay)", "Opt_4_def": "having the same qualities"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "It is an ____ for a politician to be able to give a clear but concise statement of what he or she believes in.", "Opt_1": "limit", "Opt_2": "credit", "Opt_3": "advantage", "Opt_4": "coincidence", "Answer": "advantage", "Opt_1_def": "extent, boundary", "Opt_2_def": "gained on completing a course of study; praise", "Opt_3_def": "benefit", "Opt_4_def": "an uncommon happening of two things"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "President Tom Gerety announced today that he will ____ on June 30, 2003, after nine years as the head of the college.", "Opt_1": "resign", "Opt_2": "entitle", "Opt_3": "collapse", "Opt_4": "deteriorate", "Answer": "resign", "Opt_1_def": "to give up (one's job)", "Opt_2_def": "to give the right to do something", "Opt_3_def": "to fall down completely and heavily; to fail", "Opt_4_def": "to get worse"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The B grade had come to signify work that was ____ acceptable.", "Opt_1": "generally", "Opt_2": "therefore", "Opt_3": "barely", "Opt_4": "roughly", "Answer": "barely", "Opt_1_def": "usually", "Opt_2_def": "so, as a result", "Opt_3_def": "not very much; hardly", "Opt_4_def": "about, approximately"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "A regular driving ____ does not entitle the ____ holder to drive a bus or a truck.", "Opt_1": "license", "Opt_2": "directions", "Opt_3": "theory", "Opt_4": "motive", "Answer": "license", "Opt_1_def": "permission to do something (often an official document)", "Opt_2_def": "instructions", "Opt_3_def": "idea or hypothesis", "Opt_4_def": "reason"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "He said that he did not want to discuss the issue until the ____ meeting.", "Opt_1": "diagram", "Opt_2": "transition", "Opt_3": "committee", "Opt_4": "level", "Answer": "committee", "Opt_1_def": "a type of picture or chart", "Opt_2_def": "a move from one (place, time, etc.) to another", "Opt_3_def": "a group of people meeting to discuss an issue", "Opt_4_def": "standard; layer; amount"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "We ____ the right to refuse alcohol service to anyone who cannot provide proper identification.", "Opt_1": "advise", "Opt_2": "blame", "Opt_3": "reserve", "Opt_4": "stress", "Answer": "reserve", "Opt_1_def": "to say what someone should do; to give advice", "Opt_2_def": "to accuse", "Opt_3_def": "to keep", "Opt_4_def": "to emphasize; to say what is important"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "How to increase employment and reduce crime are the two most serious problems that ____ the new government.", "Opt_1": "confront", "Opt_2": "circulate", "Opt_3": "distinguish", "Opt_4": "drain", "Answer": "confront", "Opt_1_def": "to deal with someone or something (often a problem or unpleasant situation)", "Opt_2_def": "to move from one place or person to another (often in a circle)", "Opt_3_def": "to make clear the differences between two things", "Opt_4_def": "to take away; to get rid of"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "This certificate program is a series of fully online courses that will show you how to ____ and deliver a quality course via the Internet.", "Opt_1": "range", "Opt_2": "remedy", "Opt_3": "design", "Opt_4": "battle", "Answer": "design", "Opt_1_def": "extent, distance between two points", "Opt_2_def": "cure (often for an illness)", "Opt_3_def": "planning (drawing)", "Opt_4_def": "fight, part of a war"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The suggestion is ____ not reasonable, and the department need not adopt it.", "Opt_1": "simply", "Opt_2": "gradually", "Opt_3": "respectively", "Opt_4": "therefore", "Answer": "therefore", "Opt_1_def": "completely; just; only", "Opt_2_def": "slowly; steadily", "Opt_3_def": "an expression used to refer to two things, one after the other", "Opt_4_def": "so, as a result"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "It has no alternative but to appeal to more sources and additional help from all those who are keen to ____ Palestinian education.", "Opt_1": "period", "Opt_2": "phenomenon", "Opt_3": "passage", "Opt_4": "support", "Answer": "support", "Opt_1_def": "a length of time (e.g. a lesson)", "Opt_2_def": "a happening (often unusual or unexpected)", "Opt_3_def": "a piece of written or spoken text", "Opt_4_def": "help"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "What we are really discussing is whether the industrialized countries can ____ the pensions promised by their respective governments.", "Opt_1": "remain", "Opt_2": "discern", "Opt_3": "overcome", "Opt_4": "afford", "Answer": "afford", "Opt_1_def": "to stay; still exist", "Opt_2_def": "to see; to perceive", "Opt_3_def": "to conquer, defeat", "Opt_4_def": "to be able to pay for something"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "So, what's the ____ of all this hindsight and what do we stand to gain from it?", "Opt_1": "supply", "Opt_2": "point", "Opt_3": "finance", "Opt_4": "extent", "Answer": "point", "Opt_1_def": "provision, store", "Opt_2_def": "purpose; reason; value", "Opt_3_def": "to do with money and payment", "Opt_4_def": "size, amount"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The requirements ____ to decrease family and individual student control over the transition process.", "Opt_1": "cancel", "Opt_2": "terminate", "Opt_3": "employ", "Opt_4": "threaten", "Answer": "threaten", "Opt_1_def": "to cut or stop from happening", "Opt_2_def": "to finish or stop", "Opt_3_def": "to give a job to someone; to use", "Opt_4_def": "to warn or show signs of danger"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Aschoff's trip failed because he was unable to defend his concept ____ the competitive approach favored by German and Russian scientists.", "Opt_1": "except", "Opt_2": "against", "Opt_3": "prior", "Opt_4": "among", "Answer": "against", "Opt_1_def": "but (not)", "Opt_2_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_3_def": "before", "Opt_4_def": "in, between"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "He has lost the ____ of being himself. Immigration laws have required him to pretend to be somebody else.", "Opt_1": "expense", "Opt_2": "guarantee", "Opt_3": "privilege", "Opt_4": "feature", "Answer": "privilege", "Opt_1_def": "cost", "Opt_2_def": "to promise or assure that something will or will not happen", "Opt_3_def": "a right (to do something)", "Opt_4_def": "part, aspect"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The easiest way to ____ documents in .pdf is by using the Adobe Acrobat software.", "Opt_1": "deserve", "Opt_2": "tend", "Opt_3": "refer", "Opt_4": "produce", "Answer": "produce", "Opt_1_def": "to have the right to something", "Opt_2_def": "to often behave in a certain way", "Opt_3_def": "to direct (attention) to; to mean", "Opt_4_def": "to make or create"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The Board will consider a leave for a President for a duration of ____ one month for each two years of service.", "Opt_1": "approximately", "Opt_2": "overly", "Opt_3": "eventually", "Opt_4": "simultaneously", "Answer": "approximately", "Opt_1_def": "about; not exactly", "Opt_2_def": "too", "Opt_3_def": "in the end", "Opt_4_def": "at the same time"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Many athletes who take ____ drugs risk serious, long-term damage to their health.", "Opt_1": "performance", "Opt_2": "prospect", "Opt_3": "context", "Opt_4": "support", "Answer": "performance", "Opt_1_def": "action or achievement", "Opt_2_def": "chance, likelihood", "Opt_3_def": "the place or situation in which something is found", "Opt_4_def": "help"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Sometimes it is difficult to find the ____ word to convey an idea. This is particularly true if you are speaking in your second language.", "Opt_1": "rapid", "Opt_2": "dense", "Opt_3": "exact", "Opt_4": "proper", "Answer": "exact", "Opt_1_def": "quick", "Opt_2_def": "thick; full; detailed", "Opt_3_def": "precise, opposite of approximate", "Opt_4_def": "correct, appropriate"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Since that time two major surveys were conducted with an attempt to define the ____ of the problem.", "Opt_1": "schedule", "Opt_2": "symptom", "Opt_3": "scope", "Opt_4": "dispute", "Answer": "scope", "Opt_1_def": "timetable", "Opt_2_def": "sign (often of a disease or other problem)", "Opt_3_def": "extent, range", "Opt_4_def": "argument; conflict"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Turkish law requires foreign scholars to obtain ____ permission to carry out research at institutions in Turkey.", "Opt_1": "immediate", "Opt_2": "formal", "Opt_3": "severe", "Opt_4": "serious", "Answer": "formal", "Opt_1_def": "first (without delay)", "Opt_2_def": "serious, not relaxed or everyday", "Opt_3_def": "serious, harsh", "Opt_4_def": "severe, large"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "In my ____ she is going to fail course unless she starts making more effort.", "Opt_1": "bulk", "Opt_2": "opinion", "Opt_3": "image", "Opt_4": "service", "Answer": "opinion", "Opt_1_def": "majority; largest part", "Opt_2_def": "view; what you think about someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "picture", "Opt_4_def": "work done for others; help"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "There is a ____ possibility that she will lose her job unless she becomes more reliable.", "Opt_1": "dense", "Opt_2": "classic", "Opt_3": "distinct", "Opt_4": "effective", "Answer": "distinct", "Opt_1_def": "thick; full; detailed", "Opt_2_def": "very good, the best or most used", "Opt_3_def": "clear and strong", "Opt_4_def": "good, working well"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "No other ____ has been used more often or by more college teachers than the Minute Paper.", "Opt_1": "technique", "Opt_2": "field", "Opt_3": "victory", "Opt_4": "objection", "Answer": "technique", "Opt_1_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_2_def": "area of interest or study", "Opt_3_def": "win", "Opt_4_def": "a statement of disagreement or disapproval"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Children like to ____ cars or buildings from plastic bricks.", "Opt_1": "fade", "Opt_2": "rotate", "Opt_3": "apply", "Opt_4": "construct", "Answer": "construct", "Opt_1_def": "to disappear slowly", "Opt_2_def": "to turn or move (around)", "Opt_3_def": "to be relevant (to)", "Opt_4_def": "to make"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The most important thing to keep in mind as you begin working on your assignments is that a philosophy paper is not an obstacle to be overcome but an ____ to show what you have learned.", "Opt_1": "region", "Opt_2": "opportunity", "Opt_3": "figure", "Opt_4": "committee", "Answer": "opportunity", "Opt_1_def": "part of a place", "Opt_2_def": "chance", "Opt_3_def": "number", "Opt_4_def": "a group of people meeting to discuss an issue"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The value of books would certainly degenerate if they could simply be produced and reproduced in cyberspace at an ____ minimal cost.", "Opt_1": "perhaps", "Opt_2": "naturally", "Opt_3": "respectively", "Opt_4": "extremely", "Answer": "extremely", "Opt_1_def": "maybe, possibly", "Opt_2_def": "of course, obviously", "Opt_3_def": "an expression used to refer to two things, one after the other", "Opt_4_def": "very"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "When morality comes up against profit, it is ____ profit that loses.", "Opt_1": "universally", "Opt_2": "seldom", "Opt_3": "gradually", "Opt_4": "greatly", "Answer": "seldom", "Opt_1_def": "all over the world; by everyone", "Opt_2_def": "rare", "Opt_3_def": "slowly; steadily", "Opt_4_def": "very much"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Rubin did not suffer ____ but learned to use anger and pride to fight for what was right.", "Opt_1": "pressure", "Opt_2": "profit", "Opt_3": "defeat", "Opt_4": "instruction", "Answer": "defeat", "Opt_1_def": "force; influence; stress", "Opt_2_def": "money gained", "Opt_3_def": "a loss (often in a battle or sports event)", "Opt_4_def": "advice or teaching how to do something; an order to do something"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The government predicts that oil prices will not ____ as much this year as last year.", "Opt_1": "education", "Opt_2": "vary", "Opt_3": "outcome", "Opt_4": "background", "Answer": "vary", "Opt_1_def": "schooling", "Opt_2_def": "to change or be different", "Opt_3_def": "result", "Opt_4_def": "family experiences; circumstances"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "If there is any question whether the individual might have a physical problem, the mental health professional should recommend a ____ examination.", "Opt_1": "complete", "Opt_2": "dynamic", "Opt_3": "ideal", "Opt_4": "considerable", "Answer": "complete", "Opt_1_def": "full or finished", "Opt_2_def": "changing; growing; energetic", "Opt_3_def": "best, optimal", "Opt_4_def": "very big; very much"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "I ____ my teacher for not preparing us properly for the test.", "Opt_1": "declare", "Opt_2": "absorb", "Opt_3": "contact", "Opt_4": "blame", "Answer": "blame", "Opt_1_def": "to state", "Opt_2_def": "to take in; to take up", "Opt_3_def": "to get in touch (e.g. by phone or email)", "Opt_4_def": "to accuse"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "One of the great problems in social ____s is that the ____ systems are not stable and are frequently subject to unpredictable change.", "Opt_1": "diverse", "Opt_2": "external", "Opt_3": "dynamic", "Opt_4": "temporary", "Answer": "dynamic", "Opt_1_def": "many and different", "Opt_2_def": "outside", "Opt_3_def": "changing; growing; energetic", "Opt_4_def": "for a short or limited time"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "He seems to be lacking the impulse to improve his ____ poor grades.", "Opt_1": "rather", "Opt_2": "virtually", "Opt_3": "predominantly", "Opt_4": "hence", "Answer": "rather", "Opt_1_def": "instead", "Opt_2_def": "almost", "Opt_3_def": "mostly", "Opt_4_def": "so, therefore"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The ____ of young men who walk around with large aggressive dogs is that they are from the working class and are criminals.", "Opt_1": "stereotype", "Opt_2": "circumstances", "Opt_3": "element", "Opt_4": "ratio", "Answer": "stereotype", "Opt_1_def": "a fixed idea about someone or something (often that is only partly true)", "Opt_2_def": "situation", "Opt_3_def": "aspect, part", "Opt_4_def": "mathematical relationship between two amount"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Monroe is a well-known ____ of the mechanical theory of education, with its cult of standardization, intelligence tests, etc.", "Opt_1": "exponent", "Opt_2": "career", "Opt_3": "ability", "Opt_4": "obligation", "Answer": "exponent", "Opt_1_def": "someone who holds and states an opinion", "Opt_2_def": "a long-term job", "Opt_3_def": "ableness to do something; a skill for doing something well", "Opt_4_def": "a requirement to do something"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Individuals are granted the use of the ____ on this website without written permission provided that all of the following conditions are met.", "Opt_1": "hierarchy", "Opt_2": "motive", "Opt_3": "theory", "Opt_4": "materials", "Answer": "materials", "Opt_1_def": "organizational structure (e.g. showing who works for whom)", "Opt_2_def": "reason", "Opt_3_def": "idea or hypothesis", "Opt_4_def": "the things you need to do something"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The documentation must ____ of a comprehensive, typed report that states a specific, current diagnosis.", "Opt_1": "reward", "Opt_2": "suppress", "Opt_3": "modify", "Opt_4": "consist", "Answer": "consist", "Opt_1_def": "to give something (e.g. a prize) for good work or behaviour", "Opt_2_def": "to hold back; to not allow to happen", "Opt_3_def": "to change", "Opt_4_def": "to have in it; to have as part of it"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "You will ____ many difficulties but if you persist in your efforts, you will succeed.", "Opt_1": "subsidize", "Opt_2": "ensure", "Opt_3": "annotate", "Opt_4": "encounter", "Answer": "encounter", "Opt_1_def": "to support financially", "Opt_2_def": "to make sure (of)", "Opt_3_def": "to make notes on a piece of writing", "Opt_4_def": "to meet or experience"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Every 10 years the government carries out a ____ survey of all households in the country. This is called a census.", "Opt_1": "official", "Opt_2": "current", "Opt_3": "final", "Opt_4": "apart", "Answer": "official", "Opt_1_def": "approved by an authority", "Opt_2_def": "happening now", "Opt_3_def": "last", "Opt_4_def": "not together, separate"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "It seems probable that precise measurements of the ratio of positive to negative responses will help to decide between the ____ processes.", "Opt_1": "several", "Opt_2": "odd", "Opt_3": "elaborate", "Opt_4": "minor", "Answer": "several", "Opt_1_def": "many (about 6 or seven)", "Opt_2_def": "strange, unusual", "Opt_3_def": "detailed; complex", "Opt_4_def": "small, not important"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "These questions are meant to help you research the background information you will need to evaluate some of the water ____ issues in NYC.", "Opt_1": "fallacy", "Opt_2": "state", "Opt_3": "quality", "Opt_4": "deed", "Answer": "quality", "Opt_1_def": "mistake; false belief", "Opt_2_def": "condition, situation", "Opt_3_def": "worth or value", "Opt_4_def": "an action"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "While we were not ____ surprised by the answers to our questions, it was interesting to see the amount of uniformity in answers.", "Opt_1": "dramatically", "Opt_2": "somewhat", "Opt_3": "simultaneously", "Opt_4": "overly", "Answer": "overly", "Opt_1_def": "very strongly, significantly", "Opt_2_def": "quite, rather", "Opt_3_def": "at the same time", "Opt_4_def": "too"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "After 11 years at the helm of the Scientific Computing Division, Bill Buzbee recently announced his ____ to retire at the end of this year.", "Opt_1": "impulse", "Opt_2": "responsibility", "Opt_3": "intention", "Opt_4": "detriment", "Answer": "intention", "Opt_1_def": "reason or motivation to do something", "Opt_2_def": "job, duty to do something", "Opt_3_def": "plan, aim", "Opt_4_def": "disadvantage"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The ____ cause of the accident is that the driver fell asleep, but police are investigating the possibility of a terrorist attack.", "Opt_1": "slight", "Opt_2": "original", "Opt_3": "straightforward", "Opt_4": "probable", "Answer": "probable", "Opt_1_def": "small", "Opt_2_def": "the first of its kind", "Opt_3_def": "easy", "Opt_4_def": "it is not probable that any thing better will be discovered than what was known to our fathers."}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Mechanisms by which comfrey can ____ the liver are unclear, but the main injury appears to be destruction of small veins, leading to cirrhosis.", "Opt_1": "blame", "Opt_2": "train", "Opt_3": "ruin", "Opt_4": "accuse", "Answer": "ruin", "Opt_1_def": "to accuse", "Opt_2_def": "to teach someone how to do a job", "Opt_3_def": "to spoil or damage", "Opt_4_def": "to blame"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "How to increase employment and reduce crime are the two most serious problems that ____ the new government.", "Opt_1": "illuminate", "Opt_2": "evolve", "Opt_3": "eliminate", "Opt_4": "confront", "Answer": "confront", "Opt_1_def": "to show clearly; to light up", "Opt_2_def": "to develop (into something better)", "Opt_3_def": "to dispose of", "Opt_4_def": "to deal with someone or something (often a problem or unpleasant situation)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "If you look carefully, you will ____ that the ice is starting to melt.", "Opt_1": "prosper", "Opt_2": "perceive", "Opt_3": "cooperate", "Opt_4": "warn", "Answer": "perceive", "Opt_1_def": "to do well; to become rich", "Opt_2_def": "to see; to become aware of with one of the senses; to think", "Opt_3_def": "to work (well) with another person", "Opt_4_def": "to notify (of possible danger)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "I experienced her as a very ____ teacher who had empathy for her students.", "Opt_1": "competent", "Opt_2": "rational", "Opt_3": "sound", "Opt_4": "spontaneous", "Answer": "competent", "Opt_1_def": "good at something (often a job)", "Opt_2_def": "base on reason, not on emotion or instinct", "Opt_3_def": "good; strong", "Opt_4_def": "happening without warning or planning"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "When questioned by the instructor, the student was unable to ____ several of the terms and phrases he had used in his writing.", "Opt_1": "remain", "Opt_2": "offend", "Opt_3": "assume", "Opt_4": "explain", "Answer": "explain", "Opt_1_def": "to stay; still exist", "Opt_2_def": "to go against; to upset", "Opt_3_def": "to believe to be true; to presume or predict", "Opt_4_def": "to give the reason for something or say how to do something"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "A major ____ in his success was his willingness to work very hard.", "Opt_1": "factor", "Opt_2": "conflict", "Opt_3": "counsel", "Opt_4": "privilege", "Answer": "factor", "Opt_1_def": "an aspect to be considered", "Opt_2_def": "problem, struggle or battle", "Opt_3_def": "advice; advisor", "Opt_4_def": "a right (to do something)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "English may be a ____ language but it is not yet a proper tool for exploring most of the world's societies and cultures.", "Opt_1": "global", "Opt_2": "vague", "Opt_3": "vast", "Opt_4": "evident", "Answer": "global", "Opt_1_def": "world", "Opt_2_def": "not clear or strong", "Opt_3_def": "very large", "Opt_4_def": "clear"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "It is not always possible to ____ a cause of a conflict from a consequence of that conflict.", "Opt_1": "compile", "Opt_2": "distinguish", "Opt_3": "adapt", "Opt_4": "acknowledge", "Answer": "distinguish", "Opt_1_def": "to put together (often in a list", "Opt_2_def": "to make clear the differences between two things", "Opt_3_def": "to change (often in response to a changed situation)", "Opt_4_def": "to agree with; admit to; give credit to"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The outcome of the ____ remains very much in doubt.", "Opt_1": "cause", "Opt_2": "priority", "Opt_3": "record", "Opt_4": "conflict", "Answer": "conflict", "Opt_1_def": "the reason why something happens", "Opt_2_def": "first and most important task", "Opt_3_def": "evidence; documentation", "Opt_4_def": "problem, struggle or battle"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The project itself may grow out of ____ work, but it must comprise achievement that is over and above regular ____ activities.", "Opt_1": "course", "Opt_2": "justice", "Opt_3": "trait", "Opt_4": "desire", "Answer": "course", "Opt_1_def": "a subject or period of study", "Opt_2_def": "fairness in law", "Opt_3_def": "characteristic; aspect", "Opt_4_def": "a want or wish for something"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "A student should declare a Literature ____ by the first semester of his or her junior year.", "Opt_1": "minor", "Opt_2": "compulsory", "Opt_3": "frequent", "Opt_4": "severe", "Answer": "minor", "Opt_1_def": "small, not important", "Opt_2_def": "required, must be done", "Opt_3_def": "often", "Opt_4_def": "serious, harsh"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The school ____ it impossible to fulfill its promise to reduce tuition fees.", "Opt_1": "mention", "Opt_2": "commit", "Opt_3": "master", "Opt_4": "found", "Answer": "found", "Opt_1_def": "to say; state", "Opt_2_def": "to do (often an offense)", "Opt_3_def": "to (gain) control", "Opt_4_def": "to begin (often an organization)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "No matter how good the lawyer's intuition and ability to express himself or herself, the lawyer will not ____ unless he or she can analyze logically.", "Opt_1": "succeed", "Opt_2": "offend", "Opt_3": "deserve", "Opt_4": "subsidize", "Answer": "succeed", "Opt_1_def": "to do well", "Opt_2_def": "to go against; to upset", "Opt_3_def": "to have the right to something", "Opt_4_def": "to support financially"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "We hoped to find relevant data on why ____ people donate time and money and others don't.", "Opt_1": "certain", "Opt_2": "poor", "Opt_3": "various", "Opt_4": "straightforward", "Answer": "certain", "Opt_1_def": "sure", "Opt_2_def": "bad, unsatisfactory", "Opt_3_def": "several, of different kinds", "Opt_4_def": "easy"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "It must have been about this time that Stalin took the most extraordinary decision of his career in order to ____ his political survival.", "Opt_1": "conform", "Opt_2": "confine", "Opt_3": "expel", "Opt_4": "assure", "Answer": "assure", "Opt_1_def": "to do what is required", "Opt_2_def": "to limit", "Opt_3_def": "to drive or push out", "Opt_4_def": "to make sure; to say that something will certainly happen"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The library is going to ____ a new electronic system for checking out books.", "Opt_1": "assert", "Opt_2": "introduce", "Opt_3": "ensure", "Opt_4": "contemplate", "Answer": "introduce", "Opt_1_def": "to claim, to say strongly", "Opt_2_def": "to talk about or bring in for the first time", "Opt_3_def": "to make sure (of)", "Opt_4_def": "to think about; to consider"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Once Grace Albee arrived in New York City in 1933, she was able to dedicate herself to full-time printmaking and her art began to ____ serious national attention.", "Opt_1": "command", "Opt_2": "magnitude", "Opt_3": "access", "Opt_4": "concern", "Answer": "command", "Opt_1_def": "control", "Opt_2_def": "size; amount", "Opt_3_def": "the right to enter or use", "Opt_4_def": "worry, fear"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Web sites such as Wikipedia certainly ____ the finding of information, although not all of it is reliable.", "Opt_1": "annotate", "Opt_2": "allege", "Opt_3": "facilitate", "Opt_4": "assemble", "Answer": "facilitate", "Opt_1_def": "to make notes on a piece of writing", "Opt_2_def": "to claim or state", "Opt_3_def": "to make something easier", "Opt_4_def": "to get, put or bring together"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Over 100 students marched to the Hoover Institution to ____ a possible U.S. war in Iraq.", "Opt_1": "protest", "Opt_2": "dispose", "Opt_3": "enter", "Opt_4": "omit", "Answer": "protest", "Opt_1_def": "to express anger or unhappiness about something", "Opt_2_def": "to get rid of", "Opt_3_def": "to go in or put in", "Opt_4_def": "to leave something out or not do something"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Specifically, you ____ that you were not provided with academic adjustments and auxiliary aids, and were not provided access to other services and programs at the College.", "Opt_1": "review", "Opt_2": "incorporate", "Opt_3": "allege", "Opt_4": "violate", "Answer": "allege", "Opt_1_def": "to check over (and make changes)", "Opt_2_def": "to include", "Opt_3_def": "to claim or state", "Opt_4_def": "to spoil or break"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The meeting will ____ at 8.30.", "Opt_1": "consult", "Opt_2": "commence", "Opt_3": "request", "Opt_4": "promote", "Answer": "commence", "Opt_1_def": "to get the advice of someone ( often an expert)", "Opt_2_def": "to start", "Opt_3_def": "to ask politely", "Opt_4_def": "to encourage; to raise to a higher position in a job"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Two thirds of the ____ of the earth are covered with water.", "Opt_1": "vary", "Opt_2": "limit", "Opt_3": "comparison", "Opt_4": "surface", "Answer": "surface", "Opt_1_def": "to change or be different", "Opt_2_def": "extent, boundary", "Opt_3_def": "a statement of how two things are similar or different", "Opt_4_def": "the outside layer of an object"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "He did not ____ to one set of religious beliefs and pioneered a new artistic style known today as symbolism.", "Opt_1": "replace", "Opt_2": "abuse", "Opt_3": "confirm", "Opt_4": "adhere", "Answer": "adhere", "Opt_1_def": "to put in or take the place of ..", "Opt_2_def": "to treat someone or something badly", "Opt_3_def": "to agree that something is correct", "Opt_4_def": "to keep to; to follow"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "San Francisco's justice reform program is ____ alive, says a UC Berkeley report.", "Opt_1": "naturally", "Opt_2": "nevertheless", "Opt_3": "barely", "Opt_4": "merely", "Answer": "barely", "Opt_1_def": "of course, obviously", "Opt_2_def": "however (although / despite that)", "Opt_3_def": "not very much; hardly", "Opt_4_def": "only, just, simply"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "It is a ____ to think that you can put off working until the week before the exam and still pass it.", "Opt_1": "experiment", "Opt_2": "expense", "Opt_3": "influence", "Opt_4": "fallacy", "Answer": "fallacy", "Opt_1_def": "test", "Opt_2_def": "cost", "Opt_3_def": "effect", "Opt_4_def": "mistake; false belief"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "When you finish unit 1, please do the questions and then ____ to unit 3. You don't need to do unit 2.", "Opt_1": "enter", "Opt_2": "persuade", "Opt_3": "proceed", "Opt_4": "deny", "Answer": "proceed", "Opt_1_def": "to go in or put in", "Opt_2_def": "to try and make someone do something or agree to something", "Opt_3_def": "to go forward (and do ..)", "Opt_4_def": "to refuse ( responsibility for doing or saying something); to say that something is not correct"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The older population of the U.S. and the world is growing rapidly, and these large numbers will represent a major ____ for society in general.", "Opt_1": "affair", "Opt_2": "challenge", "Opt_3": "operation", "Opt_4": "loss", "Answer": "challenge", "Opt_1_def": "an event or series of events", "Opt_2_def": "difficult situation; problem", "Opt_3_def": "procedure; happening; process", "Opt_4_def": "removal or reduction"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The grade will be amended but the ____ grade will remain on the record with an appropriate notation.", "Opt_1": "former", "Opt_2": "deliberate", "Opt_3": "brief", "Opt_4": "reasonable", "Answer": "former", "Opt_1_def": "previous, the one before, the first of two", "Opt_2_def": "intentional, not by accident", "Opt_3_def": "short", "Opt_4_def": "acceptable, quite good"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Sometimes it is difficult to find the ____ word to convey an idea. This is particularly true if you are speaking in your second language.", "Opt_1": "similar", "Opt_2": "complex", "Opt_3": "exact", "Opt_4": "compatible", "Answer": "exact", "Opt_1_def": "like, almost the same as", "Opt_2_def": "difficult, complicated", "Opt_3_def": "precise, opposite of approximate", "Opt_4_def": "able to work with someone or something else"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "When faculty members assign an Incomplete grade they must ____ the work required.", "Opt_1": "forego", "Opt_2": "transmit", "Opt_3": "appeal", "Opt_4": "specify", "Answer": "specify", "Opt_1_def": "to do without; to give up", "Opt_2_def": "to send or convey", "Opt_3_def": "to complain against an official judgment; to make a strong request", "Opt_4_def": "to state exactly"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "This is a highly subjective view of the symbolic nature of ____ reality.", "Opt_1": "physical", "Opt_2": "suitable", "Opt_3": "genuine", "Opt_4": "several", "Answer": "physical", "Opt_1_def": "of the body", "Opt_2_def": "good for a particular job or purpose", "Opt_3_def": "real and authentic", "Opt_4_def": "many (about 6 or seven)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "A snowstorm failed to ____ soccer practice on the Inlet early last week.", "Opt_1": "interrupt", "Opt_2": "correspond", "Opt_3": "illustrate", "Opt_4": "analyze", "Answer": "interrupt", "Opt_1_def": "to stop something from happening", "Opt_2_def": "to be related to", "Opt_3_def": "to show; to make clear", "Opt_4_def": "to look at something in detail in order to understand it"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The university advises female students to follow their ____ whether it is safe to accept a ride home from a man they have just met.", "Opt_1": "remedy", "Opt_2": "authority", "Opt_3": "phenomenon", "Opt_4": "instinct", "Answer": "instinct", "Opt_1_def": "cure (often for an illness)", "Opt_2_def": "control (right to control)", "Opt_3_def": "a happening (often unusual or unexpected)", "Opt_4_def": "natural feeling or reaction"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Lack of sufficient ____ often prohibits sound management activities that are necessary to the company's long-term health and stability.", "Opt_1": "treatment", "Opt_2": "revenue", "Opt_3": "sequence", "Opt_4": "service", "Answer": "revenue", "Opt_1_def": "way of handing a person, situation or problem (often of illness)", "Opt_2_def": "money, income", "Opt_3_def": "the order in which things are arranged or happen", "Opt_4_def": "work done for others; help"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "This ____ provides a quick and extremely simple way to collect written feedback on student learning.", "Opt_1": "stage", "Opt_2": "technique", "Opt_3": "amount", "Opt_4": "influence", "Answer": "technique", "Opt_1_def": "period of time, part of a process", "Opt_2_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_3_def": "how much there is of something", "Opt_4_def": "effect"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "But, for their part, the Syrian leaders failed to ____ for Israel to have rights to some of that water.", "Opt_1": "accompany", "Opt_2": "negotiate", "Opt_3": "measure", "Opt_4": "contact", "Answer": "negotiate", "Opt_1_def": "to go with someone or something; to exist together", "Opt_2_def": "to discuss (usually in politics or business)", "Opt_3_def": "to find out how much there is of something", "Opt_4_def": "to get in touch (e.g. by phone or email)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The ____ of blue agave (agave azul) cactus in Mexico has gone from one extreme to another during the past several years.", "Opt_1": "institution", "Opt_2": "situation", "Opt_3": "community", "Opt_4": "supply", "Answer": "supply", "Opt_1_def": "a large organization; an important system or custom", "Opt_2_def": "circumstances", "Opt_3_def": "a group of people", "Opt_4_def": "provision, store"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The interpretation fits well with the fact that his ____ health did not deteriorate.", "Opt_1": "mental", "Opt_2": "efficient", "Opt_3": "characteristic", "Opt_4": "broad", "Answer": "mental", "Opt_1_def": "of the brain or mind", "Opt_2_def": "working quickly and easily", "Opt_3_def": "typical", "Opt_4_def": "wide, extensive"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "It takes a lot of training to ____ the skills in professions such as car mechanics or cooking.", "Opt_1": "enhance", "Opt_2": "respect", "Opt_3": "master", "Opt_4": "announce", "Answer": "master", "Opt_1_def": "to make something better", "Opt_2_def": "to think positively about someone; to tolerate or avoid interfering with something", "Opt_3_def": "to (gain) control", "Opt_4_def": "to state (often in an official way)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The geographer urges upon his students that they first master those principles and then consider the ____ problems.", "Opt_1": "drastic", "Opt_2": "fundamental", "Opt_3": "urban", "Opt_4": "subsequent", "Answer": "subsequent", "Opt_1_def": "severe; great", "Opt_2_def": "very important", "Opt_3_def": "of the town or city", "Opt_4_def": "next, following"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "She is so ____ in German class. It's no wonder that she can hardly speak a word of the language.", "Opt_1": "suitable", "Opt_2": "annual", "Opt_3": "passive", "Opt_4": "identical", "Answer": "passive", "Opt_1_def": "good for a particular job or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "yearly", "Opt_3_def": "not active; unresponsive", "Opt_4_def": "exactly the same"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "To launch the project, a special event will ____ at Stanford University's Center for Design Research at 11am today.", "Opt_1": "commence", "Opt_2": "prevent", "Opt_3": "transfer", "Opt_4": "provoke", "Answer": "commence", "Opt_1_def": "to start", "Opt_2_def": "to stop from doing or happening", "Opt_3_def": "to move to a different place or job", "Opt_4_def": "to cause to happen"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Blair will need to persuade the Americans that Europeans will no longer ____ Saddam to play games with the inspectors.", "Opt_1": "permit", "Opt_2": "contradict", "Opt_3": "protect", "Opt_4": "measure", "Answer": "permit", "Opt_1_def": "to allow", "Opt_2_def": "to say or show that what someone has said is wrong", "Opt_3_def": "to keep something out of danger", "Opt_4_def": "to find out how much there is of something"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The government failed to understand why the people were so unhappy with its policies, and ____ was voted out at the next election.", "Opt_1": "thus", "Opt_2": "hardly", "Opt_3": "namely", "Opt_4": "fairly", "Answer": "thus", "Opt_1_def": "so", "Opt_2_def": "not very much", "Opt_3_def": "specifically, that is to say ( .. used to list or explain)", "Opt_4_def": "quite, somewhat"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "A ____ example of ambiguity is the sentence: \"I do not like visiting aunts.\"", "Opt_1": "current", "Opt_2": "classic", "Opt_3": "bold", "Opt_4": "global", "Answer": "classic", "Opt_1_def": "happening now", "Opt_2_def": "very good, the best or most used", "Opt_3_def": "brave", "Opt_4_def": "world"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "I ____ we are going to have a test on this. - You are right!", "Opt_1": "suppose", "Opt_2": "condemn", "Opt_3": "announce", "Opt_4": "neglect", "Answer": "suppose", "Opt_1_def": "to think, imagine", "Opt_2_def": "to express strong disapproval", "Opt_3_def": "to state (often in an official way)", "Opt_4_def": "to not think about or care for"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "President Tom Gerety announced today that he will ____ on June 30, 2003, after nine years as the head of the college.", "Opt_1": "resign", "Opt_2": "analyze", "Opt_3": "request", "Opt_4": "attempt", "Answer": "resign", "Opt_1_def": "to give up (one's job)", "Opt_2_def": "to look at something in detail in order to understand it", "Opt_3_def": "to ask politely", "Opt_4_def": "to try"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The weather ____ warned people to stay at home in case the storm got even worse.", "Opt_1": "forecast", "Opt_2": "reluctance", "Opt_3": "directions", "Opt_4": "justice", "Answer": "forecast", "Opt_1_def": "prediction", "Opt_2_def": "unwillingness; hesitation", "Opt_3_def": "instructions", "Opt_4_def": "fairness in law"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The former is preferable for a field of inquiry that is still in its infancy, whereas the ____ is suitable for fields that have a developed theory.", "Opt_1": "authentic", "Opt_2": "final", "Opt_3": "latter", "Opt_4": "likely", "Answer": "latter", "Opt_1_def": "real, genuine; not made-up or artificial", "Opt_2_def": "last", "Opt_3_def": "the second of two things mentioned", "Opt_4_def": "probable"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The final topic presents the impact of traditional, sometimes outdated, teaching methods and their ____ on the participants' learning.", "Opt_1": "effort", "Opt_2": "effect", "Opt_3": "attack", "Opt_4": "statistic", "Answer": "effect", "Opt_1_def": "hard work; attempt", "Opt_2_def": "result", "Opt_3_def": "to criticize; to attempt to harm or damage", "Opt_4_def": "mathematical number"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "So maybe people who see media studies as too general, too loose, too intellectually ____ have a point.", "Opt_1": "vague", "Opt_2": "ultimate", "Opt_3": "rigid", "Opt_4": "legitimate", "Answer": "vague", "Opt_1_def": "not clear or strong", "Opt_2_def": "final or most important", "Opt_3_def": "strict, unbending", "Opt_4_def": "correct; allowed"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "You can take any book ____ this one. I'm reading it.", "Opt_1": "except", "Opt_2": "beneath", "Opt_3": "due", "Opt_4": "regarding", "Answer": "except", "Opt_1_def": "but (not)", "Opt_2_def": "below", "Opt_3_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_4_def": "about, concerning, with respect to"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Various approaches to environmental ____ are discussed, along with steps in the planning process when citizen involvement is particularly effective.", "Opt_1": "commodity", "Opt_2": "sphere", "Opt_3": "justice", "Opt_4": "delay", "Answer": "justice", "Opt_1_def": "a product; something you can buy", "Opt_2_def": "area of interest", "Opt_3_def": "fairness in law", "Opt_4_def": "lateness"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "If the number of sections to be taught does not ____ to the number of students, you need to explain the reason.", "Opt_1": "blame", "Opt_2": "correspond", "Opt_3": "shrink", "Opt_4": "label", "Answer": "correspond", "Opt_1_def": "to accuse", "Opt_2_def": "to be related to", "Opt_3_def": "to get smaller", "Opt_4_def": "to give a name to someone or something"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "To ____ for the credit, fuel cells are required to be 500 watt capacity or greater with a generation efficiency of 30% or greater.", "Opt_1": "confront", "Opt_2": "qualify", "Opt_3": "speculate", "Opt_4": "raise", "Answer": "qualify", "Opt_1_def": "to deal with someone or something (often a problem or unpleasant situation)", "Opt_2_def": "to become eligible", "Opt_3_def": "to think and talk about (often future events)", "Opt_4_def": "to lift; to make higher"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "If you wish to contribute material that is copyrighted by someone ____ yourself, then you will need to document that the copyright holder has agreed.", "Opt_1": "regarding", "Opt_2": "besides", "Opt_3": "worth", "Opt_4": "except", "Answer": "besides", "Opt_1_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_2_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_3_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_4_def": "but (not)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The new version of Microsoft's Internet Explorer lets you ____ pictures by using the mouse ball and the Control key.", "Opt_1": "lessen", "Opt_2": "condemn", "Opt_3": "obey", "Opt_4": "magnify", "Answer": "magnify", "Opt_1_def": "to reduce", "Opt_2_def": "to express strong disapproval", "Opt_3_def": "to do as commanded or expected", "Opt_4_def": "to make or show larger"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The use of gender- ____ language may seem unnecessary to some writers, but the consistent use of masculine pronouns leaves the impression that women could not be among the group to which the writer is referring.", "Opt_1": "compulsory", "Opt_2": "invisible", "Opt_3": "neutral", "Opt_4": "faint", "Answer": "neutral", "Opt_1_def": "required, must be done", "Opt_2_def": "cannot be seen", "Opt_3_def": "neither for nor against; neither positive nor negative", "Opt_4_def": "not strong"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Aycock stated that he had looked over the horse before the purchase and did not ____ any marks indicating that the horse had been cut.", "Opt_1": "observe", "Opt_2": "discern", "Opt_3": "reward", "Opt_4": "hesitate", "Answer": "observe", "Opt_1_def": "to watch carefully", "Opt_2_def": "to see; to perceive", "Opt_3_def": "to give something (e.g. a prize) for good work or behaviour", "Opt_4_def": "to pause before saying or doing something"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The percentage of online adults who say they ____ ever or never search for health information has dropped to 39 percent.", "Opt_1": "indeed", "Opt_2": "nevertheless", "Opt_3": "hardly", "Opt_4": "furthermore", "Answer": "hardly", "Opt_1_def": "used in confirmation or emphasis; really", "Opt_2_def": "however (although / despite that)", "Opt_3_def": "not very much", "Opt_4_def": "also, in addition"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The ____ is not a sufficient reward for the excellence and hard work of this faculty and staff.", "Opt_1": "grant", "Opt_2": "province", "Opt_3": "hierarchy", "Opt_4": "code", "Answer": "grant", "Opt_1_def": "a sum of money given to a person or organization", "Opt_2_def": "area (of interest)", "Opt_3_def": "organizational structure (e.g. showing who works for whom)", "Opt_4_def": "a set of rules"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "I found a ____ of her homework on the cafeteria. It looked like half the school had stepped on it!", "Opt_1": "rank", "Opt_2": "credit", "Opt_3": "comment", "Opt_4": "fragment", "Answer": "fragment", "Opt_1_def": "position (in a list or hierarchy)", "Opt_2_def": "gained on completing a course of study; praise", "Opt_3_def": "a short written or spoken statement or opinion", "Opt_4_def": "part of something"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "His examination failure did not occur through lack of effort or ____ but because of serious illness in the weeks before.", "Opt_1": "growth", "Opt_2": "duration", "Opt_3": "ability", "Opt_4": "purpose", "Answer": "ability", "Opt_1_def": "development, increase", "Opt_2_def": "period of time", "Opt_3_def": "ableness to do something; a skill for doing something well", "Opt_4_def": "reason, goal"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The machine did not work properly because the person installing it did not ____ the instructions.", "Opt_1": "obey", "Opt_2": "address", "Opt_3": "launch", "Opt_4": "amend", "Answer": "obey", "Opt_1_def": "to do as commanded or expected", "Opt_2_def": "to give attention to (an issue)", "Opt_3_def": "to begin", "Opt_4_def": "to change (usually to improve something)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The former assumes a single step - that life originated on Earth - ahead of the more ____ idea that life formed elsewhere and was subsequently transported to Earth.", "Opt_1": "trivial", "Opt_2": "logical", "Opt_3": "elaborate", "Opt_4": "reliable", "Answer": "elaborate", "Opt_1_def": "not important", "Opt_2_def": "making sense", "Opt_3_def": "detailed; complex", "Opt_4_def": "can be trusted, does not let you down \r\n"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Without a filter on perceptual input, our brains would have the impossible task of sifting through an overload of information to ____ important from unimportant information.", "Opt_1": "force", "Opt_2": "precede", "Opt_3": "comprehend", "Opt_4": "separate", "Answer": "separate", "Opt_1_def": "to make happen or to make someone do something", "Opt_2_def": "to go or be before someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "to understand", "Opt_4_def": "to pull or put apart"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Doctors ____ people to restrict the number of eggs they eat to 2-3 per week.", "Opt_1": "negotiate", "Opt_2": "advise", "Opt_3": "stipulate", "Opt_4": "dictate", "Answer": "advise", "Opt_1_def": "to discuss (usually in politics or business)", "Opt_2_def": "to say what someone should do; to give advice", "Opt_3_def": "to require", "Opt_4_def": "to tell someone what to do"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "There is land ____ the ice in Antarctica, but water ____ it at the North Pole.", "Opt_1": "despite", "Opt_2": "except", "Opt_3": "instead", "Opt_4": "beneath", "Answer": "beneath", "Opt_1_def": "although", "Opt_2_def": "but (not)", "Opt_3_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_4_def": "below"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "You should write this again to ____ all the irrelevant details.", "Opt_1": "decision", "Opt_2": "record", "Opt_3": "extract", "Opt_4": "error", "Answer": "extract", "Opt_1_def": "intention to do something, choice", "Opt_2_def": "evidence; documentation", "Opt_3_def": "to remove; to take out and use", "Opt_4_def": "a mistake"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Describe the study in detail sufficient to convince the reviewer that the problem is ____ investigation.", "Opt_1": "regarding", "Opt_2": "worth", "Opt_3": "beneath", "Opt_4": "among", "Answer": "worth", "Opt_1_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_2_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_3_def": "below", "Opt_4_def": "in, between"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "For some people the ____ characteristics of a website are more important than its content.", "Opt_1": "deliberate", "Opt_2": "dense", "Opt_3": "visual", "Opt_4": "spare", "Answer": "visual", "Opt_1_def": "intentional, not by accident", "Opt_2_def": "thick; full; detailed", "Opt_3_def": "to do with sight and seeing", "Opt_4_def": "not needed"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The government surely cannot fail to ____ that its attempts to reduce teenage pregnancy are not working.", "Opt_1": "inform", "Opt_2": "notice", "Opt_3": "prefer", "Opt_4": "prepare", "Answer": "notice", "Opt_1_def": "to say, give information", "Opt_2_def": "to see or realize", "Opt_3_def": "to like better", "Opt_4_def": "to get something ready (or to get ready for something)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Even though you may know your housemates well, you should always take the ____ to lock the door. Windows should also be secured.", "Opt_1": "precaution", "Opt_2": "event", "Opt_3": "income", "Opt_4": "instinct", "Answer": "precaution", "Opt_1_def": "something done to avoid danger, harm or problems", "Opt_2_def": "a happening", "Opt_3_def": "money earned", "Opt_4_def": "natural feeling or reaction"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The new team coach is an ____ of the view: No pain, no gain!", "Opt_1": "implication", "Opt_2": "exponent", "Opt_3": "programme", "Opt_4": "theory", "Answer": "exponent", "Opt_1_def": "result or consequence", "Opt_2_def": "someone who holds and states an opinion", "Opt_3_def": "a course of lessons; a project", "Opt_4_def": "idea or hypothesis"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "For the purposes of this study, then, increasing the testing strength did not ____ more accurate results.", "Opt_1": "edit", "Opt_2": "yield", "Opt_3": "terminate", "Opt_4": "remove", "Answer": "yield", "Opt_1_def": "to make changes in a piece of writing", "Opt_2_def": "to produce", "Opt_3_def": "to finish or stop", "Opt_4_def": "to take away"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The construction of new facilities is an ____ for any university to make a clear statement about its environmental concern.", "Opt_1": "impact", "Opt_2": "status", "Opt_3": "opportunity", "Opt_4": "limit", "Answer": "opportunity", "Opt_1_def": "effect", "Opt_2_def": "position, standing", "Opt_3_def": "chance", "Opt_4_def": "extent, boundary"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "People might be surprised to know that a similar ____ had occurred in the US and that doctors and hospitals were allowed to override the family's wishes.", "Opt_1": "individual", "Opt_2": "duration", "Opt_3": "trace", "Opt_4": "situation", "Answer": "situation", "Opt_1_def": "one person", "Opt_2_def": "period of time", "Opt_3_def": "sign; indication; evidence", "Opt_4_def": "circumstances"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "All campus party noise must ____ by 12:00 Midnight.", "Opt_1": "organize", "Opt_2": "diminish", "Opt_3": "cease", "Opt_4": "arise", "Answer": "cease", "Opt_1_def": "to put into (its proper) place", "Opt_2_def": "to get smaller or less important", "Opt_3_def": "to stop", "Opt_4_def": "to happen"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Alumni have expressed much ____ reaction to the Alumni Association's recent initiatives to expand its use of electronic newsletters and its Web site.", "Opt_1": "automatic", "Opt_2": "frequent", "Opt_3": "positive", "Opt_4": "ultimate", "Answer": "positive", "Opt_1_def": "happening by itself; happening naturally or usually", "Opt_2_def": "often", "Opt_3_def": "good; optimistic", "Opt_4_def": "final or most important"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The government has become unpopular recently and is ____ to lose the coming election.", "Opt_1": "principal", "Opt_2": "liable", "Opt_3": "various", "Opt_4": "dynamic", "Answer": "liable", "Opt_1_def": "most important", "Opt_2_def": "likely to happen; at risk of happening", "Opt_3_def": "several, of different kinds", "Opt_4_def": "changing; growing; energetic"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "I believe police agencies have no right to ____ who can or cannot own guns.", "Opt_1": "prevent", "Opt_2": "ensure", "Opt_3": "trust", "Opt_4": "determine", "Answer": "determine", "Opt_1_def": "to stop from doing or happening", "Opt_2_def": "to make sure (of)", "Opt_3_def": "to believe that someone or something will be or work as promised", "Opt_4_def": "to find out; to establish or identify; state"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Some people ____ that the growth of the internet has been to the detriment of students' ability and willingness to read.", "Opt_1": "afford", "Opt_2": "invest", "Opt_3": "speculate", "Opt_4": "claim", "Answer": "claim", "Opt_1_def": "to be able to pay for something", "Opt_2_def": "to put money into something", "Opt_3_def": "to think and talk about (often future events)", "Opt_4_def": "to state to be true"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "There seemed to be no ____ of coping with the war debts that were overwhelming both nation and states.", "Opt_1": "function", "Opt_2": "prospect", "Opt_3": "record", "Opt_4": "choice", "Answer": "prospect", "Opt_1_def": "job or role", "Opt_2_def": "chance, likelihood", "Opt_3_def": "evidence; documentation", "Opt_4_def": "decision, selection"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Discussion and analysis in this area has covered a number of ____ issues, including the effect of shifting trade patterns on employment levels.", "Opt_1": "discrete", "Opt_2": "likely", "Opt_3": "vague", "Opt_4": "identical", "Answer": "discrete", "Opt_1_def": "separate", "Opt_2_def": "probable", "Opt_3_def": "not clear or strong", "Opt_4_def": "exactly the same"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "She said she initially had planned to ____ earlier, but that she postponed her departure because of pressing issues at the hospital.", "Opt_1": "reserve", "Opt_2": "retire", "Opt_3": "deliver", "Opt_4": "rotate", "Answer": "retire", "Opt_1_def": "to keep", "Opt_2_def": "to stop working", "Opt_3_def": "to provide (often by bringing to people)", "Opt_4_def": "to turn or move (around)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The powerful hold that the empire of Egypt had on Palestine at this time would not have permitted the rise of a significant ____ such as Israel.", "Opt_1": "cause", "Opt_2": "asset", "Opt_3": "sum", "Opt_4": "entity", "Answer": "entity", "Opt_1_def": "the reason why something happens", "Opt_2_def": "advantage", "Opt_3_def": "an amount of money, total", "Opt_4_def": "thing; body; organization"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "This we know: the earth does not ____ to man, man ____s to the earth.", "Opt_1": "perceive", "Opt_2": "belong", "Opt_3": "transform", "Opt_4": "decrease", "Answer": "belong", "Opt_1_def": "to see; to become aware of with one of the senses; to think", "Opt_2_def": "to be part of something or owned by someone", "Opt_3_def": "to change (often completely)", "Opt_4_def": "to get smaller, to go down"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The government has set up a committee to ____ why more young people have started smoking in the last few years.", "Opt_1": "resign", "Opt_2": "protest", "Opt_3": "broadcast", "Opt_4": "inquire", "Answer": "inquire", "Opt_1_def": "to give up (one's job)", "Opt_2_def": "to express anger or unhappiness about something", "Opt_3_def": "to tell or transmit (often by means of a television programme)", "Opt_4_def": "to ask"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Begin your paper with a brief description of the storyline, or a brief ____ from it, that suggests or illustrates your thesis.", "Opt_1": "evidence", "Opt_2": "episode", "Opt_3": "relationship", "Opt_4": "crisis", "Answer": "episode", "Opt_1_def": "proof, signs", "Opt_2_def": "period of time", "Opt_3_def": "the way to things are connected", "Opt_4_def": "very dangerous situation, catastrophe"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The government has taken the ____ decision to consult the public before passing the proposed law.", "Opt_1": "wise", "Opt_2": "subtle", "Opt_3": "optional", "Opt_4": "secure", "Answer": "wise", "Opt_1_def": "intelligent; sensible", "Opt_2_def": "not clear or strong", "Opt_3_def": "not necessary or compulsory; can do it if you want", "Opt_4_def": "safe"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "This is NOT a reliable ____ and you should simply ignore it.", "Opt_1": "staff", "Opt_2": "majority", "Opt_3": "statistic", "Opt_4": "sphere", "Answer": "statistic", "Opt_1_def": "people working at a particular place (particularly an office or school)", "Opt_2_def": "more than 50%", "Opt_3_def": "mathematical number", "Opt_4_def": "area of interest"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "These budgets must be very carefully designed as it is extremely difficult, if not impossible, to ____ the amount of the award once it has been granted.", "Opt_1": "exert", "Opt_2": "oppose", "Opt_3": "alter", "Opt_4": "manipulate", "Answer": "alter", "Opt_1_def": "to use", "Opt_2_def": "to be against or fight against something", "Opt_3_def": "to change", "Opt_4_def": "to (use and) change"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The probable ____ of the accident is that the driver fell asleep, but police are investigating the possibility of a terrorist attack.", "Opt_1": "proportion", "Opt_2": "survey", "Opt_3": "range", "Opt_4": "cause", "Answer": "cause", "Opt_1_def": "amount; number; percentage", "Opt_2_def": "questionnaire; information gained by questioning people or data", "Opt_3_def": "extent, distance between two points", "Opt_4_def": "the reason why something happens"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The ____ is to find the right mixture of materials that will result in the creation of clear electrical signals.", "Opt_1": "commodity", "Opt_2": "display", "Opt_3": "record", "Opt_4": "objective", "Answer": "objective", "Opt_1_def": "a product; something you can buy", "Opt_2_def": "a show, demonstration, illustration", "Opt_3_def": "evidence; documentation", "Opt_4_def": "aim or goal"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Each College or School should ____ the teaching of basic technology skills at the earliest level possible.", "Opt_1": "allege", "Opt_2": "tend", "Opt_3": "inquire", "Opt_4": "integrate", "Answer": "integrate", "Opt_1_def": "to claim or state", "Opt_2_def": "to often behave in a certain way", "Opt_3_def": "to ask", "Opt_4_def": "to fit into a new situation"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "For example, in many manufacturing processes several nominally rigid bodies undergo multiple, concurrent, ____ frictional contacts.", "Opt_1": "adequate", "Opt_2": "explicit", "Opt_3": "arbitrary", "Opt_4": "dynamic", "Answer": "dynamic", "Opt_1_def": "good enough; ok", "Opt_2_def": "clearly and openly expressed", "Opt_3_def": "not planned or thought-out; not considering the wishes of others", "Opt_4_def": "changing; growing; energetic"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Many people believe that the invasion of Iraq was a ____ mistake.", "Opt_1": "fundamental", "Opt_2": "inherent", "Opt_3": "medium", "Opt_4": "latter", "Answer": "fundamental", "Opt_1_def": "very important", "Opt_2_def": "part of; a fundamental characteristic of", "Opt_3_def": "in the middle", "Opt_4_def": "the second of two things mentioned"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "If you are in constant pain you should ____ a doctor.", "Opt_1": "consult", "Opt_2": "infer", "Opt_3": "possess", "Opt_4": "improve", "Answer": "consult", "Opt_1_def": "to get the advice of someone ( often an expert)", "Opt_2_def": "to come to a conclusion about something", "Opt_3_def": "to have or own", "Opt_4_def": "to get better"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Vehicles that do not display a valid parking ____ will be towed immediately.", "Opt_1": "train", "Opt_2": "permit", "Opt_3": "identify", "Opt_4": "evolve", "Answer": "permit", "Opt_1_def": "to teach someone how to do a job", "Opt_2_def": "to allow", "Opt_3_def": "to know or say who or what something is", "Opt_4_def": "to develop (into something better)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "In his view, the Empire was less a place where England exerted ____ than where it lost command of its own identity.", "Opt_1": "control", "Opt_2": "analyze", "Opt_3": "encourage", "Opt_4": "measure", "Answer": "control", "Opt_1_def": "to have and exercise power over something or someone", "Opt_2_def": "to look at something in detail in order to understand it", "Opt_3_def": "to move someone to do something by positive talk; support or help", "Opt_4_def": "to find out how much there is of something"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "I ____ to believe that the quality of my thinking has not diminished; I simply have chosen a different format to express my ideas.", "Opt_1": "prefer", "Opt_2": "yield", "Opt_3": "restrict", "Opt_4": "threaten", "Answer": "prefer", "Opt_1_def": "to like better", "Opt_2_def": "to produce", "Opt_3_def": "to limit", "Opt_4_def": "to warn or show signs of danger"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Now ____ that a box contains one fair coin and one coin with a head on each side.", "Opt_1": "clarify", "Opt_2": "remove", "Opt_3": "interfere", "Opt_4": "suppose", "Answer": "suppose", "Opt_1_def": "to make something clear, explain", "Opt_2_def": "to take away", "Opt_3_def": "to prevent; to harm", "Opt_4_def": "to think, imagine"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "A respect for other cultures is ____ in the philosophy of our international school.", "Opt_1": "unique", "Opt_2": "numerous", "Opt_3": "inherent", "Opt_4": "superficial", "Answer": "inherent", "Opt_1_def": "single, unusual, one of a kind", "Opt_2_def": "very many", "Opt_3_def": "part of; a fundamental characteristic of", "Opt_4_def": "done quickly and without enough thought; not thorough; trivial"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The Iraqi regime failed to take that final opportunity to ____ with the United Nations investigation.", "Opt_1": "assert", "Opt_2": "cooperate", "Opt_3": "insert", "Opt_4": "request", "Answer": "cooperate", "Opt_1_def": "to claim, to say strongly", "Opt_2_def": "to work (well) with another person", "Opt_3_def": "to put in", "Opt_4_def": "to ask politely"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Global warming and polar melting ____ to raise water levels and thus flood low-lying cities.", "Opt_1": "possess", "Opt_2": "contain", "Opt_3": "threaten", "Opt_4": "encounter", "Answer": "threaten", "Opt_1_def": "to have or own", "Opt_2_def": "to have in it; to hold inside", "Opt_3_def": "to warn or show signs of danger", "Opt_4_def": "to meet or experience"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "There is a very clear ____ in the school for expelling students who do not follow the rules.", "Opt_1": "demand", "Opt_2": "mechanism", "Opt_3": "commodity", "Opt_4": "topic", "Answer": "mechanism", "Opt_1_def": "a need or desire for", "Opt_2_def": "procedure, process", "Opt_3_def": "a product; something you can buy", "Opt_4_def": "area of interest or discussion"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "If we want to maintain ____ for an open and dynamic economy, our programs need to become as flexible and adaptable as the economy itself.", "Opt_1": "minimum", "Opt_2": "power", "Opt_3": "theory", "Opt_4": "support", "Answer": "support", "Opt_1_def": "the smallest amount; the least", "Opt_2_def": "the right or authority to do something", "Opt_3_def": "idea or hypothesis", "Opt_4_def": "help"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Individual investors: ____ with caution.", "Opt_1": "deviate", "Opt_2": "proceed", "Opt_3": "behave", "Opt_4": "reform", "Answer": "proceed", "Opt_1_def": "to be different", "Opt_2_def": "to go forward (and do ..)", "Opt_3_def": "to act or do things in a certain way", "Opt_4_def": "to change and improve"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The Morningside Heights area in New York is a ____ example of what Jacobs feels should not be done for city rebuilding.", "Opt_1": "suitable", "Opt_2": "prime", "Opt_3": "broad", "Opt_4": "adequate", "Answer": "prime", "Opt_1_def": "good for a particular job or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "most important", "Opt_3_def": "wide, extensive", "Opt_4_def": "good enough; ok"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "This is yet another ____ example of the positive partnership between TMH and the FSU College of Medicine.", "Opt_1": "tough", "Opt_2": "outstanding", "Opt_3": "characteristic", "Opt_4": "significant", "Answer": "outstanding", "Opt_1_def": "difficult, strong", "Opt_2_def": "excellent", "Opt_3_def": "typical", "Opt_4_def": "important, large"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "In order to make up a missed exam, you must produce written evidence within 48 hours of the exam which shows that you had a ____ reason to do so.", "Opt_1": "serious", "Opt_2": "legitimate", "Opt_3": "brief", "Opt_4": "main", "Answer": "legitimate", "Opt_1_def": "severe, large", "Opt_2_def": "correct; allowed", "Opt_3_def": "short", "Opt_4_def": "most important"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Does anyone really believe that governments will ____ tax incomes on trillions of dollars of e-commerce sales?", "Opt_1": "accumulate", "Opt_2": "contemplate", "Opt_3": "forego", "Opt_4": "associate", "Answer": "forego", "Opt_1_def": "to grow; to gather together", "Opt_2_def": "to think about; to consider", "Opt_3_def": "to do without; to give up", "Opt_4_def": "to link to; to make a connection to"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Questioning the values of parents is ____ in being a teenager.", "Opt_1": "superficial", "Opt_2": "authentic", "Opt_3": "inherent", "Opt_4": "remote", "Answer": "inherent", "Opt_1_def": "done quickly and without enough thought; not thorough; trivial", "Opt_2_def": "real, genuine; not made-up or artificial", "Opt_3_def": "part of; a fundamental characteristic of", "Opt_4_def": "far, distant, small"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "For example, in many manufacturing processes ____ nominally rigid bodies undergo multiple, concurrent, dynamic frictional contacts.", "Opt_1": "military", "Opt_2": "several", "Opt_3": "forthcoming", "Opt_4": "automatic", "Answer": "several", "Opt_1_def": "to do with army", "Opt_2_def": "many (about 6 or seven)", "Opt_3_def": "coming soon", "Opt_4_def": "happening by itself; happening naturally or usually"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "In this way, Cohen embodies the ____ student and model citizen; he speaks up when he perceives injustice regardless of the consequences.", "Opt_1": "ideal", "Opt_2": "physical", "Opt_3": "urban", "Opt_4": "distinct", "Answer": "ideal", "Opt_1_def": "best, optimal", "Opt_2_def": "of the body", "Opt_3_def": "of the town or city", "Opt_4_def": "clear and strong"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Some countries, such as Switzerland, remained ____ in the last world war.", "Opt_1": "instant", "Opt_2": "prime", "Opt_3": "neutral", "Opt_4": "suitable", "Answer": "neutral", "Opt_1_def": "immediate", "Opt_2_def": "most important", "Opt_3_def": "neither for nor against; neither positive nor negative", "Opt_4_def": "good for a particular job or purpose"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "It is predicted that Off-campus study programs will shrink ____ to the problematic financial situation.", "Opt_1": "beyond", "Opt_2": "despite", "Opt_3": "due", "Opt_4": "among", "Answer": "due", "Opt_1_def": "further than: past", "Opt_2_def": "although", "Opt_3_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_4_def": "in, between"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "A great deal of discussion focused on observations which could solve the mystery by testing the predictions of the ____ hypotheses.", "Opt_1": "liable", "Opt_2": "stable", "Opt_3": "various", "Opt_4": "comprehensive", "Answer": "various", "Opt_1_def": "likely to happen; at risk of happening", "Opt_2_def": "not changing; not easy to change", "Opt_3_def": "several, of different kinds", "Opt_4_def": "full, complete"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "It is common knowledge that credit cards are a temporary solution that can snowball into a ____ problem.", "Opt_1": "mental", "Opt_2": "abstract", "Opt_3": "visual", "Opt_4": "permanent", "Answer": "permanent", "Opt_1_def": "of the brain or mind", "Opt_2_def": "not specific or concrete", "Opt_3_def": "to do with sight and seeing", "Opt_4_def": "lasting for ever or for a very long time"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "As a child, he began to stutter severely and, ____ the best efforts of his teachers and parents, he was unable to overcome it.", "Opt_1": "among", "Opt_2": "instead", "Opt_3": "beyond", "Opt_4": "despite", "Answer": "despite", "Opt_1_def": "in, between", "Opt_2_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_3_def": "further than: past", "Opt_4_def": "although"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The district of most big cities around the main ____ station is often a dangerous place to be at night.", "Opt_1": "notice", "Opt_2": "train", "Opt_3": "verify", "Opt_4": "attach", "Answer": "train", "Opt_1_def": "to see or realize", "Opt_2_def": "to teach someone how to do a job", "Opt_3_def": "to prove or claim the truth", "Opt_4_def": "to put together with"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "To achieve this goal, planning must apply the best ____ scientific information and analysis.", "Opt_1": "available", "Opt_2": "current", "Opt_3": "competent", "Opt_4": "global", "Answer": "available", "Opt_1_def": "can be had (bought or obtained)", "Opt_2_def": "happening now", "Opt_3_def": "good at something (often a job)", "Opt_4_def": "world"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Many people buy ____ vitamin pills because they do not believe that they get enough vitamins from their regular food.", "Opt_1": "supplementary", "Opt_2": "widespread", "Opt_3": "convenient", "Opt_4": "feasible", "Answer": "supplementary", "Opt_1_def": "extra; additional", "Opt_2_def": "common", "Opt_3_def": "easy, not causing problems", "Opt_4_def": "possible"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "A new ____ of skin replaces the damaged skin during healing.", "Opt_1": "sample", "Opt_2": "habit", "Opt_3": "layer", "Opt_4": "forecast", "Answer": "layer", "Opt_1_def": "example; a smaller number of a larger collection", "Opt_2_def": "something you do regularly", "Opt_3_def": "level", "Opt_4_def": "prediction"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Some information is collected on our ____ by outside agencies in order to provide services to our visitors.", "Opt_1": "behalf", "Opt_2": "career", "Opt_3": "minimum", "Opt_4": "support", "Answer": "behalf", "Opt_1_def": "as a representative of; for the benefit of", "Opt_2_def": "a long-term job", "Opt_3_def": "the smallest amount; the least", "Opt_4_def": "help"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The students ____ that I promised to show a DVD on in class today, but I cannot remember doing so.", "Opt_1": "assert", "Opt_2": "earn", "Opt_3": "produce", "Opt_4": "protest", "Answer": "assert", "Opt_1_def": "to claim, to say strongly", "Opt_2_def": "to get money or another reward (usually by working for it)", "Opt_3_def": "to make or create", "Opt_4_def": "to express anger or unhappiness about something"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Matilda Thurston considered who was the most logical architect to ____ a proper campus for 200 students.", "Opt_1": "design", "Opt_2": "surface", "Opt_3": "liberty", "Opt_4": "rank", "Answer": "design", "Opt_1_def": "planning (drawing)", "Opt_2_def": "the outside layer of an object", "Opt_3_def": "freedom", "Opt_4_def": "position (in a list or hierarchy)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The lessons that ____ lunch today are cancelled for a special assembly.", "Opt_1": "criticize", "Opt_2": "yield", "Opt_3": "precede", "Opt_4": "observe", "Answer": "precede", "Opt_1_def": "to express disapproval; to say what you don't like or think is good about something or someone", "Opt_2_def": "to produce", "Opt_3_def": "to go or be before someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "to watch carefully"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Storage of personal information not related to university business must be limited and must not ____ in any way with the storage and maintenance of university data.", "Opt_1": "oppose", "Opt_2": "presume", "Opt_3": "demonstrate", "Opt_4": "interfere", "Answer": "interfere", "Opt_1_def": "to be against or fight against something", "Opt_2_def": "to believe, assume", "Opt_3_def": "to show", "Opt_4_def": "to prevent; to harm"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "I have no intention of being a teacher when I leave school. I want to ____ more money!", "Opt_1": "assure", "Opt_2": "arrange", "Opt_3": "formulate", "Opt_4": "earn", "Answer": "earn", "Opt_1_def": "to make sure; to say that something will certainly happen", "Opt_2_def": "to plan to happen; to group together", "Opt_3_def": "to express", "Opt_4_def": "to get money or another reward (usually by working for it)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The manager has decided form a ____ to investigate the recent increase in theft from the storeroom.", "Opt_1": "phenomenon", "Opt_2": "region", "Opt_3": "insight", "Opt_4": "committee", "Answer": "committee", "Opt_1_def": "a happening (often unusual or unexpected)", "Opt_2_def": "part of a place", "Opt_3_def": "understanding (often of a complex problem)", "Opt_4_def": "a group of people meeting to discuss an issue"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Dr. Carpenter told the jury that Hinckley was unable to ____ reality from fiction.", "Opt_1": "anticipate", "Opt_2": "facilitate", "Opt_3": "separate", "Opt_4": "confront", "Answer": "separate", "Opt_1_def": "to expect", "Opt_2_def": "to make something easier", "Opt_3_def": "to pull or put apart", "Opt_4_def": "to deal with someone or something (often a problem or unpleasant situation)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "One of the great problems in social dynamics is that the dynamic systems are not ____ and are frequently subject to unpredictable change.", "Opt_1": "cautious", "Opt_2": "stable", "Opt_3": "infinite", "Opt_4": "spare", "Answer": "stable", "Opt_1_def": "careful", "Opt_2_def": "not changing; not easy to change", "Opt_3_def": "without an end", "Opt_4_def": "not needed"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Some people think that the ____ way to stop people smoking is to raise the price of cigarettes sky-high.", "Opt_1": "minor", "Opt_2": "stable", "Opt_3": "comprehensive", "Opt_4": "ideal", "Answer": "ideal", "Opt_1_def": "small, not important", "Opt_2_def": "not changing; not easy to change", "Opt_3_def": "full, complete", "Opt_4_def": "best, optimal"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Here is a good ____ to get paid for conducting undergraduate research at UH through its Summer Research Program.", "Opt_1": "error", "Opt_2": "opportunity", "Opt_3": "summary", "Opt_4": "theory", "Answer": "opportunity", "Opt_1_def": "a mistake", "Opt_2_def": "chance", "Opt_3_def": "a short account of the most important details", "Opt_4_def": "idea or hypothesis"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Problem behaviors were found to be ____ to drinking practices.", "Opt_1": "former", "Opt_2": "related", "Opt_3": "eligible", "Opt_4": "cautious", "Answer": "related", "Opt_1_def": "previous, the one before, the first of two", "Opt_2_def": "connected; having something to do with each other", "Opt_3_def": "being entitled or qualified to do something", "Opt_4_def": "careful"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The teacher made the ____ decision to take her class out to the playground and finish the lesson there.", "Opt_1": "spontaneous", "Opt_2": "apart", "Opt_3": "novel", "Opt_4": "reasonable", "Answer": "spontaneous", "Opt_1_def": "happening without warning or planning", "Opt_2_def": "not together, separate", "Opt_3_def": "new", "Opt_4_def": "acceptable, quite good"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "A three-year Indian bachelor's ____ is NOT equivalent to a U.S. bachelor's ____.", "Opt_1": "degree", "Opt_2": "version", "Opt_3": "influence", "Opt_4": "assent", "Answer": "degree", "Opt_1_def": "amount", "Opt_2_def": "form", "Opt_3_def": "effect", "Opt_4_def": "agreement"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "I believe police agencies have no right to ____ who can or cannot own guns.", "Opt_1": "earn", "Opt_2": "determine", "Opt_3": "suggest", "Opt_4": "join", "Answer": "determine", "Opt_1_def": "to get money or another reward (usually by working for it)", "Opt_2_def": "to find out; to establish or identify; state", "Opt_3_def": "to say an idea; to recommend", "Opt_4_def": "to become a member (of an organization; to get together with others"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "That was not a very ____ thing to do.", "Opt_1": "efficient", "Opt_2": "authentic", "Opt_3": "wise", "Opt_4": "profound", "Answer": "wise", "Opt_1_def": "working quickly and easily", "Opt_2_def": "real, genuine; not made-up or artificial", "Opt_3_def": "intelligent; sensible", "Opt_4_def": "deep; great; serious"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "An even number multiplied by an odd number will always ____ an even number.", "Opt_1": "cover", "Opt_2": "yield", "Opt_3": "review", "Opt_4": "stipulate", "Answer": "yield", "Opt_1_def": "to do; to complete", "Opt_2_def": "to produce", "Opt_3_def": "to check over (and make changes)", "Opt_4_def": "to require"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "What do western Louisville and the Appalachian region have in common ____ being two of the poorest areas in Kentucky?", "Opt_1": "regarding", "Opt_2": "beyond", "Opt_3": "among", "Opt_4": "besides", "Answer": "besides", "Opt_1_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_2_def": "further than: past", "Opt_3_def": "in, between", "Opt_4_def": "in addition to; as well as"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "There are very few people living today who were born ____ to the first world war.", "Opt_1": "besides", "Opt_2": "prior", "Opt_3": "worth", "Opt_4": "except", "Answer": "prior", "Opt_1_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_2_def": "before", "Opt_3_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_4_def": "but (not)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Try to communicate that the process is more important than the answer so that the student learns that it is OK to not have an ____ solution.", "Opt_1": "instant", "Opt_2": "commercial", "Opt_3": "compulsory", "Opt_4": "poor", "Answer": "instant", "Opt_1_def": "immediate", "Opt_2_def": "to do with business", "Opt_3_def": "required, must be done", "Opt_4_def": "bad, unsatisfactory"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "There was not the tradition of going to school; it was expected that you'd go to work and ____ to the family.", "Opt_1": "exploit", "Opt_2": "ruin", "Opt_3": "contribute", "Opt_4": "fare", "Answer": "contribute", "Opt_1_def": "to use (sometimes in a negative way)", "Opt_2_def": "to spoil or damage", "Opt_3_def": "to give (for example: money, help or ideas); to play a part in", "Opt_4_def": "to do or succeed"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Burning of coal is a ____ way to obtain energy, but it creates a serious amount of pollution.", "Opt_1": "genuine", "Opt_2": "technical", "Opt_3": "numerous", "Opt_4": "convenient", "Answer": "convenient", "Opt_1_def": "real and authentic", "Opt_2_def": "to do with machines or the way things work", "Opt_3_def": "very many", "Opt_4_def": "easy, not causing problems"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "I do not wish to ____ that she is lazy, but her work is often late and of poor quality.", "Opt_1": "depend", "Opt_2": "encounter", "Opt_3": "negotiate", "Opt_4": "imply", "Answer": "imply", "Opt_1_def": "be influenced (by)", "Opt_2_def": "to meet or experience", "Opt_3_def": "to discuss (usually in politics or business)", "Opt_4_def": "to mean; to give to understand"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "This project will culminate in a ____ research essay of 2000 words.", "Opt_1": "voluntary", "Opt_2": "intrinsic", "Opt_3": "major", "Opt_4": "positive", "Answer": "major", "Opt_1_def": "done freely; from personal choice", "Opt_2_def": "belonging to; inherent in", "Opt_3_def": "important, large", "Opt_4_def": "good; optimistic"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The company yesterday said it made a ____ of \ufffd\ufffd217.46 million for the six months to June.", "Opt_1": "format", "Opt_2": "profit", "Opt_3": "category", "Opt_4": "fund", "Answer": "profit", "Opt_1_def": "appearance, layout, way of presenting", "Opt_2_def": "money gained", "Opt_3_def": "group of similar items", "Opt_4_def": "money collected for a particular purpose"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The self-hatred that this ____ inflicted led the children to attempt to wash their skin white with scouring powder.", "Opt_1": "administration", "Opt_2": "prejudice", "Opt_3": "rate", "Opt_4": "display", "Answer": "prejudice", "Opt_1_def": "the people responsible for running an organization such as the government or a school", "Opt_2_def": "bias, discrimination, beliefs or feelings influenced by one's own background", "Opt_3_def": "quantity; proportion; speed", "Opt_4_def": "a show, demonstration, illustration"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "FLO plays the key ____ as an agent for ethically sensitive consumers.", "Opt_1": "role", "Opt_2": "priority", "Opt_3": "license", "Opt_4": "materials", "Answer": "role", "Opt_1_def": "job or function", "Opt_2_def": "first and most important task", "Opt_3_def": "permission to do something (often an official document)", "Opt_4_def": "the things you need to do something"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "He has only ____ control of basic verb grammar. He quite often chooses the wrong tense or forgets the -s ending.", "Opt_1": "pure", "Opt_2": "external", "Opt_3": "strict", "Opt_4": "loose", "Answer": "loose", "Opt_1_def": "complete, 100%", "Opt_2_def": "outside", "Opt_3_def": "hard, not changeable", "Opt_4_def": "not firm or finished"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "It is my firm intention to ____ with my department for at least two years.", "Opt_1": "remain", "Opt_2": "train", "Opt_3": "submit", "Opt_4": "produce", "Answer": "remain", "Opt_1_def": "to stay; still exist", "Opt_2_def": "to teach someone how to do a job", "Opt_3_def": "to give; to send", "Opt_4_def": "to make or create"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "He has only a ____ knowledge of English grammar - not enough to be an ESL teacher.", "Opt_1": "typical", "Opt_2": "abnormal", "Opt_3": "superficial", "Opt_4": "comprehensive", "Answer": "superficial", "Opt_1_def": "usual", "Opt_2_def": "not normal, unusual", "Opt_3_def": "done quickly and without enough thought; not thorough; trivial", "Opt_4_def": "full, complete"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "No matter how good the lawyer's intuition and ability to express himself or herself, the lawyer will not succeed unless he or she can ____ logically.", "Opt_1": "analyze", "Opt_2": "reduce", "Opt_3": "persuade", "Opt_4": "notice", "Answer": "analyze", "Opt_1_def": "to look at something in detail in order to understand it", "Opt_2_def": "to make smaller or shorter", "Opt_3_def": "to try and make someone do something or agree to something", "Opt_4_def": "to see or realize"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Are you ____ of the fact that you may fail the course?", "Opt_1": "arbitrary", "Opt_2": "conscious", "Opt_3": "flexible", "Opt_4": "official", "Answer": "conscious", "Opt_1_def": "not planned or thought-out; not considering the wishes of others", "Opt_2_def": "aware, knowing", "Opt_3_def": "can be changed or bent", "Opt_4_def": "approved by an authority"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Internet businesses will only be successful if they use the ____ of clear, easy, cheap, safe shopping.", "Opt_1": "result", "Opt_2": "event", "Opt_3": "formula", "Opt_4": "contract", "Answer": "formula", "Opt_1_def": "outcome, effect", "Opt_2_def": "a happening", "Opt_3_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_4_def": "a written agreement, binding in law"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Imagine being surrounded by hundreds of people who are ____ convinced you can do anything.", "Opt_1": "especially", "Opt_2": "absolutely", "Opt_3": "hence", "Opt_4": "definitely", "Answer": "absolutely", "Opt_1_def": "particularly", "Opt_2_def": "completely; 100%", "Opt_3_def": "so, therefore", "Opt_4_def": "certainly; without doubt"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "I am ____ that you will do well in the examinations.", "Opt_1": "domestic", "Opt_2": "brief", "Opt_3": "reasonable", "Opt_4": "confident", "Answer": "confident", "Opt_1_def": "home", "Opt_2_def": "short", "Opt_3_def": "acceptable, quite good", "Opt_4_def": "sure that something will happen"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The ____ was unclear. It had been hand-drawn and then copied using weak ink.", "Opt_1": "evidence", "Opt_2": "diagram", "Opt_3": "asset", "Opt_4": "exhibit", "Answer": "diagram", "Opt_1_def": "proof, signs", "Opt_2_def": "a type of picture or chart", "Opt_3_def": "advantage", "Opt_4_def": "to show"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "More than 70 percent of the surveyed firms said that the lack of housing was not a ____ on their ability to expand.", "Opt_1": "formula", "Opt_2": "authority", "Opt_3": "belief", "Opt_4": "constraint", "Answer": "constraint", "Opt_1_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_2_def": "control (right to control)", "Opt_3_def": "what you think; what you believe in", "Opt_4_def": "to hold back; to prevent"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Mathematics course: Students will read aloud ____ problems in class and state the meaning in their own words.", "Opt_1": "elementary", "Opt_2": "subsequent", "Opt_3": "ordinary", "Opt_4": "verbal", "Answer": "verbal", "Opt_1_def": "easy", "Opt_2_def": "next, following", "Opt_3_def": "usual, typical, every day", "Opt_4_def": "to do with words and language (especially the spoken language)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "I don't believe that the government's plan to imprison more criminals is the best ____ for the problem of rising crime.", "Opt_1": "behalf", "Opt_2": "extract", "Opt_3": "remedy", "Opt_4": "contract", "Answer": "remedy", "Opt_1_def": "as a representative of; for the benefit of", "Opt_2_def": "to remove; to take out and use", "Opt_3_def": "cure (often for an illness)", "Opt_4_def": "a written agreement, binding in law"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The temperature curve shows that the increase was not ____ with time; a fact which could hardly be expected and is also not observed on other continents.", "Opt_1": "basic", "Opt_2": "adequate", "Opt_3": "steady", "Opt_4": "common", "Answer": "steady", "Opt_1_def": "first or easy", "Opt_2_def": "good enough; ok", "Opt_3_def": "gradual; without interruptions; firm", "Opt_4_def": "often seen or happening"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The government looks likely to succeed in its ____ to reduce child poverty by the end of the decade.", "Opt_1": "objective", "Opt_2": "purpose", "Opt_3": "tool", "Opt_4": "command", "Answer": "objective", "Opt_1_def": "aim or goal", "Opt_2_def": "reason, goal", "Opt_3_def": "something used to do a job", "Opt_4_def": "control"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Due to the severe shortage of highly trained nursing staff, Hopkins was unable to ____ a full team of qualified personnel.", "Opt_1": "presume", "Opt_2": "assemble", "Opt_3": "conserve", "Opt_4": "prepare", "Answer": "assemble", "Opt_1_def": "to believe, assume", "Opt_2_def": "to get, put or bring together", "Opt_3_def": "to preserve; to not use", "Opt_4_def": "to get something ready (or to get ready for something)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The ____ was first observed in 1911 by Onnes, who noted that the resistance of a frozen mercury rod abruptly dropped to zero.", "Opt_1": "attribute", "Opt_2": "phrase", "Opt_3": "shift", "Opt_4": "phenomenon", "Answer": "phenomenon", "Opt_1_def": "characteristic; property", "Opt_2_def": "one achieves best success through constantly applied pressure.", "Opt_3_def": "change", "Opt_4_def": "a happening (often unusual or unexpected)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The ____ is the most common teaching style at university. There is not so much question and answer as in schools.", "Opt_1": "lecture", "Opt_2": "influence", "Opt_3": "privilege", "Opt_4": "battle", "Answer": "lecture", "Opt_1_def": "a talk on a particular subject; talk criticizing unacceptable behaviour", "Opt_2_def": "effect", "Opt_3_def": "a right (to do something)", "Opt_4_def": "fight, part of a war"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Abortion is not a fundamental right; it can be limited if the ____ wishes.", "Opt_1": "compensation", "Opt_2": "detail", "Opt_3": "scheme", "Opt_4": "state", "Answer": "state", "Opt_1_def": "money (or some other reward) given to someone who has suffered a loss or injustice", "Opt_2_def": "a small piece of information", "Opt_3_def": "plan. idea, project", "Opt_4_def": "condition, situation"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Describe the study in detail sufficient to ____ the reviewer that the problem is worth investigation.", "Opt_1": "label", "Opt_2": "suspect", "Opt_3": "convince", "Opt_4": "lessen", "Answer": "convince", "Opt_1_def": "to give a name to someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "to believe", "Opt_3_def": "to (try and) get someone to believe something", "Opt_4_def": "to reduce"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "This may ____ relationships between children and parents, and necessitate the involvement of child welfare services.", "Opt_1": "appoint", "Opt_2": "suppose", "Opt_3": "strain", "Opt_4": "protect", "Answer": "strain", "Opt_1_def": "to give a job to someone", "Opt_2_def": "to think, imagine", "Opt_3_def": "to put under stress or make difficult", "Opt_4_def": "to keep something out of danger"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The mask must always ____ the actor in expressing both joy and grief.", "Opt_1": "postpone", "Opt_2": "measure", "Opt_3": "inhibit", "Opt_4": "discover", "Answer": "inhibit", "Opt_1_def": "to put back in time", "Opt_2_def": "to find out how much there is of something", "Opt_3_def": "to prevent or stop", "Opt_4_def": "to find out; to find something for the first time (esp. land or scientific knowledge)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "There will be a ____ class after school today for those who want extra practice for the test.", "Opt_1": "suitable", "Opt_2": "supplementary", "Opt_3": "inherent", "Opt_4": "official", "Answer": "supplementary", "Opt_1_def": "good for a particular job or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "extra; additional", "Opt_3_def": "part of; a fundamental characteristic of", "Opt_4_def": "approved by an authority"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Should the counselor attempt to ____ him and inform him that there is a risk to his future children?", "Opt_1": "approach", "Opt_2": "exaggerate", "Opt_3": "identify", "Opt_4": "degenerate", "Answer": "identify", "Opt_1_def": "to near; to get closer", "Opt_2_def": "to \"overstate\" the truth; to say something is bigger or better than it really is", "Opt_3_def": "to know or say who or what something is", "Opt_4_def": "to get worse"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Infinity is an ____ idea that many students find difficult to understand.", "Opt_1": "abstract", "Opt_2": "absent", "Opt_3": "practical", "Opt_4": "tough", "Answer": "abstract", "Opt_1_def": "not specific or concrete", "Opt_2_def": "being not there; missing", "Opt_3_def": "useful; possible", "Opt_4_def": "difficult, strong"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "How can you tell if the book, article, website, or other resource you located is a valid, ____ source?", "Opt_1": "credible", "Opt_2": "slight", "Opt_3": "similar", "Opt_4": "sole", "Answer": "credible", "Opt_1_def": "believable", "Opt_2_def": "small", "Opt_3_def": "like, almost the same as", "Opt_4_def": "only"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Factory farming is just not ____ with animal welfare.", "Opt_1": "vital", "Opt_2": "compatible", "Opt_3": "positive", "Opt_4": "subsequent", "Answer": "compatible", "Opt_1_def": "very important", "Opt_2_def": "able to work with someone or something else", "Opt_3_def": "good; optimistic", "Opt_4_def": "next, following"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The purpose of this study was to explore the internal and ____ factors influencing the career development of first generation Filipina Americans.", "Opt_1": "major", "Opt_2": "particular", "Opt_3": "evident", "Opt_4": "external", "Answer": "external", "Opt_1_def": "important, large", "Opt_2_def": "specific", "Opt_3_def": "clear", "Opt_4_def": "outside"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "It is my firm ____ to remain with my department for at least two years.", "Opt_1": "occasion", "Opt_2": "state", "Opt_3": "policy", "Opt_4": "intention", "Answer": "intention", "Opt_1_def": "time (opportunity)", "Opt_2_def": "condition, situation", "Opt_3_def": "formal rules", "Opt_4_def": "plan, aim"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "You will gain no ____ for work that has simply been copied from the internet.", "Opt_1": "purpose", "Opt_2": "credit", "Opt_3": "trait", "Opt_4": "profit", "Answer": "credit", "Opt_1_def": "reason, goal", "Opt_2_def": "gained on completing a course of study; praise", "Opt_3_def": "characteristic; aspect", "Opt_4_def": "money gained"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The government has ____ published reports about farming in the UK and illegal drug-taking. The latter has created far more interest in the media.", "Opt_1": "furthermore", "Opt_2": "recently", "Opt_3": "nevertheless", "Opt_4": "generally", "Answer": "recently", "Opt_1_def": "also, in addition", "Opt_2_def": "in the near past", "Opt_3_def": "however (although / despite that)", "Opt_4_def": "usually"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The company made a radical reduction in its workforce in ____ to improve its performance in the second part of the financial year.", "Opt_1": "order", "Opt_2": "forecast", "Opt_3": "programme", "Opt_4": "level", "Answer": "order", "Opt_1_def": "sequence, place", "Opt_2_def": "prediction", "Opt_3_def": "a course of lessons; a project", "Opt_4_def": "standard; layer; amount"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "We are going to ____ this photograph to poster size and put it on the classroom wall.", "Opt_1": "prevail", "Opt_2": "drain", "Opt_3": "enlarge", "Opt_4": "distribute", "Answer": "enlarge", "Opt_1_def": "to succeed; to overcome", "Opt_2_def": "to take away; to get rid of", "Opt_3_def": "to make larger", "Opt_4_def": "to give out"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "All new computer purchases by the University, and its various Auxiliaries, shall meet a minimum ____ for both hardware and operating system.", "Opt_1": "agent", "Opt_2": "standard", "Opt_3": "range", "Opt_4": "distance", "Answer": "standard", "Opt_1_def": "a person who is paid to do a job for someone", "Opt_2_def": "quality", "Opt_3_def": "extent, distance between two points", "Opt_4_def": "how far it is from one place to another"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The police ____ give details of whom they have arrested until they know that the person will be charged with a crime.", "Opt_1": "gradually", "Opt_2": "seldom", "Opt_3": "somewhat", "Opt_4": "therefore", "Answer": "seldom", "Opt_1_def": "slowly; steadily", "Opt_2_def": "rare", "Opt_3_def": "quite, rather", "Opt_4_def": "so, as a result"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The course is aimed to develop appropriate skills and will therefore attempt to identify contexts where a traditional ____ might be required.", "Opt_1": "desire", "Opt_2": "precaution", "Opt_3": "cause", "Opt_4": "lecture", "Answer": "lecture", "Opt_1_def": "a want or wish for something", "Opt_2_def": "something done to avoid danger, harm or problems", "Opt_3_def": "the reason why something happens", "Opt_4_def": "a talk on a particular subject; talk criticizing unacceptable behaviour"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "If you currently do not possess the ____ to meet this standard, you are advised to enroll in a class that will provide you with this capability.", "Opt_1": "period", "Opt_2": "skill", "Opt_3": "scheme", "Opt_4": "field", "Answer": "skill", "Opt_1_def": "a length of time (e.g. a lesson)", "Opt_2_def": "ability (e.g. in sport or music)", "Opt_3_def": "plan. idea, project", "Opt_4_def": "area of interest or study"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "It's difficult to ____ your good mood if it's hot and loud in the classroom, you have a headache, and the work is very boring.", "Opt_1": "cease", "Opt_2": "ruin", "Opt_3": "preserve", "Opt_4": "conduct", "Answer": "preserve", "Opt_1_def": "to stop", "Opt_2_def": "to spoil or damage", "Opt_3_def": "forward,\" said Michele Gougeon.", "Opt_4_def": "to do or perform; to behave"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The company's financial ____ has been greatly affected by the rising cost of oil.", "Opt_1": "circumstances", "Opt_2": "resource", "Opt_3": "performance", "Opt_4": "rank", "Answer": "performance", "Opt_1_def": "situation", "Opt_2_def": "a source of information or material", "Opt_3_def": "action or achievement", "Opt_4_def": "position (in a list or hierarchy)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Caesar showed no ____ to accept the office of \"dictator for life\" in February 44 B.C.", "Opt_1": "guarantee", "Opt_2": "custom", "Opt_3": "reluctance", "Opt_4": "criterion", "Answer": "reluctance", "Opt_1_def": "to promise or assure that something will or will not happen", "Opt_2_def": "a habit (often particular to a culture)", "Opt_3_def": "unwillingness; hesitation", "Opt_4_def": "a way to judge the value or importance of something"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "We believe that individuals who respect and support a diverse global ____ will prosper as leaders in schools, universities, businesses, and human service.", "Opt_1": "society", "Opt_2": "boundary", "Opt_3": "route", "Opt_4": "atmosphere", "Answer": "society", "Opt_1_def": "a group of people; the entire group of people living in a country", "Opt_2_def": "limit, extent", "Opt_3_def": "the way to get to a place or a thing", "Opt_4_def": "mood among people or groups"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "But, for their part, the Syrian leaders failed to ____ for Israel to have rights to some of that water.", "Opt_1": "embody", "Opt_2": "perceive", "Opt_3": "speculate", "Opt_4": "negotiate", "Answer": "negotiate", "Opt_1_def": "to be a good example of ..", "Opt_2_def": "to see; to become aware of with one of the senses; to think", "Opt_3_def": "to think and talk about (often future events)", "Opt_4_def": "to discuss (usually in politics or business)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "You will analyze recurrent patterns of international political conflict, identify underlying issues, and ____ alternative resolutions.", "Opt_1": "present", "Opt_2": "suggest", "Opt_3": "deliver", "Opt_4": "insist", "Answer": "suggest", "Opt_1_def": "to give or show; to make a presentation", "Opt_2_def": "to say an idea; to recommend", "Opt_3_def": "to provide (often by bringing to people)", "Opt_4_def": "to demand; to make a strong claim"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The cost will not ____ anyone from participating in the program.", "Opt_1": "negotiate", "Opt_2": "retreat", "Opt_3": "prohibit", "Opt_4": "impress", "Answer": "prohibit", "Opt_1_def": "to discuss (usually in politics or business)", "Opt_2_def": "to go back", "Opt_3_def": "to ban, disallow", "Opt_4_def": "to create a favourable reaction"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Financial aid is the ____ we use to describe a variety of funds available to help students and their families finance the cost of a Berry College education.", "Opt_1": "trace", "Opt_2": "topic", "Opt_3": "term", "Opt_4": "territory", "Answer": "term", "Opt_1_def": "sign; indication; evidence", "Opt_2_def": "area of interest or discussion", "Opt_3_def": "a word or expression", "Opt_4_def": "land; area (of interest)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Doctors ____ the difficulty of giving up smoking. That's why they recommend never starting.", "Opt_1": "combine", "Opt_2": "deprive", "Opt_3": "appoint", "Opt_4": "recognize", "Answer": "recognize", "Opt_1_def": "to put or go together", "Opt_2_def": "to take away (the opportunity)", "Opt_3_def": "to give a job to someone", "Opt_4_def": "to know or understand (who someone is or what something is)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "In Germany most students have the chance to gain ____ experience in an office or factory, before deciding what job they would like to do.", "Opt_1": "trivial", "Opt_2": "obvious", "Opt_3": "dynamic", "Opt_4": "practical", "Answer": "practical", "Opt_1_def": "not important", "Opt_2_def": "clear, evident", "Opt_3_def": "changing; growing; energetic", "Opt_4_def": "useful; possible"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "It may well be that the two towers on Boynton Hill will soon become a familiar ____ of innovation to educators and students across the country.", "Opt_1": "delay", "Opt_2": "point", "Opt_3": "symbol", "Opt_4": "bond", "Answer": "symbol", "Opt_1_def": "lateness", "Opt_2_def": "purpose; reason; value", "Opt_3_def": "a picture; the representation of an idea", "Opt_4_def": "link; tie"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Unlike other animals, humans have no ____ for survival; we often choose to do things that may be detrimental to our health.", "Opt_1": "precaution", "Opt_2": "instinct", "Opt_3": "relationship", "Opt_4": "rate", "Answer": "instinct", "Opt_1_def": "something done to avoid danger, harm or problems", "Opt_2_def": "natural feeling or reaction", "Opt_3_def": "the way to things are connected", "Opt_4_def": "quantity; proportion; speed"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "If you ____ someone who is not qualified for the job, you cannot be surprised if they have problems.", "Opt_1": "block", "Opt_2": "appoint", "Opt_3": "dictate", "Opt_4": "accumulate", "Answer": "appoint", "Opt_1_def": "to not allow; to stop or prevent", "Opt_2_def": "to give a job to someone", "Opt_3_def": "to tell someone what to do", "Opt_4_def": "to grow; to gather together"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Although the agreement was compulsory rather than voluntary, it led to substantial ____ reforms along French lines.", "Opt_1": "rational", "Opt_2": "military", "Opt_3": "moderate", "Opt_4": "ambiguous", "Answer": "military", "Opt_1_def": "base on reason, not on emotion or instinct", "Opt_2_def": "to do with army", "Opt_3_def": "not very much; not very strong; not extreme", "Opt_4_def": "not clear; open to more than one interpretation"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Most countries have a code by which parents can decide if a film is ____ for their children.", "Opt_1": "precise", "Opt_2": "absent", "Opt_3": "suitable", "Opt_4": "local", "Answer": "suitable", "Opt_1_def": "exact", "Opt_2_def": "being not there; missing", "Opt_3_def": "good for a particular job or purpose", "Opt_4_def": "in the area where you live or work"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Your main ____ for this lesson is to work together to prepare a presentation on air pollution.", "Opt_1": "scale", "Opt_2": "task", "Opt_3": "mechanism", "Opt_4": "sequence", "Answer": "task", "Opt_1_def": "extent", "Opt_2_def": "job", "Opt_3_def": "procedure, process", "Opt_4_def": "the order in which things are arranged or happen"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Children who are moved more frequently are more likely to have ____ problems than children in more stable placements.", "Opt_1": "widespread", "Opt_2": "minor", "Opt_3": "subsequent", "Opt_4": "neutral", "Answer": "subsequent", "Opt_1_def": "common", "Opt_2_def": "small, not important", "Opt_3_def": "next, following", "Opt_4_def": "neither for nor against; neither positive nor negative"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Why did the Bush Administration refuse to ____ its goals in order to achieve a consensus?", "Opt_1": "conform", "Opt_2": "decline", "Opt_3": "modify", "Opt_4": "adapt", "Answer": "modify", "Opt_1_def": "to do what is required", "Opt_2_def": "to go down or get worse", "Opt_3_def": "to change", "Opt_4_def": "to change (often in response to a changed situation)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "History is filled with examples of military leaders who have suffered at the mercy of climate conditions that they failed to ____ adequately.", "Opt_1": "contemplate", "Opt_2": "refuse", "Opt_3": "protest", "Opt_4": "collaborate", "Answer": "contemplate", "Opt_1_def": "to think about; to consider", "Opt_2_def": "to not do something that someone wants you to do", "Opt_3_def": "to express anger or unhappiness about something", "Opt_4_def": "to work together"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Some people use unethical methods to create a ____ that says what they want it to say.", "Opt_1": "defeat", "Opt_2": "statistic", "Opt_3": "support", "Opt_4": "facilities", "Answer": "statistic", "Opt_1_def": "a loss (often in a battle or sports event)", "Opt_2_def": "mathematical number", "Opt_3_def": "help", "Opt_4_def": "buildings and other places that can be used by people"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "I was unable to ____ the reason for Angelica's sudden departure at the beginning of the second trimester.", "Opt_1": "discover", "Opt_2": "associate", "Opt_3": "exceed", "Opt_4": "raise", "Answer": "discover", "Opt_1_def": "to find out; to find something for the first time (esp. land or scientific knowledge)", "Opt_2_def": "to link to; to make a connection to", "Opt_3_def": "to be more than or better than", "Opt_4_def": "to lift; to make higher"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Injuries occur when there is a certain blow or pressure ____ the head, damaging the interior of the brain.", "Opt_1": "except", "Opt_2": "against", "Opt_3": "despite", "Opt_4": "beneath", "Answer": "against", "Opt_1_def": "but (not)", "Opt_2_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_3_def": "although", "Opt_4_def": "below"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The human mind cannot ____ the true nature of God, nor can the angels.", "Opt_1": "comprehend", "Opt_2": "correspond", "Opt_3": "hesitate", "Opt_4": "provide", "Answer": "comprehend", "Opt_1_def": "to understand", "Opt_2_def": "to be related to", "Opt_3_def": "to pause before saying or doing something", "Opt_4_def": "to give"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The government had to retreat from its starting position in the face of ____ criticism in the newspapers.", "Opt_1": "permanent", "Opt_2": "basic", "Opt_3": "ambitious", "Opt_4": "massive", "Answer": "massive", "Opt_1_def": "lasting for ever or for a very long time", "Opt_2_def": "first or easy", "Opt_3_def": "having high goals (especially in a career; challenging", "Opt_4_def": "very large"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "From the airplane it was possible to see the ____ of the destruction caused in the earthquake.", "Opt_1": "choice", "Opt_2": "source", "Opt_3": "route", "Opt_4": "scale", "Answer": "scale", "Opt_1_def": "decision, selection", "Opt_2_def": "where something begins, where you can find something", "Opt_3_def": "the way to get to a place or a thing", "Opt_4_def": "extent"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The OCC provides counsel and legal advice in the development of policy, procedures, and strategy ____ to the management and operation of the UC Riverside campus.", "Opt_1": "supplementary", "Opt_2": "infinite", "Opt_3": "adjacent", "Opt_4": "related", "Answer": "related", "Opt_1_def": "extra; additional", "Opt_2_def": "without an end", "Opt_3_def": "next to", "Opt_4_def": "connected; having something to do with each other"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Some subjects in our school have a higher ____ than others. Everyone wants to take science, but few want to study a second language.", "Opt_1": "status", "Opt_2": "assignment", "Opt_3": "revenue", "Opt_4": "attitude", "Answer": "status", "Opt_1_def": "position, standing", "Opt_2_def": "a task; the giving of a task", "Opt_3_def": "money, income", "Opt_4_def": "what someone thinks about something (and how their behaviour is influenced by their thinking)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Unfortunately, heroines of this sort are not numerous in oral tales, and do not ____ at all in any of the Grimm tales.", "Opt_1": "exist", "Opt_2": "retain", "Opt_3": "damage", "Opt_4": "transmit", "Answer": "exist", "Opt_1_def": "to be alive, to be in the world", "Opt_2_def": "to keep", "Opt_3_def": "to spoil or break", "Opt_4_def": "to send or convey"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "He was a soldier, and doubtless felt that it was not his ____ to volunteer advice to the political department.", "Opt_1": "field", "Opt_2": "province", "Opt_3": "image", "Opt_4": "bond", "Answer": "province", "Opt_1_def": "area of interest or study", "Opt_2_def": "area (of interest)", "Opt_3_def": "picture", "Opt_4_def": "link; tie"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Before making our decision we need to ____ the issue of financial support.", "Opt_1": "consider", "Opt_2": "release", "Opt_3": "increase", "Opt_4": "prefer", "Answer": "consider", "Opt_1_def": "to think", "Opt_2_def": "to let go or let out", "Opt_3_def": "to get bigger", "Opt_4_def": "to like better"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Strong families ____ the ability to manage both daily stressors and difficult life crises creatively and effectively.", "Opt_1": "infer", "Opt_2": "remove", "Opt_3": "possess", "Opt_4": "maintain", "Answer": "possess", "Opt_1_def": "to come to a conclusion about something", "Opt_2_def": "to take away", "Opt_3_def": "to have or own", "Opt_4_def": "to claim or state"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Both Initial and Wokingham now dispute the ____ for the cost of food and say it is lower.", "Opt_1": "legislation", "Opt_2": "aid", "Opt_3": "figure", "Opt_4": "area", "Answer": "figure", "Opt_1_def": "governmental rule; law", "Opt_2_def": "help (often financial help)", "Opt_3_def": "number", "Opt_4_def": "field, sphere"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Smith starts out with a ____ idea of what she wants to achieve.", "Opt_1": "intrinsic", "Opt_2": "eligible", "Opt_3": "classic", "Opt_4": "loose", "Answer": "loose", "Opt_1_def": "belonging to; inherent in", "Opt_2_def": "being entitled or qualified to do something", "Opt_3_def": "very good, the best or most used", "Opt_4_def": "not firm or finished"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Therefore, it is important to ____ low birth weight infants according to their weight for their gestational age.", "Opt_1": "classify", "Opt_2": "compile", "Opt_3": "emerge", "Opt_4": "speculate", "Answer": "classify", "Opt_1_def": "to put into a category or class", "Opt_2_def": "to put together (often in a list", "Opt_3_def": "to come out; to become known", "Opt_4_def": "to think and talk about (often future events)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The human mind cannot ____ the true nature of God, nor can the angels.", "Opt_1": "differentiate", "Opt_2": "discuss", "Opt_3": "accuse", "Opt_4": "comprehend", "Answer": "comprehend", "Opt_1_def": "to make different; to see the difference", "Opt_2_def": "to talk about", "Opt_3_def": "to blame", "Opt_4_def": "to understand"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The ____ version of our anatomy information system has evolved from several previous systems.", "Opt_1": "current", "Opt_2": "uniform", "Opt_3": "global", "Opt_4": "elementary", "Answer": "current", "Opt_1_def": "happening now", "Opt_2_def": "having the same qualities", "Opt_3_def": "world", "Opt_4_def": "easy"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The latest ____ of his bad behaviour was to lock another student in the toilet.", "Opt_1": "labour", "Opt_2": "instance", "Opt_3": "balance", "Opt_4": "treatment", "Answer": "instance", "Opt_1_def": "work", "Opt_2_def": "example", "Opt_3_def": "equalness", "Opt_4_def": "way of handing a person, situation or problem (often of illness)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The strategy failed to persuade workers themselves to consider domestic service as anything other than a ____ transition.", "Opt_1": "abnormal", "Opt_2": "severe", "Opt_3": "temporary", "Opt_4": "exact", "Answer": "temporary", "Opt_1_def": "not normal, unusual", "Opt_2_def": "serious, harsh", "Opt_3_def": "for a short or limited time", "Opt_4_def": "precise, opposite of approximate"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "If you currently do not ____ the skill to meet this standard, you are advised to enroll in a class that will provide you with this capability.", "Opt_1": "revive", "Opt_2": "suspend", "Opt_3": "possess", "Opt_4": "facilitate", "Answer": "possess", "Opt_1_def": "to bring back (to life)", "Opt_2_def": "to stop (often for a short time only)", "Opt_3_def": "to have or own", "Opt_4_def": "to make something easier"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The student must ____ the thesis before a committee of three or more faculty members.", "Opt_1": "stipulate", "Opt_2": "defend", "Opt_3": "prepare", "Opt_4": "collaborate", "Answer": "defend", "Opt_1_def": "to require", "Opt_2_def": "to give reasons for", "Opt_3_def": "to get something ready (or to get ready for something)", "Opt_4_def": "to work together"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The government has invested little money in the health system. The quality of hospital care is sure to ____ more and more.", "Opt_1": "trade", "Opt_2": "deteriorate", "Opt_3": "evaluate", "Opt_4": "descend", "Answer": "deteriorate", "Opt_1_def": "to exchange products or services", "Opt_2_def": "to get worse", "Opt_3_def": "to decide on the value, quality or importance of something", "Opt_4_def": "to go down"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Her mother is a ____ visitor to the school. In fact she comes two or three times a week!", "Opt_1": "artificial", "Opt_2": "ancient", "Opt_3": "apart", "Opt_4": "frequent", "Answer": "frequent", "Opt_1_def": "not real or natural", "Opt_2_def": "very old", "Opt_3_def": "not together, separate", "Opt_4_def": "often"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "My teacher has the ____ of telling us the homework in the last minute of the lesson. It's not good.", "Opt_1": "assent", "Opt_2": "extent", "Opt_3": "habit", "Opt_4": "administration", "Answer": "habit", "Opt_1_def": "agreement", "Opt_2_def": "size, amount", "Opt_3_def": "something you do regularly", "Opt_4_def": "the people responsible for running an organization such as the government or a school"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Try to ____ that the process is more important than the answer so that the student learns that it is OK to not have an instant solution.", "Opt_1": "communicate", "Opt_2": "construct", "Opt_3": "neglect", "Opt_4": "address", "Answer": "communicate", "Opt_1_def": "to convey information", "Opt_2_def": "to make", "Opt_3_def": "to not think about or care for", "Opt_4_def": "to give attention to (an issue)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "John has many strong opinions. You have to be sure not to let him ____ groupwork in class.", "Opt_1": "yield", "Opt_2": "dominate", "Opt_3": "distribute", "Opt_4": "illustrate", "Answer": "dominate", "Opt_1_def": "to produce", "Opt_2_def": "to be much better, to play the most important part", "Opt_3_def": "to give out", "Opt_4_def": "to show; to make clear"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "She accepted the arduous task of vice president, according to the papers, saying that she could not ____ the will of the people.", "Opt_1": "sustain", "Opt_2": "manufacture", "Opt_3": "predict", "Opt_4": "frustrate", "Answer": "frustrate", "Opt_1_def": "to keep going; to maintain", "Opt_2_def": "to produce (with machines)", "Opt_3_def": "to say what will happen in the future", "Opt_4_def": "to stop or prevent"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The course is intended to ____ a lot of class discussion.", "Opt_1": "dedicate", "Opt_2": "involve", "Opt_3": "prevent", "Opt_4": "degenerate", "Answer": "involve", "Opt_1_def": "to devote (time and attention)", "Opt_2_def": "to include or mean", "Opt_3_def": "to stop from doing or happening", "Opt_4_def": "to get worse"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "We can conclude that China is unlikely to put significant ____ on Sudan, and that Sudan could and would easily resist such ____.", "Opt_1": "growth", "Opt_2": "power", "Opt_3": "survey", "Opt_4": "pressure", "Answer": "pressure", "Opt_1_def": "development, increase", "Opt_2_def": "the right or authority to do something", "Opt_3_def": "questionnaire; information gained by questioning people or data", "Opt_4_def": "force; influence; stress"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Madam Chair, I move that the matter under discussion is not the ____ business of the Senate.", "Opt_1": "main", "Opt_2": "automatic", "Opt_3": "abundant", "Opt_4": "proper", "Answer": "proper", "Opt_1_def": "most important", "Opt_2_def": "happening by itself; happening naturally or usually", "Opt_3_def": "existing in large quantities", "Opt_4_def": "correct, appropriate"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "It explores the lives of a group of adolescent boys in the ____ between the departure of the Nazis and the arrival of the Communists.", "Opt_1": "interval", "Opt_2": "purpose", "Opt_3": "behalf", "Opt_4": "exercise", "Answer": "interval", "Opt_1_def": "a period of time", "Opt_2_def": "reason, goal", "Opt_3_def": "as a representative of; for the benefit of", "Opt_4_def": "a piece of work, activity"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "In all cases, employers must offer ____ dates for a second-round interview if the date originally suggested is inconvenient.", "Opt_1": "detriment", "Opt_2": "trace", "Opt_3": "manner", "Opt_4": "alternative", "Answer": "alternative", "Opt_1_def": "disadvantage", "Opt_2_def": "sign; indication; evidence", "Opt_3_def": "way of doing something", "Opt_4_def": "other possibility"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Class data will be collected to compare perceived overweight and attempt at dieting with actual weight ____ classification.", "Opt_1": "risk", "Opt_2": "criticize", "Opt_3": "contradict", "Opt_4": "incorporate", "Answer": "risk", "Opt_1_def": "to act in a way that might lead to danger or failure", "Opt_2_def": "to express disapproval; to say what you don't like or think is good about something or someone", "Opt_3_def": "to say or show that what someone has said is wrong", "Opt_4_def": "to include"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Students with Advanced Placement scores of 4 or 5 in English Language ____ a credit toward graduation but not toward the English major.", "Opt_1": "receive", "Opt_2": "intervene", "Opt_3": "assume", "Opt_4": "publish", "Answer": "receive", "Opt_1_def": "to get", "Opt_2_def": "to step into a situation (in order to stop or change something)", "Opt_3_def": "to believe to be true; to presume or predict", "Opt_4_def": "to make available in paper or online form"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Students are strongly recommended to ____ assistance from the Student Rights Officer at their campus should they decide to appeal against exclusion.", "Opt_1": "clarify", "Opt_2": "seek", "Opt_3": "communicate", "Opt_4": "induce", "Answer": "seek", "Opt_1_def": "to make something clear, explain", "Opt_2_def": "to look for or want", "Opt_3_def": "to convey information", "Opt_4_def": "to make happen; to force"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "We can separate white light into its ____ colors with a prism and use an identical prism to recombine the light.", "Opt_1": "institution", "Opt_2": "defect", "Opt_3": "component", "Opt_4": "instruction", "Answer": "component", "Opt_1_def": "a large organization; an important system or custom", "Opt_2_def": "problem; mistake", "Opt_3_def": "part of; an element of", "Opt_4_def": "advice or teaching how to do something; an order to do something"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The group work done during these workshops will ____ in a series of papers, presented by project participants, at a one-day conference.", "Opt_1": "culminate", "Opt_2": "enhance", "Opt_3": "intervene", "Opt_4": "perceive", "Answer": "culminate", "Opt_1_def": "to end", "Opt_2_def": "to make something better", "Opt_3_def": "to step into a situation (in order to stop or change something)", "Opt_4_def": "to see; to become aware of with one of the senses; to think"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "I did not understand what the artist was trying to express by these two pieces, nor did I see any ____ in the work.", "Opt_1": "attitude", "Opt_2": "outline", "Opt_3": "aim", "Opt_4": "skill", "Answer": "skill", "Opt_1_def": "what someone thinks about something (and how their behaviour is influenced by their thinking)", "Opt_2_def": "plan or summary", "Opt_3_def": "goal or intention", "Opt_4_def": "ability (e.g. in sport or music)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Dairy farmers have led the latest in a long series of protests by agricultural associations, ____ the record high prices for farm products.", "Opt_1": "despite", "Opt_2": "prior", "Opt_3": "worth", "Opt_4": "beneath", "Answer": "despite", "Opt_1_def": "although", "Opt_2_def": "before", "Opt_3_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_4_def": "below"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Very ____ water does not conduct electricity well compared with contaminated water because it contains no inorganic ions.", "Opt_1": "considerable", "Opt_2": "poor", "Opt_3": "radical", "Opt_4": "pure", "Answer": "pure", "Opt_1_def": "very big; very much", "Opt_2_def": "bad, unsatisfactory", "Opt_3_def": "extreme, strong", "Opt_4_def": "complete, 100%"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "That is no way to ____ yourself in the library.", "Opt_1": "blame", "Opt_2": "devote", "Opt_3": "conduct", "Opt_4": "conserve", "Answer": "conduct", "Opt_1_def": "to accuse", "Opt_2_def": "to give (time) to", "Opt_3_def": "to do or perform; to behave", "Opt_4_def": "to preserve; to not use"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "If you are ____ and flexible, enjoy solving tasks independently and are committed to achieving outstanding performance, then this is the job for you.", "Opt_1": "effective", "Opt_2": "remote", "Opt_3": "vast", "Opt_4": "reliable", "Answer": "reliable", "Opt_1_def": "good, working well", "Opt_2_def": "far, distant, small", "Opt_3_def": "very large", "Opt_4_def": "can be trusted, does not let you down \r\n"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Computer hard disk cleaning is not an ____ that many people perform very frequently.", "Opt_1": "interior", "Opt_2": "doubt", "Opt_3": "operation", "Opt_4": "struggle", "Answer": "operation", "Opt_1_def": "inside", "Opt_2_def": "a feeling of uncertainty (whether something is true)", "Opt_3_def": "procedure; happening; process", "Opt_4_def": "a fight, a difficult situation to be overcome"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Students are encouraged to discuss topics early on with the instructor, ____ in the case of an independent investigation.", "Opt_1": "overly", "Opt_2": "definitely", "Opt_3": "especially", "Opt_4": "merely", "Answer": "especially", "Opt_1_def": "too", "Opt_2_def": "certainly; without doubt", "Opt_3_def": "particularly", "Opt_4_def": "only, just, simply"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Beyond this, if you have a ____ reason for absence or coming in late, such as a documented medical excuse, you should provide that information to the instructor.", "Opt_1": "capable", "Opt_2": "medium", "Opt_3": "credible", "Opt_4": "accurate", "Answer": "credible", "Opt_1_def": "able", "Opt_2_def": "in the middle", "Opt_3_def": "believable", "Opt_4_def": "exact, containing no mistakes"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "This is especially true in the environmental sciences where many of the systems are dynamic and ____ complex.", "Opt_1": "indeed", "Opt_2": "extremely", "Opt_3": "accordingly", "Opt_4": "simply", "Answer": "extremely", "Opt_1_def": "used in confirmation or emphasis; really", "Opt_2_def": "very", "Opt_3_def": "appropriate to; in compliance with", "Opt_4_def": "completely; just; only"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The information that you receive in today's lesson will ____ you to complete your project on nuclear energy.", "Opt_1": "recover", "Opt_2": "fade", "Opt_3": "deny", "Opt_4": "enable", "Answer": "enable", "Opt_1_def": "to get back", "Opt_2_def": "to disappear slowly", "Opt_3_def": "to refuse ( responsibility for doing or saying something); to say that something is not correct", "Opt_4_def": "to make something or someone able to do something"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The search results are likely to include lots of hits that are not particularly ____ to your topic.", "Opt_1": "practical", "Opt_2": "relevant", "Opt_3": "satisfactory", "Opt_4": "deliberate", "Answer": "relevant", "Opt_1_def": "useful; possible", "Opt_2_def": "connected to the topic of discussion or consideration", "Opt_3_def": "enough;OK", "Opt_4_def": "intentional, not by accident"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Many people buy supplementary vitamin pills because they do not believe that they get enough vitamins from their ____ food.", "Opt_1": "intense", "Opt_2": "regular", "Opt_3": "permanent", "Opt_4": "wise", "Answer": "regular", "Opt_1_def": "strong, extreme", "Opt_2_def": "predictable, following a pattern; normal", "Opt_3_def": "lasting for ever or for a very long time", "Opt_4_def": "intelligent; sensible"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "You can submit your work at any time ____ to the due date.", "Opt_1": "prior", "Opt_2": "instead", "Opt_3": "despite", "Opt_4": "beneath", "Answer": "prior", "Opt_1_def": "before", "Opt_2_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_3_def": "although", "Opt_4_def": "below"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "It operated below 60%, was generally poorly designed and therefore not ____ considering.", "Opt_1": "except", "Opt_2": "besides", "Opt_3": "worth", "Opt_4": "against", "Answer": "worth", "Opt_1_def": "but (not)", "Opt_2_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_3_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_4_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Now that you have revised your work, the next stage of the writing process is to ____ it for errors of grammar or spelling.", "Opt_1": "adjust", "Opt_2": "edit", "Opt_3": "fail", "Opt_4": "define", "Answer": "edit", "Opt_1_def": "to change (often in order to make something work properly)", "Opt_2_def": "to make changes in a piece of writing", "Opt_3_def": "to not do something, or not work as expected; to do badly", "Opt_4_def": "to state what something is or means"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "In order to match you up with the most ____ roommate we can, please fill out the Housing Intake Questionaire.", "Opt_1": "legal", "Opt_2": "likely", "Opt_3": "prompt", "Opt_4": "compatible", "Answer": "compatible", "Opt_1_def": "acceptable in law (to do with the law)", "Opt_2_def": "probable", "Opt_3_def": "quick; on or before time", "Opt_4_def": "able to work with someone or something else"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "This form is to be used by students who seek to ____ or drop a course during the first two weeks of the trimester.", "Opt_1": "append", "Opt_2": "edit", "Opt_3": "succeed", "Opt_4": "add", "Answer": "add", "Opt_1_def": "to add to the end (of a piece of writing)", "Opt_2_def": "to make changes in a piece of writing", "Opt_3_def": "to do well", "Opt_4_def": "to include; to give or say extra"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "There was an unpleasant ____ on the playground yesterday when a fight started between two groups of students.", "Opt_1": "fallacy", "Opt_2": "incident", "Opt_3": "interval", "Opt_4": "atmosphere", "Answer": "incident", "Opt_1_def": "mistake; false belief", "Opt_2_def": "happening; event", "Opt_3_def": "a period of time", "Opt_4_def": "mood among people or groups"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It offers an effective solution to a problem based on good audience analysis, and fulfills ____ as well as all major purposes.", "Opt_1": "confident", "Opt_2": "massive", "Opt_3": "minor", "Opt_4": "substantial", "Answer": "minor", "Opt_1_def": "sure that something will happen", "Opt_2_def": "very large", "Opt_3_def": "small, not important", "Opt_4_def": "large"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "You need to ____ the material covered by the homework problems in order to pass the quizzes and final examination.", "Opt_1": "reverse", "Opt_2": "avoid", "Opt_3": "exceed", "Opt_4": "assimilate", "Answer": "assimilate", "Opt_1_def": "to turn back or go back", "Opt_2_def": "to not do something or go somewhere", "Opt_3_def": "to be more than or better than", "Opt_4_def": "to take in"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The human mind cannot ____ the true nature of God, nor can the angels.", "Opt_1": "prevent", "Opt_2": "comprehend", "Opt_3": "yield", "Opt_4": "rotate", "Answer": "comprehend", "Opt_1_def": "to stop from doing or happening", "Opt_2_def": "to understand", "Opt_3_def": "to produce", "Opt_4_def": "to turn or move (around)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The additional time is necessary to ____ him to make a sound decision on an Alaska natural gas transportation system.", "Opt_1": "deprive", "Opt_2": "enable", "Opt_3": "explain", "Opt_4": "base", "Answer": "enable", "Opt_1_def": "to take away (the opportunity)", "Opt_2_def": "to make something or someone able to do something", "Opt_3_def": "to give the reason for something or say how to do something", "Opt_4_def": "to use as a way of doing or deciding something"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Colorado State University scientists have found a way to ____ improve the quality of laser light at extremely short wavelengths.", "Opt_1": "dramatically", "Opt_2": "rather", "Opt_3": "barely", "Opt_4": "perhaps", "Answer": "dramatically", "Opt_1_def": "very strongly, significantly", "Opt_2_def": "instead", "Opt_3_def": "not very much; hardly", "Opt_4_def": "maybe, possibly"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Can you please ____ this letter to your parents?", "Opt_1": "control", "Opt_2": "distort", "Opt_3": "deprive", "Opt_4": "convey", "Answer": "convey", "Opt_1_def": "to have and exercise power over something or someone", "Opt_2_def": "to change or affect something (negatively)", "Opt_3_def": "to take away (the opportunity)", "Opt_4_def": "to pass on to another person (often by speaking)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Every necessary precaution has been taken to provide up-to-date, ____ information in this website.", "Opt_1": "accurate", "Opt_2": "drastic", "Opt_3": "liable", "Opt_4": "poor", "Answer": "accurate", "Opt_1_def": "exact, containing no mistakes", "Opt_2_def": "severe; great", "Opt_3_def": "likely to happen; at risk of happening", "Opt_4_def": "bad, unsatisfactory"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The study did not ____ any significant relationship between the type of music and the amount of stress.", "Opt_1": "appear", "Opt_2": "interact", "Opt_3": "address", "Opt_4": "discover", "Answer": "discover", "Opt_1_def": "to come, be seen", "Opt_2_def": "to react, to affect and be affected", "Opt_3_def": "to give attention to (an issue)", "Opt_4_def": "to find out; to find something for the first time (esp. land or scientific knowledge)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "If you want to travel at half-price on the trains and buses in Frankfurt, you need a ____ identity card with the school stamp.", "Opt_1": "valid", "Opt_2": "ordinary", "Opt_3": "subjective", "Opt_4": "aware", "Answer": "valid", "Opt_1_def": "correct", "Opt_2_def": "usual, typical, every day", "Opt_3_def": "based on personal opinion or feeling", "Opt_4_def": "knowing"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The entire structure of Iraqi ____ and civil society collapsed so completely as the war ended, leaving a vast problem for American troops to handle.", "Opt_1": "arbitrary", "Opt_2": "vast", "Opt_3": "military", "Opt_4": "medium", "Answer": "military", "Opt_1_def": "not planned or thought-out; not considering the wishes of others", "Opt_2_def": "very large", "Opt_3_def": "to do with army", "Opt_4_def": "in the middle"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "If you want too be successful in an English language school or university it is ____ that you learn academic words such as those on this website.", "Opt_1": "imaginary", "Opt_2": "vital", "Opt_3": "infinite", "Opt_4": "broad", "Answer": "vital", "Opt_1_def": "not real; from the imagination", "Opt_2_def": "very important", "Opt_3_def": "without an end", "Opt_4_def": "wide, extensive"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Many people ____ very bad road accidents because they use a seat belt and their car has an air bag.", "Opt_1": "donate", "Opt_2": "survive", "Opt_3": "apply", "Opt_4": "confine", "Answer": "survive", "Opt_1_def": "to give (usually money)", "Opt_2_def": "to not die", "Opt_3_def": "to be relevant (to)", "Opt_4_def": "to limit"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The student was reported to the headmaster for continually trying to ____ the class.", "Opt_1": "implement", "Opt_2": "conform", "Opt_3": "disrupt", "Opt_4": "ruin", "Answer": "disrupt", "Opt_1_def": "to start or put into practice (something that has been planned)", "Opt_2_def": "to do what is required", "Opt_3_def": "to interrupt an event; to damage", "Opt_4_def": "to spoil or damage"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The syllabus must ____ how attendance and participation affect, if at all, the student's course grade.", "Opt_1": "conserve", "Opt_2": "adjust", "Opt_3": "clarify", "Opt_4": "culminate", "Answer": "clarify", "Opt_1_def": "to preserve; to not use", "Opt_2_def": "to change (often in order to make something work properly)", "Opt_3_def": "to make something clear, explain", "Opt_4_def": "to end"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "By reason of the duress of ____ disease, he has so far lost the power to choose between right and wrong.", "Opt_1": "mental", "Opt_2": "vital", "Opt_3": "legitimate", "Opt_4": "deliberate", "Answer": "mental", "Opt_1_def": "of the brain or mind", "Opt_2_def": "very important", "Opt_3_def": "correct; allowed", "Opt_4_def": "intentional, not by accident"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "This is NOT a reliable ____ and you should simply ignore it.", "Opt_1": "statistic", "Opt_2": "defeat", "Opt_3": "fee", "Opt_4": "effort", "Answer": "statistic", "Opt_1_def": "mathematical number", "Opt_2_def": "a loss (often in a battle or sports event)", "Opt_3_def": "money for a service (e.g. a baking service)", "Opt_4_def": "hard work; attempt"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Before doing a longer piece of writing it is usually a good idea to make an ____ to organize your main ideas.", "Opt_1": "research", "Opt_2": "struggle", "Opt_3": "outline", "Opt_4": "aspect", "Answer": "outline", "Opt_1_def": "study; the finding of information", "Opt_2_def": "a fight, a difficult situation to be overcome", "Opt_3_def": "plan or summary", "Opt_4_def": "environment that lifts people up,\" says Jain."}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "I am ____ surprised I did so well in the test because I didn't work very hard this term.", "Opt_1": "universally", "Opt_2": "simply", "Opt_3": "absolutely", "Opt_4": "somewhat", "Answer": "somewhat", "Opt_1_def": "all over the world; by everyone", "Opt_2_def": "completely; just; only", "Opt_3_def": "completely; 100%", "Opt_4_def": "quite, rather"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Many tourists to foreign countries buy a ____ book to help them speak a few words of the language.", "Opt_1": "resource", "Opt_2": "phrase", "Opt_3": "experience", "Opt_4": "prestige", "Answer": "phrase", "Opt_1_def": "a source of information or material", "Opt_2_def": "one achieves best success through constantly applied pressure.", "Opt_3_def": "knowledge and skills gained over a long period of time", "Opt_4_def": "fame and respect"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "A student who fails to cite sources in a ____ attempt to conceal the source of the work should be considered to be cheating.", "Opt_1": "perpetual", "Opt_2": "economic", "Opt_3": "deliberate", "Opt_4": "practical", "Answer": "deliberate", "Opt_1_def": "continuing for ever; never disappearing", "Opt_2_def": "financial; to do with money", "Opt_3_def": "intentional, not by accident", "Opt_4_def": "useful; possible"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "A large ____ map shows a small area with a large amount of detail.", "Opt_1": "scale", "Opt_2": "version", "Opt_3": "event", "Opt_4": "objection", "Answer": "scale", "Opt_1_def": "extent", "Opt_2_def": "form", "Opt_3_def": "a happening", "Opt_4_def": "a statement of disagreement or disapproval"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Her chances of success in the examinations will continue to ____ unless she starts working harder very soon.", "Opt_1": "shrink", "Opt_2": "assert", "Opt_3": "fail", "Opt_4": "comprise", "Answer": "shrink", "Opt_1_def": "to get smaller", "Opt_2_def": "to claim, to say strongly", "Opt_3_def": "to not do something, or not work as expected; to do badly", "Opt_4_def": "to be made up of; to include"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The many hours of practice that usually underlie exceptional ____ remain out of sight to the casual observer.", "Opt_1": "cycle", "Opt_2": "context", "Opt_3": "atmosphere", "Opt_4": "performance", "Answer": "performance", "Opt_1_def": "a complete series of events or processes", "Opt_2_def": "the place or situation in which something is found", "Opt_3_def": "mood among people or groups", "Opt_4_def": "action or achievement"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "It is interesting to think about how teaching will ____ under the influence of digital technologies.", "Opt_1": "observe", "Opt_2": "correlate", "Opt_3": "evolve", "Opt_4": "retreat", "Answer": "evolve", "Opt_1_def": "to watch carefully", "Opt_2_def": "to have a close connection", "Opt_3_def": "to develop (into something better)", "Opt_4_def": "to go back"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Bali has failed to ____ a proposed ten year program to work on sustainable production and consumption.", "Opt_1": "deliver", "Opt_2": "demonstrate", "Opt_3": "consent", "Opt_4": "assume", "Answer": "deliver", "Opt_1_def": "to provide (often by bringing to people)", "Opt_2_def": "to show", "Opt_3_def": "to agree", "Opt_4_def": "to believe to be true; to presume or predict"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The amount of water that you ____ when you get into the bath is equal to the mass of your body.", "Opt_1": "displace", "Opt_2": "cover", "Opt_3": "conduct", "Opt_4": "formulate", "Answer": "displace", "Opt_1_def": "to push out or take the place of something or someone", "Opt_2_def": "to do; to complete", "Opt_3_def": "to do or perform; to behave", "Opt_4_def": "to express"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The government intends to ____ the information for itself. The public will not have access to it until the end of the decade.", "Opt_1": "succeed", "Opt_2": "discover", "Opt_3": "reserve", "Opt_4": "impose", "Answer": "reserve", "Opt_1_def": "to do well", "Opt_2_def": "to find out; to find something for the first time (esp. land or scientific knowledge)", "Opt_3_def": "to keep", "Opt_4_def": "to force; to require to happen"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Injuries ____ when there is a certain blow or pressure against the head, damaging the interior of the brain.", "Opt_1": "occur", "Opt_2": "fluctuate", "Opt_3": "assess", "Opt_4": "derive", "Answer": "occur", "Opt_1_def": "to happen; take place", "Opt_2_def": "to vary; to rise and fall", "Opt_3_def": "to judge or test", "Opt_4_def": "to come from or get from"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "We all have to ____ differences of opinion in the political world and, in order to do that, we have to understand that there are real reasons for these differences.", "Opt_1": "compete", "Opt_2": "spread", "Opt_3": "survive", "Opt_4": "tolerate", "Answer": "tolerate", "Opt_1_def": "to try and win against someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "to move (over a wider area)", "Opt_3_def": "to not die", "Opt_4_def": "to allow to happen; to bear"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The good results in recent matches ____ that the new trainer knows what he is doing.", "Opt_1": "exploit", "Opt_2": "imply", "Opt_3": "import", "Opt_4": "train", "Answer": "imply", "Opt_1_def": "to use (sometimes in a negative way)", "Opt_2_def": "to mean; to give to understand", "Opt_3_def": "to bring in (to a country)", "Opt_4_def": "to teach someone how to do a job"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The doctor examined the patient carefully, ____ that he forgot to check blood pressure.", "Opt_1": "worth", "Opt_2": "due", "Opt_3": "except", "Opt_4": "among", "Answer": "except", "Opt_1_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_3_def": "but (not)", "Opt_4_def": "in, between"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "There is a growing ____ to use the cell phone as the primary phone, without any need for landlines.", "Opt_1": "doubt", "Opt_2": "environment", "Opt_3": "domain", "Opt_4": "trend", "Answer": "trend", "Opt_1_def": "a feeling of uncertainty (whether something is true)", "Opt_2_def": "the world around us", "Opt_3_def": "area (of interest)", "Opt_4_def": "pattern of continuing behaviour"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The use of gender- neutral language may seem unnecessary to some writers, but the ____ use of masculine pronouns leaves the impression that women could not be among the group to which the writer is referring.", "Opt_1": "widespread", "Opt_2": "consistent", "Opt_3": "automatic", "Opt_4": "considerable", "Answer": "consistent", "Opt_1_def": "common", "Opt_2_def": "regular or predictable; remaining the same", "Opt_3_def": "happening by itself; happening naturally or usually", "Opt_4_def": "very big; very much"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The University of Washington has agreed to ____ a class-action lawsuit over faculty salaries.", "Opt_1": "fluctuate", "Opt_2": "deserve", "Opt_3": "settle", "Opt_4": "review", "Answer": "settle", "Opt_1_def": "to vary; to rise and fall", "Opt_2_def": "to have the right to something", "Opt_3_def": "to solve a problem or dispute", "Opt_4_def": "to check over (and make changes)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The school has a ratio of ____ one teacher for every fifteen students.", "Opt_1": "predominantly", "Opt_2": "therefore", "Opt_3": "approximately", "Opt_4": "merely", "Answer": "approximately", "Opt_1_def": "mostly", "Opt_2_def": "so, as a result", "Opt_3_def": "about; not exactly", "Opt_4_def": "only, just, simply"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "If UVA is to increase level of satisfaction ____ junior faculty, it must make an effort to align its policies and practices more closely with the needs and expectations of the faculty.", "Opt_1": "beyond", "Opt_2": "against", "Opt_3": "due", "Opt_4": "among", "Answer": "among", "Opt_1_def": "further than: past", "Opt_2_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_3_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_4_def": "in, between"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The tax system must not discourage economic activity and it must not ____ from the tax systems in other countries.", "Opt_1": "explore", "Opt_2": "retain", "Opt_3": "diverge", "Opt_4": "override", "Answer": "diverge", "Opt_1_def": "to look into a place or thing (in order to learn more about it)", "Opt_2_def": "to keep", "Opt_3_def": "to move apart; to be different from", "Opt_4_def": "to take precedence over; to disregard"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Recent government IT initiatives focus narrowly on a specific technical problem, like enabling ____ data communication or Web-based transactions.", "Opt_1": "mobile", "Opt_2": "major", "Opt_3": "contemporary", "Opt_4": "relevant", "Answer": "mobile", "Opt_1_def": "moving; able to move", "Opt_2_def": "important, large", "Opt_3_def": "of this time, happening now", "Opt_4_def": "connected to the topic of discussion or consideration"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Please do not ____ me. I know what I said is correct.", "Opt_1": "provoke", "Opt_2": "contradict", "Opt_3": "exist", "Opt_4": "notice", "Answer": "contradict", "Opt_1_def": "to cause to happen", "Opt_2_def": "to say or show that what someone has said is wrong", "Opt_3_def": "to be alive, to be in the world", "Opt_4_def": "to see or realize"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The new Smartboard in my classroom must ____ a lot of energy. I've already had to change the bulb 3 times.", "Opt_1": "consume", "Opt_2": "exist", "Opt_3": "distribute", "Opt_4": "depend", "Answer": "consume", "Opt_1_def": "to use, or use up", "Opt_2_def": "to be alive, to be in the world", "Opt_3_def": "to give out", "Opt_4_def": "be influenced (by)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Niehuss does much to ____ the enormous impact of consumer culture on West German women's lives.", "Opt_1": "encourage", "Opt_2": "present", "Opt_3": "violate", "Opt_4": "illuminate", "Answer": "illuminate", "Opt_1_def": "to move someone to do something by positive talk; support or help", "Opt_2_def": "to give or show; to make a presentation", "Opt_3_def": "to spoil or break", "Opt_4_def": "to show clearly; to light up"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The government is bringing in a new law to require food manufacturers to ____ their products as high-, low- or medium fat.", "Opt_1": "arise", "Opt_2": "label", "Opt_3": "prefer", "Opt_4": "abandon", "Answer": "label", "Opt_1_def": "to happen", "Opt_2_def": "to give a name to someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "to like better", "Opt_4_def": "to leave or give up"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "She discussed the ____ for implementing the system through April 2003 and outlined several potential advantages of the system.", "Opt_1": "schedule", "Opt_2": "survey", "Opt_3": "coincidence", "Opt_4": "occasion", "Answer": "schedule", "Opt_1_def": "timetable", "Opt_2_def": "questionnaire; information gained by questioning people or data", "Opt_3_def": "an uncommon happening of two things", "Opt_4_def": "time (opportunity)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The government had to ____ from its starting position in the face of massive criticism in the newspapers.", "Opt_1": "persist", "Opt_2": "retreat", "Opt_3": "edit", "Opt_4": "complicate", "Answer": "retreat", "Opt_1_def": "to continue (often in the face of difficulty)", "Opt_2_def": "to go back", "Opt_3_def": "to make changes in a piece of writing", "Opt_4_def": "to make things more complex or difficult"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "You need to ____ on your admissions application that you will have 24 credits completed at the time of attendance.", "Opt_1": "correlate", "Opt_2": "motivate", "Opt_3": "investigate", "Opt_4": "indicate", "Answer": "indicate", "Opt_1_def": "to have a close connection", "Opt_2_def": "to get someone interested enough to do something", "Opt_3_def": "to find out what has happened or why something has happened", "Opt_4_def": "to show or convey"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "It operated below 60%, was generally poorly designed and therefore not ____ considering.", "Opt_1": "regarding", "Opt_2": "worth", "Opt_3": "except", "Opt_4": "prior", "Answer": "worth", "Opt_1_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_2_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_3_def": "but (not)", "Opt_4_def": "before"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Contrary to what you've been told by Courtney Love and the manipulated media reports, Kurt Cobain had no ____ for suicide.", "Opt_1": "supply", "Opt_2": "motive", "Opt_3": "dispute", "Opt_4": "section", "Answer": "motive", "Opt_1_def": "provision, store", "Opt_2_def": "reason", "Opt_3_def": "argument; conflict", "Opt_4_def": "part"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Army leadership must emphasize the importance of reducing energy ____ to decrease costs.", "Opt_1": "course", "Opt_2": "demand", "Opt_3": "victory", "Opt_4": "propensity", "Answer": "demand", "Opt_1_def": "a subject or period of study", "Opt_2_def": "a need or desire for", "Opt_3_def": "win", "Opt_4_def": "tendency; desire"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "This report draws on lessons learned from ____ military deployments to consider strategies to protect the health of troops in future deployments.", "Opt_1": "intense", "Opt_2": "military", "Opt_3": "infinite", "Opt_4": "previous", "Answer": "previous", "Opt_1_def": "strong, extreme", "Opt_2_def": "to do with army", "Opt_3_def": "without an end", "Opt_4_def": "the one before"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "A ____ in science or engineering usually pays more than one in manufacturing.", "Opt_1": "struggle", "Opt_2": "record", "Opt_3": "career", "Opt_4": "revolution", "Answer": "career", "Opt_1_def": "a fight, a difficult situation to be overcome", "Opt_2_def": "evidence; documentation", "Opt_3_def": "a long-term job", "Opt_4_def": "a time of great change"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "In order to match you up with the most ____ roommate we can, please fill out the Housing Intake Questionaire.", "Opt_1": "serious", "Opt_2": "various", "Opt_3": "reasonable", "Opt_4": "compatible", "Answer": "compatible", "Opt_1_def": "severe, large", "Opt_2_def": "several, of different kinds", "Opt_3_def": "acceptable, quite good", "Opt_4_def": "able to work with someone or something else"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Truman managed to win a narrow ____ with 49.5 percent of the popular vote.", "Opt_1": "victory", "Opt_2": "rank", "Opt_3": "access", "Opt_4": "opinion", "Answer": "victory", "Opt_1_def": "win", "Opt_2_def": "position (in a list or hierarchy)", "Opt_3_def": "the right to enter or use", "Opt_4_def": "view; what you think about someone or something"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Over the same period research was unable to ____ significant effects on achievement from readily available school characteristics.", "Opt_1": "recognize", "Opt_2": "measure", "Opt_3": "attempt", "Opt_4": "attract", "Answer": "measure", "Opt_1_def": "to know or understand (who someone is or what something is)", "Opt_2_def": "to find out how much there is of something", "Opt_3_def": "to try", "Opt_4_def": "to be interesting; to cause to like"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "It's no use trying to ____ me that your father speaks 10 languages. I just don't believe you.", "Opt_1": "avoid", "Opt_2": "convince", "Opt_3": "depart", "Opt_4": "review", "Answer": "convince", "Opt_1_def": "to not do something or go somewhere", "Opt_2_def": "to (try and) get someone to believe something", "Opt_3_def": "to leave; to be different from", "Opt_4_def": "to check over (and make changes)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "She found, however, that there is no documented process for achieving a wise ____ to adversity.", "Opt_1": "response", "Opt_2": "instruction", "Opt_3": "prospect", "Opt_4": "comment", "Answer": "response", "Opt_1_def": "answer or reply; reaction", "Opt_2_def": "advice or teaching how to do something; an order to do something", "Opt_3_def": "chance, likelihood", "Opt_4_def": "a short written or spoken statement or opinion"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "It was an ____ idea to allow the students to write their own test.", "Opt_1": "effective", "Opt_2": "fundamental", "Opt_3": "extraordinary", "Opt_4": "classic", "Answer": "extraordinary", "Opt_1_def": "good, working well", "Opt_2_def": "very important", "Opt_3_def": "very unusual", "Opt_4_def": "very good, the best or most used"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "At lunchtime students ____ to all parts of the school building and play areas.", "Opt_1": "remain", "Opt_2": "decrease", "Opt_3": "trade", "Opt_4": "disperse", "Answer": "disperse", "Opt_1_def": "to stay; still exist", "Opt_2_def": "to get smaller, to go down", "Opt_3_def": "to exchange products or services", "Opt_4_def": "to spread out; to move apart"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Doctors often fail in their attempt to ____ patients to stop smoking. The habit is too addictive.", "Opt_1": "enforce", "Opt_2": "donate", "Opt_3": "persuade", "Opt_4": "regard", "Answer": "persuade", "Opt_1_def": "to make something happen (particularly a law or regulation)", "Opt_2_def": "to give (usually money)", "Opt_3_def": "to try and make someone do something or agree to something", "Opt_4_def": "to think or have an opinion about something or someone"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "To launch the project, a special event will ____ at Stanford University's Center for Design Research at 11am today.", "Opt_1": "explain", "Opt_2": "commence", "Opt_3": "persuade", "Opt_4": "induce", "Answer": "commence", "Opt_1_def": "to give the reason for something or say how to do something", "Opt_2_def": "to start", "Opt_3_def": "to try and make someone do something or agree to something", "Opt_4_def": "to make happen; to force"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Science and technology are driving explosive growth in the production of new knowledge, often with the power to ____ profound changes in society.", "Opt_1": "devise", "Opt_2": "induce", "Opt_3": "stimulate", "Opt_4": "replace", "Answer": "induce", "Opt_1_def": "to create or think up", "Opt_2_def": "to make happen; to force", "Opt_3_def": "to interest, make grow or encourage", "Opt_4_def": "to put in or take the place of .."}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "You need to ____ the material covered by the homework problems in order to pass the quizzes and final examination.", "Opt_1": "exclude", "Opt_2": "dominate", "Opt_3": "attend", "Opt_4": "assimilate", "Answer": "assimilate", "Opt_1_def": "to leave out; opposite of include", "Opt_2_def": "to be much better, to play the most important part", "Opt_3_def": "to go to, to be present at", "Opt_4_def": "to take in"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Many of the world-wide organizations such as Greenpeace and Oxfam depend very heavily on ____ workers.", "Opt_1": "final", "Opt_2": "likely", "Opt_3": "voluntary", "Opt_4": "confident", "Answer": "voluntary", "Opt_1_def": "last", "Opt_2_def": "probable", "Opt_3_def": "done freely; from personal choice", "Opt_4_def": "sure that something will happen"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "He is an American ____ which obviously puts him in a different category from the kinds of individuals that the president has suggested might be suitable.", "Opt_1": "liberty", "Opt_2": "symbol", "Opt_3": "citizen", "Opt_4": "decade", "Answer": "citizen", "Opt_1_def": "freedom", "Opt_2_def": "a picture; the representation of an idea", "Opt_3_def": "person (member of a country)", "Opt_4_def": "a period of ten years"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "They must not be allowed to ____ the emergence of a competitive market economy.", "Opt_1": "present", "Opt_2": "affect", "Opt_3": "frustrate", "Opt_4": "classify", "Answer": "frustrate", "Opt_1_def": "to give or show; to make a presentation", "Opt_2_def": "to have an influence on", "Opt_3_def": "to stop or prevent", "Opt_4_def": "to put into a category or class"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "This is especially true from an investing ____ when repeating the same strategy could be a road to utter disaster.", "Opt_1": "detail", "Opt_2": "perspective", "Opt_3": "expense", "Opt_4": "power", "Answer": "perspective", "Opt_1_def": "a small piece of information", "Opt_2_def": "view; opinion; way of thinking", "Opt_3_def": "cost", "Opt_4_def": "the right or authority to do something"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "This page contains a ____ outline to be used as a guide for the creation of a strong outline.", "Opt_1": "profession", "Opt_2": "image", "Opt_3": "sample", "Opt_4": "factor", "Answer": "sample", "Opt_1_def": "job; occupation", "Opt_2_def": "picture", "Opt_3_def": "example; a smaller number of a larger collection", "Opt_4_def": "an aspect to be considered"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "You will ____ an email from the Financial Aid office when your financial aid eligibility has been determined.", "Opt_1": "receive", "Opt_2": "diminish", "Opt_3": "join", "Opt_4": "postpone", "Answer": "receive", "Opt_1_def": "to get", "Opt_2_def": "to get smaller or less important", "Opt_3_def": "to become a member (of an organization; to get together with others", "Opt_4_def": "to put back in time"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Different newspapers will often have a different ____ of the same event - especially newspapers from different parts of the world.", "Opt_1": "account", "Opt_2": "transition", "Opt_3": "intention", "Opt_4": "route", "Answer": "account", "Opt_1_def": "a written or spoken report of a happening", "Opt_2_def": "a move from one (place, time, etc.) to another", "Opt_3_def": "plan, aim", "Opt_4_def": "the way to get to a place or a thing"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "They ____ their nutrients from the air and not from the plant on which they are growing.", "Opt_1": "commit", "Opt_2": "impress", "Opt_3": "dictate", "Opt_4": "derive", "Answer": "derive", "Opt_1_def": "to do (often an offense)", "Opt_2_def": "to create a favourable reaction", "Opt_3_def": "to tell someone what to do", "Opt_4_def": "to come from or get from"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Because of their mobile lifestyle, they did not ____ many objects.", "Opt_1": "accumulate", "Opt_2": "fail", "Opt_3": "occur", "Opt_4": "notice", "Answer": "accumulate", "Opt_1_def": "to grow; to gather together", "Opt_2_def": "to not do something, or not work as expected; to do badly", "Opt_3_def": "to happen; take place", "Opt_4_def": "to see or realize"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "She ignored an ____ warning that she would be expelled if she did not start working harder.", "Opt_1": "concise", "Opt_2": "dynamic", "Opt_3": "explicit", "Opt_4": "accurate", "Answer": "explicit", "Opt_1_def": "short, not detailed", "Opt_2_def": "changing; growing; energetic", "Opt_3_def": "clearly and openly expressed", "Opt_4_def": "exact, containing no mistakes"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "It is especially important to remember that parents as a group have not usually taken the riding lessons and are not ____ to supervise their children.", "Opt_1": "valid", "Opt_2": "immediate", "Opt_3": "competent", "Opt_4": "ordinary", "Answer": "competent", "Opt_1_def": "correct", "Opt_2_def": "first (without delay)", "Opt_3_def": "good at something (often a job)", "Opt_4_def": "usual, typical, every day"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The government will ____ its announcement until it has up-to-date information.", "Opt_1": "postpone", "Opt_2": "recur", "Opt_3": "pursue", "Opt_4": "displace", "Answer": "postpone", "Opt_1_def": "to put back in time", "Opt_2_def": "to happen again", "Opt_3_def": "to follow (or do)", "Opt_4_def": "to push out or take the place of something or someone"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The political system must not be allowed to ____ into unlimited majority rule, which could result in the erosion of individual liberty.", "Opt_1": "degenerate", "Opt_2": "train", "Opt_3": "dedicate", "Opt_4": "abuse", "Answer": "degenerate", "Opt_1_def": "to get worse", "Opt_2_def": "to teach someone how to do a job", "Opt_3_def": "to devote (time and attention)", "Opt_4_def": "to treat someone or something badly"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The government is going to introduce a law that will ____ smoking in public places.", "Opt_1": "prohibit", "Opt_2": "convey", "Opt_3": "persist", "Opt_4": "receive", "Answer": "prohibit", "Opt_1_def": "to ban, disallow", "Opt_2_def": "to pass on to another person (often by speaking)", "Opt_3_def": "to continue (often in the face of difficulty)", "Opt_4_def": "to get"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Conversely, rising wage rates often ____ workers to try to work fewer hours as they become rich enough to afford more leisure.", "Opt_1": "assemble", "Opt_2": "induce", "Opt_3": "predict", "Opt_4": "condemn", "Answer": "induce", "Opt_1_def": "to get, put or bring together", "Opt_2_def": "to make happen; to force", "Opt_3_def": "to say what will happen in the future", "Opt_4_def": "to express strong disapproval"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "It is a ____ at the school for teachers to share a cake or cookies with their colleagues when it is their birthday.", "Opt_1": "tradition", "Opt_2": "domain", "Opt_3": "support", "Opt_4": "potential", "Answer": "tradition", "Opt_1_def": "a usual, old-time way of doing things", "Opt_2_def": "area (of interest)", "Opt_3_def": "help", "Opt_4_def": "good possibility"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The ____ of the urban districts, particularly in the Northern states, were totally averse to this development.", "Opt_1": "statement", "Opt_2": "decision", "Opt_3": "bulk", "Opt_4": "passage", "Answer": "bulk", "Opt_1_def": "a spoken sentence or sentences (sometimes prepared in advance)", "Opt_2_def": "intention to do something, choice", "Opt_3_def": "majority; largest part", "Opt_4_def": "a piece of written or spoken text"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The ____ family is expected to drive past the school tomorrow morning. The children will be standing by the road waving flags.", "Opt_1": "preliminary", "Opt_2": "royal", "Opt_3": "numerous", "Opt_4": "subjective", "Answer": "royal", "Opt_1_def": "first; initial", "Opt_2_def": "of kings and queens", "Opt_3_def": "very many", "Opt_4_def": "based on personal opinion or feeling"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The government did not proceed with the recommendations ____ the disability program and decided to review changes to the program.", "Opt_1": "among", "Opt_2": "except", "Opt_3": "regarding", "Opt_4": "instead", "Answer": "regarding", "Opt_1_def": "in, between", "Opt_2_def": "but (not)", "Opt_3_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_4_def": "in place of; rather than"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The government is thinking about introducing courses to ____ young people how to be good parents.", "Opt_1": "train", "Opt_2": "consider", "Opt_3": "include", "Opt_4": "cease", "Answer": "train", "Opt_1_def": "to teach someone how to do a job", "Opt_2_def": "to think", "Opt_3_def": "to put in; to have in", "Opt_4_def": "to stop"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "This is the first step to permanently limiting enrollment growth, something that seemed only a ____ possibility earlier this year.", "Opt_1": "effective", "Opt_2": "various", "Opt_3": "military", "Opt_4": "remote", "Answer": "remote", "Opt_1_def": "good, working well", "Opt_2_def": "several, of different kinds", "Opt_3_def": "to do with army", "Opt_4_def": "far, distant, small"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Freedom of speech is not the only ____ of democracy.", "Opt_1": "treatment", "Opt_2": "target", "Opt_3": "aspect", "Opt_4": "institution", "Answer": "aspect", "Opt_1_def": "way of handing a person, situation or problem (often of illness)", "Opt_2_def": "aim, goal", "Opt_3_def": "environment that lifts people up,\" says Jain.", "Opt_4_def": "a large organization; an important system or custom"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The pharmacy does not have ____ to your medical record, thus is unable to obtain insurance information from the health forms.", "Opt_1": "privilege", "Opt_2": "staff", "Opt_3": "schedule", "Opt_4": "access", "Answer": "access", "Opt_1_def": "a right (to do something)", "Opt_2_def": "people working at a particular place (particularly an office or school)", "Opt_3_def": "timetable", "Opt_4_def": "the right to enter or use"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "A headache may seem like a ____ problem, but it could be the sign of something more serious.", "Opt_1": "characteristic", "Opt_2": "probable", "Opt_3": "immense", "Opt_4": "trivial", "Answer": "trivial", "Opt_1_def": "typical", "Opt_2_def": "it is not probable that any thing better will be discovered than what was known to our fathers.", "Opt_3_def": "very large", "Opt_4_def": "not important"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The boss decided not to ____ her employee's request to leave work early.", "Opt_1": "lessen", "Opt_2": "approve", "Opt_3": "reflect", "Opt_4": "acquire", "Answer": "approve", "Opt_1_def": "to reduce", "Opt_2_def": "to agree to", "Opt_3_def": "to think or consider", "Opt_4_def": "to get or obtain"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The company's target for the year was to expand sales by \ufffd\ufffd2 million. Now they expect to exceed this ____ by 40%.", "Opt_1": "figure", "Opt_2": "relationship", "Opt_3": "individual", "Opt_4": "license", "Answer": "figure", "Opt_1_def": "number", "Opt_2_def": "the way to things are connected", "Opt_3_def": "one person", "Opt_4_def": "permission to do something (often an official document)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The correct interpretation of this text requires recovering ____ implicit information that relies on commonsense knowledge.", "Opt_1": "classic", "Opt_2": "former", "Opt_3": "certain", "Opt_4": "formal", "Answer": "certain", "Opt_1_def": "very good, the best or most used", "Opt_2_def": "previous, the one before, the first of two", "Opt_3_def": "sure", "Opt_4_def": "serious, not relaxed or everyday"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The headmaster was unable to ____ his proposal to lengthen the school day.", "Opt_1": "develop", "Opt_2": "collapse", "Opt_3": "hesitate", "Opt_4": "defend", "Answer": "defend", "Opt_1_def": "to grow or improve", "Opt_2_def": "to fall down completely and heavily; to fail", "Opt_3_def": "to pause before saying or doing something", "Opt_4_def": "to give reasons for"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "If the funding is from personal or family funds, you will need to obtain a current bank statement showing that you have enough funds to ____ expenses.", "Opt_1": "notice", "Opt_2": "allege", "Opt_3": "cover", "Opt_4": "confirm", "Answer": "cover", "Opt_1_def": "to see or realize", "Opt_2_def": "to claim or state", "Opt_3_def": "to do; to complete", "Opt_4_def": "to agree that something is correct"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The student was reported to the headmaster for continually trying to ____ the class.", "Opt_1": "risk", "Opt_2": "disturb", "Opt_3": "assume", "Opt_4": "disrupt", "Answer": "disrupt", "Opt_1_def": "to act in a way that might lead to danger or failure", "Opt_2_def": "to interrupt, stop from working", "Opt_3_def": "to believe to be true; to presume or predict", "Opt_4_def": "to interrupt an event; to damage"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "There was a ____ in language teaching about 40 years ago when the spoken language replaced writing and grammar as the main focus of teaching.", "Opt_1": "compensation", "Opt_2": "evidence", "Opt_3": "revolution", "Opt_4": "property", "Answer": "revolution", "Opt_1_def": "money (or some other reward) given to someone who has suffered a loss or injustice", "Opt_2_def": "proof, signs", "Opt_3_def": "a time of great change", "Opt_4_def": "the things that belong to someone, especially their home"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The company had to ____ their profit predictions after the cost of oil doubled within 6 months.", "Opt_1": "preserve", "Opt_2": "admit", "Opt_3": "accept", "Opt_4": "amend", "Answer": "amend", "Opt_1_def": "forward,\" said Michele Gougeon.", "Opt_2_def": "to allow to enter", "Opt_3_def": "to agree (to have)", "Opt_4_def": "to change (usually to improve something)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Before the accident he did not ____ his guns locked or unloaded; now he does.", "Opt_1": "amend", "Opt_2": "afford", "Opt_3": "store", "Opt_4": "transfer", "Answer": "store", "Opt_1_def": "to change (usually to improve something)", "Opt_2_def": "to be able to pay for something", "Opt_3_def": "to put something in a place where it can be found and used later", "Opt_4_def": "to move to a different place or job"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The management wanted to ____ the incompetent employee but could find no-one better to replace him.", "Opt_1": "reform", "Opt_2": "improve", "Opt_3": "abuse", "Opt_4": "dismiss", "Answer": "dismiss", "Opt_1_def": "to change and improve", "Opt_2_def": "to get better", "Opt_3_def": "to treat someone or something badly", "Opt_4_def": "to reject, to treat as unimportant"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Nevertheless, thirty-three years later, Israel is not willing to ____ from the Golan Heights to the 4 June 1967, prewar border.", "Opt_1": "approve", "Opt_2": "withdraw", "Opt_3": "contradict", "Opt_4": "appreciate", "Answer": "withdraw", "Opt_1_def": "to agree to", "Opt_2_def": "to go back or take away", "Opt_3_def": "to say or show that what someone has said is wrong", "Opt_4_def": "to understand (the value of someone or something)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The government has announced its ____ for the introduction of the new tax system over the next 5 years.", "Opt_1": "desire", "Opt_2": "assent", "Opt_3": "pattern", "Opt_4": "schedule", "Answer": "schedule", "Opt_1_def": "a want or wish for something", "Opt_2_def": "agreement", "Opt_3_def": "clear and consistent behaviour", "Opt_4_def": "timetable"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "One danger of any powerful ____ is that, at the height of its power, people confuse the ____ and the thing that is being compared to it.", "Opt_1": "image", "Opt_2": "apparatus", "Opt_3": "record", "Opt_4": "profit", "Answer": "image", "Opt_1_def": "picture", "Opt_2_def": "equipment; things you need to do a job", "Opt_3_def": "evidence; documentation", "Opt_4_def": "money gained"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "It's not enough to ____ something; you have to work hard to achieve it.", "Opt_1": "limit", "Opt_2": "labour", "Opt_3": "desire", "Opt_4": "criterion", "Answer": "desire", "Opt_1_def": "extent, boundary", "Opt_2_def": "work", "Opt_3_def": "a want or wish for something", "Opt_4_def": "a way to judge the value or importance of something"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Germany had to ____ a harsh peace treaty after being defeated in the first world war.", "Opt_1": "submit", "Opt_2": "accept", "Opt_3": "illuminate", "Opt_4": "develop", "Answer": "accept", "Opt_1_def": "to give; to send", "Opt_2_def": "to agree (to have)", "Opt_3_def": "to show clearly; to light up", "Opt_4_def": "to grow or improve"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "While a ____ degree of agreement was attained, a uniform approach to food policy could not be reached.", "Opt_1": "particular", "Opt_2": "consistent", "Opt_3": "considerable", "Opt_4": "trivial", "Answer": "considerable", "Opt_1_def": "specific", "Opt_2_def": "regular or predictable; remaining the same", "Opt_3_def": "very big; very much", "Opt_4_def": "not important"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The company directors made a ____ attempt to save the business by dismissing half the workforce.", "Opt_1": "drastic", "Opt_2": "widespread", "Opt_3": "average", "Opt_4": "stable", "Answer": "drastic", "Opt_1_def": "severe; great", "Opt_2_def": "common", "Opt_3_def": "ordinary, typical", "Opt_4_def": "not changing; not easy to change"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Examples of everyday fitness programs include walking during lunch hour, parking farther away from one's place of work, and taking stairs ____ of an elevator.", "Opt_1": "instead", "Opt_2": "except", "Opt_3": "against", "Opt_4": "beneath", "Answer": "instead", "Opt_1_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_2_def": "but (not)", "Opt_3_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_4_def": "below"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "In most school parents are asked to ____ to their child participating in sex education lessons.", "Opt_1": "label", "Opt_2": "magnify", "Opt_3": "disrupt", "Opt_4": "consent", "Answer": "consent", "Opt_1_def": "to give a name to someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "to make or show larger", "Opt_3_def": "to interrupt an event; to damage", "Opt_4_def": "to agree"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The partners realized that their small fund was not sufficient to support early stage start-ups in the ____ of the early 2000s.", "Opt_1": "design", "Opt_2": "status", "Opt_3": "incident", "Opt_4": "environment", "Answer": "environment", "Opt_1_def": "planning (drawing)", "Opt_2_def": "position, standing", "Opt_3_def": "happening; event", "Opt_4_def": "the world around us"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "It is impossible to revive any Yuan play in its ____ style because the music is lost and its social context has changed.", "Opt_1": "original", "Opt_2": "ancient", "Opt_3": "inherent", "Opt_4": "deficient", "Answer": "original", "Opt_1_def": "the first of its kind", "Opt_2_def": "very old", "Opt_3_def": "part of; a fundamental characteristic of", "Opt_4_def": "poor, lacking in quantity or quality"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The lesson plans contained an incomplete description of learners, their ____ and prior knowledge.", "Opt_1": "industry", "Opt_2": "background", "Opt_3": "shortage", "Opt_4": "assent", "Answer": "background", "Opt_1_def": "area of business ( often manufacturing )", "Opt_2_def": "family experiences; circumstances", "Opt_3_def": "lack; an amount which is less than needed", "Opt_4_def": "agreement"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "As people are defining a process or a problem, sometimes solutions emerge in that moment, in the ____ of their description.", "Opt_1": "outcome", "Opt_2": "amount", "Opt_3": "detail", "Opt_4": "formula", "Answer": "detail", "Opt_1_def": "result", "Opt_2_def": "how much there is of something", "Opt_3_def": "a small piece of information", "Opt_4_def": "a method of doing something"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Dhawan says that he is ____ that the summer rate cuts will prevent the economy from spiraling into a recession.", "Opt_1": "preliminary", "Opt_2": "spontaneous", "Opt_3": "fundamental", "Opt_4": "confident", "Answer": "confident", "Opt_1_def": "first; initial", "Opt_2_def": "happening without warning or planning", "Opt_3_def": "very important", "Opt_4_def": "sure that something will happen"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The best advice I can give is to ____ advice. Life is too short to be distracted by the opinions of others.", "Opt_1": "ignore", "Opt_2": "negotiate", "Opt_3": "suspend", "Opt_4": "advocate", "Answer": "ignore", "Opt_1_def": "to take no notice of; to leave out (of consideration)", "Opt_2_def": "to discuss (usually in politics or business)", "Opt_3_def": "to stop (often for a short time only)", "Opt_4_def": "to speak or write on behalf of someone or something"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Not all scientists agree that thought disorder and language disorder are ____ problems.", "Opt_1": "typical", "Opt_2": "discrete", "Opt_3": "minor", "Opt_4": "mobile", "Answer": "discrete", "Opt_1_def": "usual", "Opt_2_def": "separate", "Opt_3_def": "small, not important", "Opt_4_def": "moving; able to move"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Students should not ____ others of cheating unless there is clear evidence.", "Opt_1": "accuse", "Opt_2": "harm", "Opt_3": "represent", "Opt_4": "precede", "Answer": "accuse", "Opt_1_def": "to blame", "Opt_2_def": "to damage or injure", "Opt_3_def": "to be; to show or indicate", "Opt_4_def": "to go or be before someone or something"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Forests are both an important part of the global ecosystem and an important ____ of raw materials for lumber, paper, and fuelwood.", "Opt_1": "majority", "Opt_2": "shift", "Opt_3": "resource", "Opt_4": "objective", "Answer": "resource", "Opt_1_def": "more than 50%", "Opt_2_def": "change", "Opt_3_def": "a source of information or material", "Opt_4_def": "aim or goal"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "It is virtually impossible to predict which infants in the latter group will not ____ without support.", "Opt_1": "explore", "Opt_2": "forego", "Opt_3": "comply", "Opt_4": "survive", "Answer": "survive", "Opt_1_def": "to look into a place or thing (in order to learn more about it)", "Opt_2_def": "to do without; to give up", "Opt_3_def": "to do what someone asks or orders", "Opt_4_def": "to not die"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Venus will next ____ in the night sky in August 2007.", "Opt_1": "share", "Opt_2": "settle", "Opt_3": "govern", "Opt_4": "appear", "Answer": "appear", "Opt_1_def": "to exchange; to give", "Opt_2_def": "to solve a problem or dispute", "Opt_3_def": "to control or influence", "Opt_4_def": "to come, be seen"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "In recognition of your continuous satisfactory ____ to the university, you will receive an award at five-year intervals.", "Opt_1": "power", "Opt_2": "service", "Opt_3": "field", "Opt_4": "condition", "Answer": "service", "Opt_1_def": "the right or authority to do something", "Opt_2_def": "work done for others; help", "Opt_3_def": "area of interest or study", "Opt_4_def": "state"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The new version of Microsoft's Internet Explorer lets you ____ pictures by using the mouse ball and the Control key.", "Opt_1": "eliminate", "Opt_2": "add", "Opt_3": "magnify", "Opt_4": "tend", "Answer": "magnify", "Opt_1_def": "to dispose of", "Opt_2_def": "to include; to give or say extra", "Opt_3_def": "to make or show larger", "Opt_4_def": "to often behave in a certain way"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "It's good to see students of different nationalities ____ so naturally as they do at our school.", "Opt_1": "participate", "Opt_2": "condemn", "Opt_3": "contemplate", "Opt_4": "interact", "Answer": "interact", "Opt_1_def": "to take part", "Opt_2_def": "to express strong disapproval", "Opt_3_def": "to think about; to consider", "Opt_4_def": "to react, to affect and be affected"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "This program will ____ entry to the field and to advanced study of nutrition.", "Opt_1": "enforce", "Opt_2": "involve", "Opt_3": "accelerate", "Opt_4": "pursue", "Answer": "accelerate", "Opt_1_def": "to make something happen (particularly a law or regulation)", "Opt_2_def": "to include or mean", "Opt_3_def": "to get or make faster", "Opt_4_def": "to follow (or do)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "You can ____ all the things you need for class at the school's bookstore.", "Opt_1": "obtain", "Opt_2": "coordinate", "Opt_3": "adopt", "Opt_4": "seek", "Answer": "obtain", "Opt_1_def": "to get", "Opt_2_def": "to bring things or people together so that they work well", "Opt_3_def": "to take in; to start", "Opt_4_def": "to look for or want"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The case of Nicaragua demonstrates how the United States failed to ____ on the implementation of democratic procedures.", "Opt_1": "justify", "Opt_2": "postpone", "Opt_3": "insist", "Opt_4": "threaten", "Answer": "insist", "Opt_1_def": "to give a reason for doing something", "Opt_2_def": "to put back in time", "Opt_3_def": "to demand; to make a strong claim", "Opt_4_def": "to warn or show signs of danger"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "In order to self-correct your writing, you need to get an ____ diagnosis of your problems.", "Opt_1": "abstract", "Opt_2": "apparent", "Opt_3": "accurate", "Opt_4": "secure", "Answer": "accurate", "Opt_1_def": "not specific or concrete", "Opt_2_def": "clear; obvious", "Opt_3_def": "exact, containing no mistakes", "Opt_4_def": "safe"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "I think that everyone going for the maximum marks, the highest grades and the greatest possible output is not the best ____ for a well-rounded individual.", "Opt_1": "formula", "Opt_2": "interior", "Opt_3": "range", "Opt_4": "minimum", "Answer": "formula", "Opt_1_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_2_def": "inside", "Opt_3_def": "extent, distance between two points", "Opt_4_def": "the smallest amount; the least"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The UCLA Philharmonia, however, is bridging the gap between North and South campuses with two concerts that ____ symphony with science and history.", "Opt_1": "enforce", "Opt_2": "consist", "Opt_3": "combine", "Opt_4": "halt", "Answer": "combine", "Opt_1_def": "to make something happen (particularly a law or regulation)", "Opt_2_def": "to have in it; to have as part of it", "Opt_3_def": "to put or go together", "Opt_4_def": "to stop"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The company was in a very strong ____ after winning a million dollar contract to build its machines.", "Opt_1": "condition", "Opt_2": "duration", "Opt_3": "mechanism", "Opt_4": "priority", "Answer": "condition", "Opt_1_def": "state", "Opt_2_def": "period of time", "Opt_3_def": "procedure, process", "Opt_4_def": "first and most important task"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "In my opinion the government should ____ more to prevent young people drinking and driving.", "Opt_1": "prove", "Opt_2": "undertake", "Opt_3": "culminate", "Opt_4": "behave", "Answer": "undertake", "Opt_1_def": "to show to be true", "Opt_2_def": "to (plan to) do", "Opt_3_def": "to end", "Opt_4_def": "to act or do things in a certain way"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The government was fully ____ of the magnitude of its decision to go to war.", "Opt_1": "ordinary", "Opt_2": "subjective", "Opt_3": "aware", "Opt_4": "visual", "Answer": "aware", "Opt_1_def": "usual, typical, every day", "Opt_2_def": "based on personal opinion or feeling", "Opt_3_def": "knowing", "Opt_4_def": "to do with sight and seeing"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "A thought- provoking ____ suggests we should expect the extinction of intelligent life on Earth soon.", "Opt_1": "growth", "Opt_2": "bulk", "Opt_3": "commodity", "Opt_4": "argument", "Answer": "argument", "Opt_1_def": "development, increase", "Opt_2_def": "majority; largest part", "Opt_3_def": "a product; something you can buy", "Opt_4_def": "justification or reason (for an idea)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Some people use unethical methods to create a ____ that says what they want it to say.", "Opt_1": "function", "Opt_2": "tradition", "Opt_3": "phenomenon", "Opt_4": "statistic", "Answer": "statistic", "Opt_1_def": "job or role", "Opt_2_def": "a usual, old-time way of doing things", "Opt_3_def": "a happening (often unusual or unexpected)", "Opt_4_def": "mathematical number"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Burning of coal is a convenient way to ____ energy, but it creates a serious amount of pollution.", "Opt_1": "ruin", "Opt_2": "obtain", "Opt_3": "offer", "Opt_4": "migrate", "Answer": "obtain", "Opt_1_def": "to spoil or damage", "Opt_2_def": "to get", "Opt_3_def": "to ask if someone would like something (e.g. food or help)", "Opt_4_def": "to go to another place"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It was an ____ in how new communication technologies could serve a community's educational goals.", "Opt_1": "purpose", "Opt_2": "order", "Opt_3": "experiment", "Opt_4": "task", "Answer": "experiment", "Opt_1_def": "reason, goal", "Opt_2_def": "sequence, place", "Opt_3_def": "test", "Opt_4_def": "job"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The faculty member cannot refuse a reasonable request for extension of the project ____ date.", "Opt_1": "except", "Opt_2": "besides", "Opt_3": "despite", "Opt_4": "due", "Answer": "due", "Opt_1_def": "but (not)", "Opt_2_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_3_def": "although", "Opt_4_def": "as a result of, because of"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "In about 5 billion years, the sun will ____ its fuel supply, and will puff up into a bloated star called a red giant.", "Opt_1": "exhaust", "Opt_2": "replace", "Opt_3": "suspect", "Opt_4": "remain", "Answer": "exhaust", "Opt_1_def": "to use up", "Opt_2_def": "to put in or take the place of ..", "Opt_3_def": "to believe", "Opt_4_def": "to stay; still exist"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The company's financial performance has been ____ affected by the rising cost of oil.", "Opt_1": "respectively", "Opt_2": "eventually", "Opt_3": "namely", "Opt_4": "greatly", "Answer": "greatly", "Opt_1_def": "an expression used to refer to two things, one after the other", "Opt_2_def": "in the end", "Opt_3_def": "specifically, that is to say ( .. used to list or explain)", "Opt_4_def": "very much"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The teacher spoke so fast that it was difficult to ____ all the information he was giving.", "Opt_1": "refer", "Opt_2": "absorb", "Opt_3": "transfer", "Opt_4": "deprive", "Answer": "absorb", "Opt_1_def": "to direct (attention) to; to mean", "Opt_2_def": "to take in; to take up", "Opt_3_def": "to move to a different place or job", "Opt_4_def": "to take away (the opportunity)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "An ____ of English that many learners find difficult is verb grammar.", "Opt_1": "instruction", "Opt_2": "constraint", "Opt_3": "aspect", "Opt_4": "attack", "Answer": "aspect", "Opt_1_def": "advice or teaching how to do something; an order to do something", "Opt_2_def": "to hold back; to prevent", "Opt_3_def": "environment that lifts people up,\" says Jain.", "Opt_4_def": "to criticize; to attempt to harm or damage"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Unlike normal children she cannot attach its ____ meaning to the word \"blue\", so she cannot fully understand basic sentences.", "Opt_1": "convenient", "Opt_2": "steady", "Opt_3": "urban", "Opt_4": "ordinary", "Answer": "ordinary", "Opt_1_def": "easy, not causing problems", "Opt_2_def": "gradual; without interruptions; firm", "Opt_3_def": "of the town or city", "Opt_4_def": "usual, typical, every day"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "He was inspired by the dreams and disappointments of those individual schoolteachers who dared to challenge the ____ and follow their own visions toward a better future.", "Opt_1": "resource", "Opt_2": "assent", "Opt_3": "detail", "Opt_4": "hierarchy", "Answer": "hierarchy", "Opt_1_def": "a source of information or material", "Opt_2_def": "agreement", "Opt_3_def": "a small piece of information", "Opt_4_def": "organizational structure (e.g. showing who works for whom)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "With her departure we have decided to ____ teaching Spanish this fall as we await the committee report.", "Opt_1": "admit", "Opt_2": "engage", "Opt_3": "deduce", "Opt_4": "suspend", "Answer": "suspend", "Opt_1_def": "to allow to enter", "Opt_2_def": "to participate in; to focus attention on", "Opt_3_def": "to come to a conclusion about someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "to stop (often for a short time only)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Each student's ____ was so varied that I was unable to isolate common themes for discussion.", "Opt_1": "experience", "Opt_2": "element", "Opt_3": "assent", "Opt_4": "administration", "Answer": "experience", "Opt_1_def": "knowledge and skills gained over a long period of time", "Opt_2_def": "aspect, part", "Opt_3_def": "agreement", "Opt_4_def": "the people responsible for running an organization such as the government or a school"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The test will be a ____ of reading comprehension passages and short writing texts.", "Opt_1": "treatment", "Opt_2": "doubt", "Opt_3": "career", "Opt_4": "mixture", "Answer": "mixture", "Opt_1_def": "way of handing a person, situation or problem (often of illness)", "Opt_2_def": "a feeling of uncertainty (whether something is true)", "Opt_3_def": "a long-term job", "Opt_4_def": "combination"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "A sound card is an ____ component of a games computer.", "Opt_1": "essential", "Opt_2": "original", "Opt_3": "liable", "Opt_4": "fortunate", "Answer": "essential", "Opt_1_def": "very important", "Opt_2_def": "the first of its kind", "Opt_3_def": "likely to happen; at risk of happening", "Opt_4_def": "lucky"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "I ____ come to school by bus, but my father is driving me this week.", "Opt_1": "greatly", "Opt_2": "barely", "Opt_3": "generally", "Opt_4": "simply", "Answer": "generally", "Opt_1_def": "very much", "Opt_2_def": "not very much; hardly", "Opt_3_def": "usually", "Opt_4_def": "completely; just; only"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Furthermore, the system can also ____ environmental conditions in the immediate surroundings including ambient light level, humidity, and temperature.", "Opt_1": "prepare", "Opt_2": "measure", "Opt_3": "enable", "Opt_4": "arrange", "Answer": "measure", "Opt_1_def": "to get something ready (or to get ready for something)", "Opt_2_def": "to find out how much there is of something", "Opt_3_def": "to make something or someone able to do something", "Opt_4_def": "to plan to happen; to group together"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "It is not difficult to ____ on what could happen to these laws if the computer really does change our attitude to knowledge.", "Opt_1": "depart", "Opt_2": "judge", "Opt_3": "speculate", "Opt_4": "measure", "Answer": "speculate", "Opt_1_def": "to leave; to be different from", "Opt_2_def": "to give an opinion about someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "to think and talk about (often future events)", "Opt_4_def": "to find out how much there is of something"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The OCC provides counsel and legal advice in the development of policy, procedures, and ____ related to the management and operation of the UC Riverside campus.", "Opt_1": "design", "Opt_2": "access", "Opt_3": "strategy", "Opt_4": "description", "Answer": "strategy", "Opt_1_def": "planning (drawing)", "Opt_2_def": "the right to enter or use", "Opt_3_def": "a plan for how to achieve a goal", "Opt_4_def": "an account of what something is like or looks like"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Students may take a longer time to complete this program, but a ____ of two semesters shall be devoted to full-time work and normally the program must be completed within eight calendar years.", "Opt_1": "decade", "Opt_2": "minimum", "Opt_3": "tool", "Opt_4": "skill", "Answer": "minimum", "Opt_1_def": "a period of ten years", "Opt_2_def": "the smallest amount; the least", "Opt_3_def": "something used to do a job", "Opt_4_def": "ability (e.g. in sport or music)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The government is unpopular and is expected to fare badly in the ____ election.", "Opt_1": "forthcoming", "Opt_2": "available", "Opt_3": "urgent", "Opt_4": "formal", "Answer": "forthcoming", "Opt_1_def": "coming soon", "Opt_2_def": "can be had (bought or obtained)", "Opt_3_def": "very important, must be done immediately", "Opt_4_def": "serious, not relaxed or everyday"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The ____ between the United States and Mexico represents one of the greatest divisions of wealth on Earth.", "Opt_1": "vary", "Opt_2": "boundary", "Opt_3": "profit", "Opt_4": "alternative", "Answer": "boundary", "Opt_1_def": "to change or be different", "Opt_2_def": "limit, extent", "Opt_3_def": "money gained", "Opt_4_def": "other possibility"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "If this request is approved by the IRB, the researcher and his or her clinic ____ would be permitted to review the medical records.", "Opt_1": "deed", "Opt_2": "exhibit", "Opt_3": "magnitude", "Opt_4": "staff", "Answer": "staff", "Opt_1_def": "an action", "Opt_2_def": "to show", "Opt_3_def": "size; amount", "Opt_4_def": "people working at a particular place (particularly an office or school)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Despite the enormous amount of effort invested in her language teaching she was not able to ____ grammatical sentences.", "Opt_1": "measure", "Opt_2": "embody", "Opt_3": "dismiss", "Opt_4": "construct", "Answer": "construct", "Opt_1_def": "to find out how much there is of something", "Opt_2_def": "to be a good example of ..", "Opt_3_def": "to reject, to treat as unimportant", "Opt_4_def": "to make"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The Political Bureau will work to ensure the ____ progress of the reform of the administrative system.", "Opt_1": "prompt", "Opt_2": "smooth", "Opt_3": "remote", "Opt_4": "apparent", "Answer": "smooth", "Opt_1_def": "quick; on or before time", "Opt_2_def": "easy, unproblematic", "Opt_3_def": "far, distant, small", "Opt_4_def": "clear; obvious"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The government plans to ____ a new campaign to reduce teenage drinking.", "Opt_1": "involve", "Opt_2": "launch", "Opt_3": "acquire", "Opt_4": "disrupt", "Answer": "launch", "Opt_1_def": "to include or mean", "Opt_2_def": "to begin", "Opt_3_def": "to get or obtain", "Opt_4_def": "to interrupt an event; to damage"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The pharmacy does not have access to your medical record, ____ is unable to obtain insurance information from the health forms.", "Opt_1": "definitely", "Opt_2": "absolutely", "Opt_3": "merely", "Opt_4": "thus", "Answer": "thus", "Opt_1_def": "certainly; without doubt", "Opt_2_def": "completely; 100%", "Opt_3_def": "only, just, simply", "Opt_4_def": "so"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Asia is our closest region and essentially I feel that we need more understanding and ____ culturally to make sense of where we all are'.", "Opt_1": "purchase", "Opt_2": "exchange", "Opt_3": "suppress", "Opt_4": "neglect", "Answer": "exchange", "Opt_1_def": "to buy", "Opt_2_def": "to give or change one thing and get a different thing", "Opt_3_def": "to hold back; to not allow to happen", "Opt_4_def": "to not think about or care for"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "It is scheduled to begin at 3:30 p.m. A decision to cancel or ____ the match will be made later in the day, if necessary.", "Opt_1": "signify", "Opt_2": "confirm", "Opt_3": "postpone", "Opt_4": "gather", "Answer": "postpone", "Opt_1_def": "to mean; to be a sign of", "Opt_2_def": "to agree that something is correct", "Opt_3_def": "to put back in time", "Opt_4_def": "to bring or get together"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "During the period of time that a student is on probation, any further ____ of misconduct will cause the Board seriously to consider requiring the student to withdraw from the College.", "Opt_1": "impulse", "Opt_2": "sequence", "Opt_3": "instance", "Opt_4": "episode", "Answer": "instance", "Opt_1_def": "reason or motivation to do something", "Opt_2_def": "the order in which things are arranged or happen", "Opt_3_def": "example", "Opt_4_def": "period of time"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Over the course of her ____ in the program she has come a great distance from her primary focus as an agent for FEMA.", "Opt_1": "interpretation", "Opt_2": "journey", "Opt_3": "location", "Opt_4": "education", "Answer": "journey", "Opt_1_def": "explanation; assessment", "Opt_2_def": "a long trip to a different place", "Opt_3_def": "place, where something or someone is", "Opt_4_def": "schooling"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The government will never win the ____ against drug-taking.", "Opt_1": "exercise", "Opt_2": "display", "Opt_3": "battle", "Opt_4": "item", "Answer": "battle", "Opt_1_def": "a piece of work, activity", "Opt_2_def": "a show, demonstration, illustration", "Opt_3_def": "fight, part of a war", "Opt_4_def": "thing, element"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The hypothesis put forward in this paper depends in no ____ upon the completeness of our knowledge of the former condition of the organic world.", "Opt_1": "degree", "Opt_2": "programme", "Opt_3": "figure", "Opt_4": "distance", "Answer": "degree", "Opt_1_def": "amount", "Opt_2_def": "a course of lessons; a project", "Opt_3_def": "number", "Opt_4_def": "how far it is from one place to another"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It was only one stage in a long ____ that did not come to a legal end until 1971.", "Opt_1": "diagram", "Opt_2": "criterion", "Opt_3": "struggle", "Opt_4": "manner", "Answer": "struggle", "Opt_1_def": "a type of picture or chart", "Opt_2_def": "a way to judge the value or importance of something", "Opt_3_def": "a fight, a difficult situation to be overcome", "Opt_4_def": "way of doing something"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "If you discover that you have the wrong textbook, you must ____ the source from which you purchased the book and make arrangements to exchange the book.", "Opt_1": "offend", "Opt_2": "contact", "Opt_3": "observe", "Opt_4": "constitute", "Answer": "contact", "Opt_1_def": "to go against; to upset", "Opt_2_def": "to get in touch (e.g. by phone or email)", "Opt_3_def": "to watch carefully", "Opt_4_def": "to be; to make up"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Could you please ____ this book to its proper place on the shelf.", "Opt_1": "restore", "Opt_2": "recover", "Opt_3": "induce", "Opt_4": "obey", "Answer": "restore", "Opt_1_def": "to put back, create again", "Opt_2_def": "to get back", "Opt_3_def": "to make happen; to force", "Opt_4_def": "to do as commanded or expected"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Sometimes it is necessary to ____ a limit on the number of solutions searched for, since in general the number of such solutions could be infinite.", "Opt_1": "impose", "Opt_2": "regret", "Opt_3": "train", "Opt_4": "enhance", "Answer": "impose", "Opt_1_def": "to force; to require to happen", "Opt_2_def": "to feel sorry (for doing or saying something)", "Opt_3_def": "to teach someone how to do a job", "Opt_4_def": "to make something better"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Desdemona is passive for much of the play and when she dies at the end, she takes the ____ for her death.", "Opt_1": "forego", "Opt_2": "blame", "Opt_3": "inspect", "Opt_4": "reform", "Answer": "blame", "Opt_1_def": "to do without; to give up", "Opt_2_def": "to accuse", "Opt_3_def": "to look at carefully", "Opt_4_def": "to change and improve"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The additional time is necessary to enable him to make a sound ____ on an Alaska natural gas transportation system.", "Opt_1": "decision", "Opt_2": "issue", "Opt_3": "design", "Opt_4": "perspective", "Answer": "decision", "Opt_1_def": "intention to do something, choice", "Opt_2_def": "a matter or problem", "Opt_3_def": "planning (drawing)", "Opt_4_def": "view; opinion; way of thinking"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Science should be about objective facts, not ____ opinions.", "Opt_1": "infinite", "Opt_2": "substantial", "Opt_3": "ordinary", "Opt_4": "subjective", "Answer": "subjective", "Opt_1_def": "without an end", "Opt_2_def": "large", "Opt_3_def": "usual, typical, every day", "Opt_4_def": "based on personal opinion or feeling"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "You can take any book ____ this one. I'm reading it.", "Opt_1": "beyond", "Opt_2": "due", "Opt_3": "except", "Opt_4": "among", "Answer": "except", "Opt_1_def": "further than: past", "Opt_2_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_3_def": "but (not)", "Opt_4_def": "in, between"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The situation in Iraq continues to ____ the government's attention.", "Opt_1": "cancel", "Opt_2": "criticize", "Opt_3": "contemplate", "Opt_4": "occupy", "Answer": "occupy", "Opt_1_def": "to cut or stop from happening", "Opt_2_def": "to express disapproval; to say what you don't like or think is good about something or someone", "Opt_3_def": "to think about; to consider", "Opt_4_def": "to up space or time"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "You must try to ____ a balance between work and play. At the moment it's too much play!", "Opt_1": "achieve", "Opt_2": "identify", "Opt_3": "terminate", "Opt_4": "convey", "Answer": "achieve", "Opt_1_def": "to gain or get something (often academic success)", "Opt_2_def": "to know or say who or what something is", "Opt_3_def": "to finish or stop", "Opt_4_def": "to pass on to another person (often by speaking)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Picasso's ____ to draw found expression in a variety of forms.", "Opt_1": "duty", "Opt_2": "balance", "Opt_3": "impulse", "Opt_4": "credit", "Answer": "impulse", "Opt_1_def": "responsibility, or job that you are required to do", "Opt_2_def": "equalness", "Opt_3_def": "reason or motivation to do something", "Opt_4_def": "gained on completing a course of study; praise"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "One of the most common laments we hear from instructor is that they can't get their students to ____ substantial revisions.", "Opt_1": "contradict", "Opt_2": "tolerate", "Opt_3": "ruin", "Opt_4": "undertake", "Answer": "undertake", "Opt_1_def": "to say or show that what someone has said is wrong", "Opt_2_def": "to allow to happen; to bear", "Opt_3_def": "to spoil or damage", "Opt_4_def": "to (plan to) do"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Throughout the day, with a brief ____ for lunch, he stared at the history project which was due the next morning.", "Opt_1": "contrary", "Opt_2": "interval", "Opt_3": "shortage", "Opt_4": "degree", "Answer": "interval", "Opt_1_def": "opposite", "Opt_2_def": "a period of time", "Opt_3_def": "lack; an amount which is less than needed", "Opt_4_def": "amount"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Women often earn less money that men doing the same job. This ____ must be stopped.", "Opt_1": "innovation", "Opt_2": "scheme", "Opt_3": "anomaly", "Opt_4": "hypothesis", "Answer": "anomaly", "Opt_1_def": "new object or idea", "Opt_2_def": "plan. idea, project", "Opt_3_def": "an unexpected happening or piece of data", "Opt_4_def": "idea or prediction"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "There is a ____ of toilets in the school. Every time I want to use one, it is occupied.", "Opt_1": "comparison", "Opt_2": "shortage", "Opt_3": "drawback", "Opt_4": "resource", "Answer": "shortage", "Opt_1_def": "a statement of how two things are similar or different", "Opt_2_def": "lack; an amount which is less than needed", "Opt_3_def": "disadvantage, problem", "Opt_4_def": "a source of information or material"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Doing so will probably ____ a strong negative response from the group's normal readership.", "Opt_1": "restore", "Opt_2": "enlarge", "Opt_3": "contain", "Opt_4": "provoke", "Answer": "provoke", "Opt_1_def": "to put back, create again", "Opt_2_def": "to make larger", "Opt_3_def": "to have in it; to hold inside", "Opt_4_def": "to cause to happen"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "This is especially true in the environmental sciences where many of the systems are dynamic and ____ complex.", "Opt_1": "extremely", "Opt_2": "thus", "Opt_3": "generally", "Opt_4": "simultaneously", "Answer": "extremely", "Opt_1_def": "very", "Opt_2_def": "so", "Opt_3_def": "usually", "Opt_4_def": "at the same time"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Increased ____ caused consumers to spend more and firms to invest more.", "Opt_1": "error", "Opt_2": "labour", "Opt_3": "income", "Opt_4": "opinion", "Answer": "income", "Opt_1_def": "a mistake", "Opt_2_def": "work", "Opt_3_def": "money earned", "Opt_4_def": "view; what you think about someone or something"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Part of the job of an ESL teacher in an international school is to ____ the need to make work comprehensible to non-native speakers.", "Opt_1": "dismiss", "Opt_2": "develop", "Opt_3": "acquire", "Opt_4": "advocate", "Answer": "advocate", "Opt_1_def": "to reject, to treat as unimportant", "Opt_2_def": "to grow or improve", "Opt_3_def": "to get or obtain", "Opt_4_def": "to speak or write on behalf of someone or something"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "You have learned this lesson that water and other liquids ____ sound better than air.", "Opt_1": "stress", "Opt_2": "transmit", "Opt_3": "manufacture", "Opt_4": "engage", "Answer": "transmit", "Opt_1_def": "to emphasize; to say what is important", "Opt_2_def": "to send or convey", "Opt_3_def": "to produce (with machines)", "Opt_4_def": "to participate in; to focus attention on"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "This is especially true from an investing perspective when repeating the same strategy could be a road to ____ disaster.", "Opt_1": "utter", "Opt_2": "numerous", "Opt_3": "invisible", "Opt_4": "intrinsic", "Answer": "utter", "Opt_1_def": "complete, total", "Opt_2_def": "very many", "Opt_3_def": "cannot be seen", "Opt_4_def": "belonging to; inherent in"}]]